字幕由爆炸的头骨提供来源www.OpenSubtitles.org
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
上帝啊 你创造了我
♪ I'm just what you made, God ♪
但我没有那么信任你
- ♪ Not many I trust ♪
上帝啊 我坚持走自己的路
♪ I'm-a go my own way, God ♪
你想如何摆弄我的命运都行
♪ Take my fate to wherever you want ♪
我就在这里
♪ I'm out here, on my son ♪
不达目的不罢休
♪ Won't stop till I get me some ♪
我流连酒吧忘返
♪ Club hopping trying to get me some ♪
坏女人企图让我春心荡漾
♪ Bad bitches wanna get me sprung ♪
清晨醒来 浑身灼热
♪ Early in the morning I'm waking, baking ♪
一边喝酒一边冥想
♪ Drinking  contemplating ♪
撒旦啥的不存在的
♪ Ain't no such thing as Satan ♪
恶魔都是你造出来的
♪ Evil is what you make it ♪
感谢上帝 让那灌木燃烧
♪ Thank the Lord for that burning bush ♪
天生我才逐大奔
♪ That big-body Benz I was born to push ♪
我要点燃 Kush
♪ On my way, I'm burning kush ♪
黑人兄弟不要担心我们
♪ Nigga, don't beworried 'bout us ♪
邻居来敲门
♪ Neighbors knocking on the door ♪
让我们调低音量
♪ Asking can we turn it down... ♪
我去
Jesus!
没有音乐
- ♪ Ain't no music... ♪
我  我要
- ♪ I ♪ ♪ I need ♪
要抽烟
♪ Need smoke ♪
喔喔喔
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
我需要
- ♪ I need ♪
我
♪ I... ♪
不是故意的 不好意思啊
Sorry. I'm sorry.
要抽烟
♪ To smoke ♪
谁能阻挡的了我
♪ Who gon' hold me down now? ♪
我要嗨爆全场
♪ I wanna get high, y'all ♪
哦喔
- ♪ Whoa ♪
我要嗨爆全场
♪ I wanna get high, y'all ♪
要过得去 过得去
♪ Need it, need it to get by... ♪
不好意思 不好意思啊
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
要过得去
♪ Need it to get by, y'all. ♪
回来
Get back!
我喜欢这个电影
I love this movie.
他们在斯塔顿岛拍的这个剧
They-they shot this on Staten Island.
唷   哦
- Whew! - Oh!
哦 我的妈呀
- Oh! - Ooh, God!
赞哪  对啊
- Awesome.- Hell yeah.
唷
- Ew!
对我的口儿
That's my shit.
这电影逻辑不对啊
This movie makes no sense.
为什么 为什么政府允许人类清除计划的存在
Why-why would the government make a purge legal?
很明显他们是来泄愤的撒 是啊
- Clearly to let them blow off some steam. Hello.- Yeah.
那你可以去做水疗啊 是的 或是去找心理医生啊
- That's why you go to the spa. - Yeah. Or the therapist.
或者去做指甲 或者
- Or get your nails done. -  Or...
或者杀点人咯
Or murder some folks. Hmm?
我说 大家伙儿 我把Tara带来
I mean, come on, guys. I-I brought Tara over
就是为了让大家走出这个地下室
so that we could get out of this basement.
我们出门儿玩儿吧  去蹦迪吧
Let's go out. Let's go dancing.
我喜欢蹦迪  出门走走吧
- I love dancing. - Let's do something.
我们不约
We don't go out.
我们不蹦迪
We don't dance.
看《人类清除计划》 还不够 -不够
- The Purge is not enough for you? - No.
还有谁喜欢蹦迪的
Does anybody else like dancing?
我喜欢 是的 我
- I like it.-  Yes, me!
你喜欢   我喜欢蹦迪
- You do? - I love dancing.
是的
Yes.
他超爱  他蹦得可好了呢
He loves... He's a really good dancer.
你最喜欢的招式是
What's your favorite move?
就那种有律动的摇摆
It's kind of like a shake.
摇摆 额   说不上来啦
- A shake? That's...- I don't know.
就跟着音乐摇摆呗
I just do whatever the m-music tells me to do.
就是舞池里的混蛋
There's nothing but douchebags at these clubs.
我喜欢呆这里 安全  噢 别这样嘛
- I love it here, man. It's safe.- Oh, but, come on.
你这是打算坐这里一整天
God, you just sit here all day,
吸大麻 然后一起滚床单吗
- and then smoke weed and jerk each other off.
- Yeah.
挺好的呀
That sounds amazing.
我都没和我朋友滚过呢
I've never been jerked off by any of my friends.
我也没有
Me, either.
我蛮喜欢你纹身的诶
I like your tattoos.
我就知道你会喜欢  那些是
- I knew you would, right? - Those are...
哦 我去  别 被跟他搞
- Oh, my God. That...
- No, don't talk to him.
他有 他有披衣菌  我治好了好吗
- He has, he has chlamydia. - I had.
我的天   我曾经是有披衣菌
- Oh, my God. - Had chlamydia.
那是可治愈的毛病  是你介绍给我认识的妹子传给我的
- It's curable.- And you introduced me to the girl that gave me chlamydia,
所以是你让我染上的披衣菌
so you basically gave me chlamydia.
你助长了披衣菌的传播
You assisted the chlamydia.
他没有医保
He doesn't have insurance.
他没那钱治的  还好啦
- He can't get the meds. -  It's fine.
事实上我也搞过那些纹身
I act... I actually did some of those.
哦
You did?
你知道我老喜欢那个岛了
You know I got to rep the island.
是呢 斯塔顿岛  哇喔  斯塔顿嘢
-  Hey. - Staten Island. -  Wow, Staten.
你懂的  嗯
- S.I., you know. - Yeah.
看起来很赞哦  谢谢
- Looks so good. - Thank you.
你也有一堆纹身诶  是啊
- You have a bunch of tattoos also. - Yeah.
那个日期是啥意思  啊 哦（准备看戏）
- What is that date? - Oh.  Ooh.
额 那天我爸去世了
Uh, that's, uh, the date my Dad died.
啊天哪 你爹去世了啊 不好意思啊
Oh, my God, your dad died? I'm so sorry.
没啥的啦 还好了 不用介怀
Don't be. It's fine. It's totally cool.
怎么去世的呀 唉唉唉
- So, what happened? -  Ooh!
你就别问了吧   别
- Okay, you don't need to ask. - No.
别别别  别问了
- No, no, no, no. - Don't ask that.
不是太礼貌啊
It's kind of inappropriate.
额 他是个 消防员
Uh, he was a, he was a fireman.
所以 他死于一场火灾
So, he died in a fire.
我的天
Oh, my God.
我们知道啊 我们知道啊
- Yeah, we knew. - Yeah, we knew.
只是我们不提而已 我们知道
- We don't like to talk about it. - We knew.
所以我们才不提的呀
That's why we don't bring it up.
跟Scott道个歉啊  是不应该提呢
- Apologize to Scott.- It's the right thing to do.
你得道歉  不道歉就滚出去吧
- You should say sorry. - Apologize or get out.
不应该这样的
It's not okay.
Scott 额 我只想说我真心抱歉啊
Scott, um, I just wanted to say that I'm really sorry
我不该问你纹身含义的  么事呢
- that I asked about your tattoo.-  Yeah.
怎么了
What?
他不介意的啦 还好了
He doesn't care. It's fine.
他不介意的   你看他
-  He doesn't care. - Look at him.
他一直在笑  我没事啦
- He's laughing so much. -  I don't care.
我们经常提起他过世的老爹的啦
We talk about his dead dad all the time.
咚咚咚  谁呀
- Knock, knock. - Who's there?
不是你爹啊
Not your dad.
我最喜欢这个梗了
-  That's my favorite one.
我去 太好笑了
Oh, my God, that's so funny.
我们经常拿这个打趣儿
We've made so many jokes about it.
我去 我一点儿
Oh, my God, I don't even...
我一点儿都不想他  太搞笑了
- I don't even miss him at all. -  So funny.
是啊
Yeah.
哦
Oh!
哦 是的 就是这样 很好啊
Oh, yeah, yeah,that's pretty good.
就这样 就是这样
Keep-keep doing that! Keep doing that!
你爽吗
- Are-are you, are you happy?
爽爽 老娘太爽了 就这样接着来
Yes, yes, it's fucking great! Keep going!
别停 别停
No, wait, d-d... don't stop!
额 你高潮了吗
Did you, um, did you, did you come?
嘿嘿 有呀
Well, yes.
你呢 高潮了吗
Were you there?
我反正高潮了
Yeah, I did.
高潮了6 趟  挺好
- Like, six times.- Cool.
很赞哦 刚才这炮挺好
- Awesome. - It was great.
你呢  没有诶
- Did you? - No, no, no.
但是没事儿啊  我挺开心的
But it's okay. I-I had fun.
我感觉也挺好
I had fun back there.
是嘛
Yeah.
我很遗憾都没有满足到你
You know, I feel bad that you never do.
不 我很满足啊
No, I-I do all the time.
我只是没有你表现的那么明显而已
I just... you know, I don't put on a Broadway show like you do.
我比较安静
You know, I'm-I'm more quiet.
我的高潮跟卓别林哑剧比较像
I'm more like Charlie Chaplin when I come.
像看哑剧一样的爽  对就是这样
- Like a silent movie.- Silent movie.
额 你觉得是因为抗抑郁的药物的作用吗
Um, do you think it's the antidepressants?
嗯 是吧
Oh, yeah, for sure.
是啊 如果不是吃了抗抑郁的药
Yeah. If I didn't have the antidepressants,
我8秒就射了
I'd come in, like, eight seconds.
然后你的高潮就没有了
And then you wouldn't come.
然后你会抑郁的
And then you'd be depressed.
然后你就得吃抗抑郁的药了
And then you would have to take antidepressants.
我不知道呢 我能发表下我的想法么我  你说
- I don't know, can I say something? I, um...- Yeah.
我就是不能理解为啥咱俩要这般偷鸡摸狗呢
I just still don't understand why this is such a big secret.
你懂为什么的呀 因为咱俩这是特殊关系呀
You know why it's a big secret.'Cause it's special.
这是我们之间的小秘密啊。
It's-it's, like, our thing, you know?
如果大家都知道了我们的关系就不特殊了呢
It-it wouldn't be special if everybody knew about it.
话虽如此 但我不想我俩只是这样的关系啊
Yeah, but I don't just want to do this.
懂 我理解  那我们以后还要这么搞么
Yeah, I totally get that. So, should we stop?
我不是这个意思
No, I...
我不知道怎么说 我们这算什么呀
I don't know, like, this... like, what is this?
我不知道为啥  这关系
- And I don't know why... - This?
咱们这是   我只想像正常人一样
- This is... - I want to do what normal people do.
我懂 我只是 你知道的 我
Yeah, I know. I just, you know, I...
公开很奇怪啊
It-it might be weird, you know.
我们都认识对方那么久了
We've known each other for, like, ever.
从小学四年级开始吧
Since fourth grade.
公开的话感觉像乱伦一样
It would be like incest.
不会啦
No, it wouldn't.
会啊 感觉就是我们一直是好朋友
No, it's like, yeah, w-we're best pals,
我不想因为这个伤到 我们的友谊
and I wouldn't want to, like,jeopardize our friendship
或者友谊就被其他什么取代了
or something like that over something...
不是不对 就是这样风险很大
not silly, but, you know, it's just... it's a big risk.
但是我们已经发生关系了呀
But we've already done the deed.
我说还有啥阻碍的  已经发生关系了
- I mean, what else is there? - "Done the deed"?
我不知道啦 但是
-  I don't know.- But, you know, it's just,
你以后一定会遇到一个比我更好的人  什么
- you deserve somebody way better than me. - What?
你已经很好了
You're a good guy.
你很好啊 我喜欢你  额
- You're a good guy. I like you.- Uh...
好吧  你为什么这么说
Well, I... Based on what?
我也喜欢你啊 就像
I mean, I like you, too. It's just like...
好吧 我 跟你说 我可以跟你说个事儿么
All right, can I just tell you... can I tell you something?
但只有你知道不要告诉别人
But can you, like, not tell anybody?
可能别人也知道吧 但是 就像
Well, people probably know, but, like... (sighs)
我可能有毛病
There's, like, something wrong with me.
精神疾病  啥
- Like, mentally, like... - What?
我发病的时候
Like, I'm not okay up there.
就像
You know? Like...
我会变得癫狂 像疯子一样
I-I get all mad, acting, like, crazy,
然后我真的会神志不清 做一些冲动的事情
and I, and I make really insane,impulsive decisions.
然后我
And I get...
我自己都怕自己 但我不想
I'm d... I'm scared o-of myself, and I don't...
我不想吓到你或和我自己
I don't want to, like, scare you or me
或者伤到其他人 你懂吗
or, like, hurt anyone, you know?
所以我想最好
So, I think it would just be best
我应该还是离你远点好
and really responsible of me if I just backed off, you know?
你不要这么想你自己嘛
I don't want you to f-feel like that about yourself.
不是我这么想自己 是
Oh, no, it's...
我只是我不想冒犯到你 懂么
I just, I just don't want to offend you, you know?
你最好了 你是（世界上）最好的人
You're... you're the best. I think you're the greatest.
我知道你觉得我很好 我是很好
I know you think I'm great. I'm awesome.
我只是很抱歉你看低了你自己
I feel bad that you don't think you're great.
早啊 亲爱的
Hey, honey.
我给你做了煎蛋卷
I made you an omelet.
你打算穿啥去你妹妹的毕业典礼啊
What are you gonna wear to your sister's graduation party?
我在想要要不你穿你爹的西服吧
I was thinking, what about one of your dad's suits?
我知道啊
I don't know.
我觉得不太适合穿西服吧
I-I don't think I'm really a suit guy, you know?
再说那些西服都过时了 所以
Plus-plus, all those suits are out of style, so...
我觉得他们很复古啊
You know, I thought they were back in style.
还有你去聚会前咱能不吸大麻么
And... can you not smoke pot before the party?
为毛
Why?
因为太臭了 到时你浑身都裹着臭味
Because it smells. You smell bad.
也别吸电子烟 不然人家会以为你吸了大麻
And no vaping because they're gonna think it's pot.
那个叔叔是个警察
The uncle is a cop.
我们别给自己找麻烦
We don't need that kind of trouble.
去他妈的
Fuck that guy.
我讨厌这个家
I hate this family.
他们浑身铜臭又傲慢
They're so rich and snooty.
他们对Clare很好啊
They've been really nice to Claire.
嘿 老妈 可以给几个塑料箱子么
Hey, Mom. You got me the plastic containers.
我只需要几个纸箱丢不要的东西
I just need the cardboard boxes I can throw away.
但是他们很擅长分类
But they're so good for storing things.
我没啥需要收纳的
Yeah, but I don't have any storage.
我衣橱只有两尺宽呢
- My closet's, like, two feet wide.
嘿 Chaire 你要我去你毕业典礼么
Hey, Claire, do you even want me at your graduation party?
我想让你去吗 我是无所谓了
Do I want you to go? I don't care.
只是 你不去会显得很奇怪
Just... It's weird if you don't go.
好像不是很想我去啊
That wasn't exactly a warm invitation.
哈 好吧 我也不是很想邀请你
Yeah, well, it's not the part I'm looking forward to most.
但我想你他还是去吧
But I want you to be there.
她邀请你去了  不她不想
She wants you to go.  No, she doesn't.
她刚说了呀   不 我不想他去
- She just said it.-  No, I don't want him to go.
他得去
He has to go.
就不要全程缩在沙发上的一个角落就行
Just don't sit on the couch in the corner the whole time.
太诡异了  我没觉得
- It's weird. - No, I don't see the problem
坐在一个角落里有啥问题啊
with sitting in the corner, okay?
聚会上有些人会去舞池里跳舞
There's some people that go to the party and dance,
有些人就是会坐在角落看而已
and there's some people that sit in the corner.
我就是那个坐角落的人而已
I'm the corner guy.
爱不爱 你哥哥我就是这样一个人
Accept your brother.
还有别想 跟Layla上床啊
Also, don't try to fuck Layla, okay?
她都跟你说了她对你没兴趣
She told you she's not interested.
你说啥呢
What are you talking about?
我从来没想跟她在一起啊
I never tried to hook up with her.
是她自己一直想勾搭我 我考虑到你的感受
She's always trying to fuck me,and I-I have to avoid it
不惜一切代价 躲着她
at all costs, out of respect for you.
我只是觉得她穿裤子很好看而已
I just thought she looked really good in those pants.
我去 这是个称赞好吧
- Jesus. - Thought that was a nice thing to say.
别说了 我还以为你会回应我你也赞同呢
- Just don't. - I didn't know I would get MeToo'd for it.
你爹的西服塑封着放在车库里
Dad's suits are vacuum-sealed in the garage.
哦   你自己选个中意的吧
- Yeah? - Just pick yourself a nice one.
你得好好打扮下
You have to look nice.
我们是去庆祝你妹妹获得的成就的
We're celebrating your sister's achievements.
等她不在了你会想她的
You're gonna miss her when she's gone.
是啊 为我庆祝吧
Yeah. Celebrate me.
哇 时间过得真快呀
Wow, this, uh... this all happened so fast.
真不敢相信你这么就毕业了
I-I can't believe you're graduating already.
我会想你的
I'm gonna really miss you.
第二回合
Round two.
开打
- Fight!
哟 你从哪儿搞到这个的啊
Yo, where'd you get this?
这玩意儿味道不是很好啊
This shit does not taste very good.
你说啥呢 这玩意儿很猛的 不识货的家伙
What are you talking about? This shit's fire, dawg.
你们现在还嗑药么
Do you guys even really get high anymore?
我觉的现在嗑药都没啥意思了
I-I don't really think I get high anymore.
我就是有啥说啥
I think I just kind of act myself.
兄弟我有阵子没嗑了
I haven't been high in a while, man.
但我还是会嗑的
But I still do it.
我就是喜欢这种生活方式
I like the lifestyle.
我现在超嗨
I'm mad high.
嘿 跟Scott 说说
Yo, tell Scotty about
你是怎么被黏上的
how you're being catfished.
谁  你啊
- Who? - You!
兄弟 你怎么被黏上的
How you're being catfished, bro.
快说来听听
Tell him the truth.
你交女朋友了还是怎么了
You got a girlfriend? What's up?
没    是的
- No. -  Yeah.
太好了啊 是啊
- That's awesome. - Yes.
她叫Carla
- Her name is Carla.
我们电话讲着讲着  不是吧兄弟
- We talk on the phone.-  Nah, dude.
那女孩就和他陷入了爱河
Like, this girl, like, slid into his DMs, and, like,
不知道后面怎么了就约他出去还是啥的
I don't know, she, like, asked him out or whatever.
但是100% 是个陷阱 兄弟   她
- But hundred percent a trick, dude.-  She...
她是很野 但她不是你的   怎么说
- She's bad, but that's not yours.- Why?
她身材很火辣 兄弟
And she's, like, so hot, dude.
她就像游艇女郎
Yo, she, like,hangs out on yachts.
就像  嘿 胡说
- Like, yo.- Oh, come on.
没啦 没啦就像   老兄
- No, no, like, no.- Dude...
超不可思议的
Like, it's not real, like...
兄弟 他们就是嫉妒
Bro, they're just being jealous, bro.
他们就是嫉妒 因为你钓到
They're just jealous 'cause you're getting that...
哦 对了就是这个鲶鱼
Oh, yeah, that's a catfish.
喔 我去 盯上你的人也太正了吧
Oh, you getting catfished like a motherfucker!
我去  我说的是吧 兄弟
- Oh, my God! -  Right, dude?
兄弟  她怎么
- Bro... -  What does she...
我要把这图片发给我自己
Straight up, I'm-a send myself this one, honestly.
讲真 兄弟 她也太假了吧
Honestly, dude, she's fucking fake.
她觉得我很性感
She thinks I'm hot.
怎么会 你俩都没见过面
How? You guys never even seen each other.
你俩怎么没视频下
How come you guys don't FaceTime?
跟Scotty 说说你为啥没跟人视频
Tell Scotty why you don't FaceTime.
她手机摄像头坏了 但是她给我发了这些照片
Her phone camera's broken, but she sent me all these photos.
是啊  兄弟 这些是谷歌出来的图片好吧
-  Yeah.-  Bro, these are Google Images.
对啊 兄弟   我去 不一定啊
-  Exactly, dude. -  Shit, you don't know that.
可能人家妹子就爱 Igor 这款的呢
Maybe-maybe this girl is, uh, is into Igor.
他其实很可爱啊
Well, you know, he's-he's, you know, cute.
哈 你都不知道怎么和妹子聊天
Yo, like, you don't even know how to talk to girls.
你怎么和这个妹子聊天
What do you even talk to her about?
-Igor  -哦哦
- Igor.-  Mm-hmm.
去开门啊兄弟  你愣着干嘛
Go get that shit, bro. What are you doing?
他 真的是最烂的助手了
Yo, he is the worst assistant.
发生了很多事啊他
He's clearly going through a lot.
6片赞安诺多少钱来的
How much for, like, six Xanax?
6个
Six.
我们有几个 我们有几个
What do we have? What do we have?
谁需要6个赞安诺来着 我这里有1个 2 个
- Who needs six Xanax? - I got one, two...
我这里有 3个
I got three right here, I think.
1个 2个
One, two...
这个是么  是的
Is this a... Yeah.
-你最近过得怎么样了  -我还好啊
- How you doing? - I'm all right.
嘿 你是  Jimmy Bags 的兄弟对吗
Yo, you're Jimmy Bags' brother, right?
是的 亲
- Yes, bro.
转告你兄弟说他是个碧池
Tell your brother he's a bitch.
懂了吗  好 懂了
- You understand that?- Yeah. I do.
跟我说一遍   他是个碧池 他是个碧池
- Say it back to me.- He's a bitch. He's a bitch.
现在
And now, you know what?
我只有4个 但是你要付我6个的钱
I got four,but you're paying for six.
不 别这样 大哥 他他妈的是我兄弟来的
Nah, come on. That's my fucking brother, bro.
-你想干嘛  -不不不 小兄弟
- Like, what are you...
- Nah. Nah, dude.
我讨厌你兄弟
I hate your brother.
你看着就像迷你版的他
And now you look like a little version of him,
我现在就像打你
and I want to punch you in the face.
如果不想这样你就给我60块
So, instead of doing that, just give me 60.
我只有40块
I only got 40.
那就滚回家 爱干嘛干嘛去 别来了
Then go home, do chores, and dont come back.
-我才不理你  -不行啊
- I don't give a fuck. - I-I can't.
这钱是从我妈钱包里偷的 她钱包里只有40块啊
I stole it from my mom's purse, but she only had 40.
好吧 那这样吧 你把你鞋给我
Well, then, give me your shoes.
大哥不行啊
No, bro, I can't.
给我你的鞋子 就这么成交了
Just give me your shoes and we'll call it a day.
-嘿你鞋多大码的 -鞋码9
- Hey, what size are you? -  Like, a nine.
那适合你
Those'll fit you.
-Igor 那给你了  -嗯 我要了
- Igor, you can have those. - IGOR: I'll take 'em.
快看 Igor 得到了个礼物
Look at that, Igor got a gift.
他不是9码的  滚丫的
- He's not a fucking nine.- Fuck you!
别取笑我朋友
You don't make fun of my friend!
他TMD的都坐不了过山车的
He-he can't get on fucking roller coasters,
-他那么矮  -你丫的闭嘴   -喔
- he's that small. - Shut the fuck up! - Whoa!
-我们可以取笑他  -他怎么穿得上
- We make fun of him! - How is he gonna wear them?
你不可以取笑他 他是我们的朋友
- You don't make fun of him! - He's our friend.
他一直都能坐过山车
He rides roller coasters all the time.
我们可以取笑他 你不能
We make fun of him, not you.
他也就穿5号吧 大哥
He's, like, a size five,
bro, like...
嘿 闭嘴
Yo! Stop!
滚出我窗口
Get the fuck away from my window.
你们就是群小娘儿们
You guys are a bunch of fucking pussies.
老妈 他说他要穿这个工装裤去参加我的典礼
Mom, he's saying he's gonna wear these cargo shorts to the party.
哦 别
Oh, no.
啥 我都跟你说了去穿你爹的西服啊
What? I told you to wear Dad's suit.
我不想穿老爸的西服好吗
I don't want to wear Dad's old suit, okay?
-我有自己的穿衣风格 我 -滚离我远一点
- I have my own personal style, and I... - Get the fuck off me!
-别这么穿  -我不想穿西装好吗
- Don't do that! - I-I don't want to wear a suit, okay?
我感觉我要吐了
- I think, I think I'm gonna throw up.
我感觉我得了流感
I think I have the flu.
哦哦 好的  用你的鼻子呼吸
Oh, oh, okay. Just-just breathe through your nose.
等下啊
One second.
闭嘴 老妈 他看起来
Oh, shut up. Mom, he looks like
就像天桥底下卖可卡因的毒贩子
he fucking sells crack under a bridge.
我认识天桥下卖可卡因的贩子好吗
I know the guy who sells crack under the bridge, okay?
他看起来可精神了
And he looks awesome.
你就穿西装吧 拜托了 Scott
Just put on the suit, Scott, please.
不 这不公平
No! It's not fair!
她觉得自己是世上的公主
She thinks she's, like, princess of the world...
好了 就麻烦
Okay, well, then just please
稍稍尊重我下好吗
be respectful for two fucking seconds!
以为她高中毕业了
...because she graduated high school.
谁没高中毕业啊
Everybody graduates high school!
- 克莱尔：闭嘴  - 斯科特!
- CLAIRE: Shut up! - Scott!
妈 求你了
Mom, please...
你把西装穿上
Just put on the suit.
有点礼貌
Be respectful.
我一小时后回家
I'll be home in an hour.
我穿 行了吧
Fine!
克莱尔:谢谢
CLAIRE:Thank you.
你感觉怎么样
How are you feeling?
对不起
I'm sorry.
刚才想提醒您来着 可您忙着视频呢
I tried to warn you, but you were on the phone.
谢谢你让我用你的手机
Thanks for letting me use your phone.
我家也有问题
My family has problems, too.
克莱尔:我喜欢这房子
CLAIRE: I love this house.
斯科特：你要是有钱的话
SCOTT:If you have money,
干嘛还要住在史泰登岛呢
why would you ever live in Staten Island?
- 克莱尔:哦 耶  - 乔安:太棒了
- CLAIRE: Oh, God. Yeah.  - JOANNE: So good.
乔安母：我们为我们的女儿乔安
JOANNE'S MOTHER:We are so proud
感到非常骄傲
of our daughter Joanne...
还有克莱尔 这些年常常陪伴着我们家
and Claire, who's been at our house so much over the years
你就像我们的第二个女儿
you feel like our second daughter.
玛姬 谢谢你这些年让女儿陪伴我们
Thank you, Margie, for lending her to us all these years.
你们是非常努力的人 我们也非常为你们骄傲
You guys have worked so hard, and we are so, so proud of you.
老天 您别装了 死基佬
Jesus Christ, dial it back, you fucking fruits.
乔安父:乔安
JOANNE'S FATHER: Joanne,
你是我们最重要的女儿
you are a very special girl.
你让我们梦想成真
You made our dreams come true, too.
你是我们可爱的天使
You're my sweet angel.
她可不是
No, she's not.
能成为你的父母是我们的荣幸
It's such an honor to be your parents.
你教给我们的和我们教给你的东西一样多 还有克莱尔
You've taught us as much as we've taught you. Claire...
乔安母:你经历了太多
JOANNE'S MOTHER:You've been through so much,
但却非常争气
and you've done so well,
换做我们也不可能做得这么好
so much better than any of us could have handled it.
你父亲斯坦一定也为你骄傲
Your dad Stan would be so proud of you.
他此刻就在天堂看着你
He's looking down at you right now.
是的
Yes, he is.
他可没有
No, he's not.
敬乔安和克莱尔
A toast to Joanne and Claire.
乔安父:太骄傲了
JOANNE'S FATHER: So proud.
祝贺你们
Congratulations!
- 你好啊 托德  - 你好 斯科特
- What's up, Todd?  - What's up, Scott?
你什么时候也要上大学吧
You going to college, too, someday?
是啊 我是想去 我想学法律
I'd like to, yeah. I'd go study law.
是吗 那挺不错的
Oh, yeah? That's awesome, man.
听着真不错 你有大麻吗
That sounds really cool. Do you have any weed?
- 有啊  - 我能来点儿吗
- I do.  - Could I have some?
- 当然 我去拿点儿  - 好啊 谢啦 托德
- Definitely. I'll go grab it.  - Cool. Thanks, Todd.
小伙子还他妈不错 托德
Fucking home run, Todd.
一想起我妹妹可怜地
It makes me sad to think of my little sister
独自坐在家里等着儿子成才
sitting in that sad little house,
我就伤心
waiting for her son to be perfect.
我没有
I'm not.
那你可白瞎了这副好身材
Then you're wasting all of this.
活活浪费了
All of it's getting wasted.
- 你喝醉了  - 你真是浪费了
- You're a mess.  - You're wasted.
妈妈可要...她可要对你失望了
Mom would be so disappoin... Mom would be disappointed in you.
你才是那个经常喝醉的人
You're the one who's always wasted.
你浪费了 就像剩饭一样
You're wasting. It's like leaving food on the table.
得了吧
Come on.
- 我带你出去玩  - 与人交往太难了
- Let me take you out.  - It's so hard to meet people.
- 我是真心地  - 不 我是说 唉
- I'm totally open.  - No, it's... I mean, God...
你一点也不真诚
You're not open at all.
- 与人交往就是很难  - 你撒谎
- It's really hard to meet people.  - You're a liar.
自欺欺人 什么叫与人交往很难
You're not open. "Hard to meet people"?
- 我在急诊室工作 我看到的都是  - 你一晚上
- I'm in the E.R. All I see is, like...  - You meet...
- 你一晚上能见到上百人  - 中枪的人
- You meet a hundred people a night.  - People who were shot...
就是说啊 都中枪了
Yeah, they're shot.
他们 他们 呃 他们是罪犯
They're-they're, uh, they're criminals.
- 别总是自我束缚了  - 我见谁啊我
- Stop limiting yourself.  - Who am I gonna meet?
别自我束缚好吗
Stop limiting yourself.
- 但我在医院上班  - 是啊
- But I'm at the hospital.  - Yeah.
- 他们也不全是罪犯啊  - 你工作能遇见很多人
- They're not all criminals.  - You meet people at work.
- 这就是为什么  - 有些还是受害者呢
- That's what it's...  - Some of them are victims.
多尔
Doll...
我们可以给你一周安排两班
You know, we could put you on two shifts a week,
- 就 就只是试一试  - 我不需要工作
- just-just, just to try it.  - I don't need a job.
我跟文身店签了合同了
I, uh, I got a contact at a tattoo shop.
我 我准备去做学徒
I'm-I'm hoping for an apprenticeship, so...
那你肯定需要钱吧
Then you're gonna need some money.
可不 有些人走的时候还给80块小费呢
Yeah, some of these guys walk away with 80 bucks in tips.
斯科特 你堂兄在给你安排工作 你就考虑一下吧 好吗
Scott, your cousin's offering you a job. Consider it, okay?
要是你干的好 你还能当个侍应生
If you're good at it, you can become a waiter.
说起来你为什么要给我安排工作
Why are you offering me a job anyway?
因为我跟你父亲保证我会照顾你
Because I told your father I'd always look out for you.
怎么可能 他死于一场突发火灾
How?He died suddenly in a fire.
你问的是他的魂儿吗
Uh, did you ask his ghost?
别耍这种小聪明 斯科特
That's not witty, Scott.
我觉得你那黑色幽默一点也不好笑
Your dark sense of humor doesn't work for me.
我觉着好笑
I find it funny.
今天是你妹妹重要的日子 有点礼貌
It's your sister's big day. Be a gentleman.
好吧 移民局突击检查拘了我们几个人
Okay, we lost a few guys in an ICE raid.
操蛋 抱歉
Ah, shit. Sorry.
也许你可以半工半读
Maybe you should work and go to college.
- 读大学可太扯淡了  - 哦
- College is bullshit!  - Oh.
你知道谁读的哈佛大学吗 炸弹怪客
You know who went to Harvard? The Unabomber.
你知道谁读的天普大学吗 比尔 科斯比
You know who went to Temple? Bill Cosby.
你知道还有谁读的天普大学吗 泰德·邦迪
You know who else who went to Temple? Ted Bundy.
你知道还有谁读的霍夫斯特拉大学吗 伯尼·麦道夫
You know who went to Hofstra? Bernie Madoff.
你知道谁读的沃顿商学院吗 唐纳德·特朗普
You know who went to Wharton? Donald Trump.
大学就是个骗局
It's all a scam.
好吧 那我也不该上大学
Okay, well, maybe I shouldn't go, then.
哦不 你会度过人生中最好的时光的
Oh, no, you'll have the time of your life.
克莱尔:嗨 斯科特
CLAIRE:Hey, Scott.
坐吧
Sit down.
好
Okay.
我给你买了这个
I got you this.
这 这啥啊 这 这什么意思
So, what-what is, uh, what is, what is this?
就是画笔和一些颜料
It's paintbrushes and some paint.
我知道你喜欢美术 所以我就想着 在我不在的时候
Well, I know you're into art, so I thought you could
你可以用这些来开阔视野
expand your horizons while I'm gone.
你还专门要了礼物收据吗
You got a gift receipt for this?
- 你没事吧  - 没事 嗯
- You okay?  - Fine... Yeah.
怎么了 没事啊
Wh-What do you mean? Yeah, I'm...
我不在家你没事的吧
You gonna be okay without me here?
什么意思 你觉得你走了我就活不了了吗
What, you don't think I can survive here without you?
好吧 那你别老干混蛋事儿啊
Okay, just don't be a dick, okay?
对妈妈好点儿 听到没 别老气她
Like, be nice to Mom, okay? Don't give her a hard time.
- 让她歇会儿吧  - 我怎么没让她歇着了
- She deserves a break.  - I always give her a-a break.
你什么意思 我 谁能让我歇会儿
What are you... When's... When am I gonna get my break?
就
Like...
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
每个人就知道关心你
All anyone ever does is worry about you.
我的童年没人理就是因为你
I was ignored my entire childhood 'cause of you.
哦 是吗 我还真不记得我的童年多美好了
Oh, yeah, I forgot that my childhood was so dandy.
你别疯疯癫癫一辈子
Okay, you don't get to act crazy your whole life
就因为爸爸去世了 好吗
just 'cause Dad died, okay?
至少你还见过他
At least you got to know him.
告诉你 你没见过他才是幸运的
Well, you're lucky you didn't get to know him, okay?
因为这个你好歹像个正常人
'Cause that's why you're almost normal.
如果你见过他 你就会知道
If you got to know him, you would've known that he was,
他他妈是最酷的人
like, the fucking coolest guy ever,
然后你这辈子就不会再好了
and that would've ruined the rest of your life.
但你还能怎样呢
Okay, like, but what are you gonna do?
你准备去找工作还是离开家
Are you gonna get a job or are you gonna leave the house?
不知道
I don't know.
我 我想开家文身餐厅
I-I'm gonna open that tattoo restaurant.
不 是说认真的
No, like, for real.
我就是认真的啊
I am being real.
会很棒 前所未有的概念
It's a great...It's never been done before.
我查过 谷歌的
I looked it up. I googled it.
前所未有的概念 都不曾在梗里出现过
It's never been done, not even as a joke.
那是因为没人想去餐厅吃饭的同时
Because no one wants to go to a restaurant
还得看着别人文身
and watch people get tattooed while they eat.
- 太恶心了  - 这个主意最棒了
- It's gross.  - It's the best idea ever.
红宝石纹身日 欢迎所有人光临
Ruby Tattoosdays, where everyone's welcome.
- 炸鸡与文身  - 根本没有这行儿
- Chicken and tattoos.  - That's not a business!
知道吗 你必须振作起来
You know, you got to get your shit together.
时光飞逝
Time is passing by very quickly.
这就是为什么我一天到晚抽大麻 好吧
That's why I smoke weed all the time, okay?
它会让时间慢下来
It slows it all down.
听不懂人话
Fucking God.
我这是在担心你
See, I'm worried about you.
现在担心什么 你不是从来不关心的么
Well, why now? You never gave a shit.
你 这一秒之前 一直也没鸟过我
You, like, literally never cared until this second.
有什么动机吗
Like, wh-what, what gives?
你从没有罩过我一次
You never looked out for me once.
你是我哥哥
You're my older brother.
难道不是应该你罩着我吗
You're supposed to look out for me.
你 你只是因为要走了所以心中有愧吧
You're-you're just guilty 'cause you're leaving?
现在突然间 你就一下子开始担心我要死了
Now, all of a sudden, you're afraid I'm gonna die?
我终究会死 你走不走都一样
I was gonna die anyway, whether you stay or not.
- 你要自残吗  - 有可能
- Are you gonna hurt yourself?  - Probably.
是啊 我有可能会自残
Yeah, I'm probably gonna hurt myself.
还没想好怎么做 但会的
I don't know how, but yeah.
我就是最有可能这么做的人了
If anybody could do it, it's me.
这就是为什么我不想理你 因为我知道
This is why I don't talk to you, 'cause the one thing I know is
你不会听我的 所以
you're not gonna listen to my advice, so...
斯科特:是啊 我为什么要听
SCOTT: Yeah, well, why would I?
你根本就不在乎
Like, you don't even give a shit.
你 你还要走呢
You're-you're leaving.
你都不属于这个家了
You're not even part of the family.
我他妈才是这个家里唯一的正常人
I'm the only fucking normal person in this family.
天哪 你知道吗
Jesus. You know...
我不在你身边的每一秒我都在担心你
Every second I'm away from you, I'm worrying about you.
你就是这样让人担心
That's what you do to people.
你就该担心
You should be worried.
好了 别破坏我对大学的向往了
Okay, don't fucking ruin college for me, okay?
滚
Go!
好啊
Fine.
嘿 你真该把这讨喜的性格带到大学里去
Hey, you should bring that chipper personality to college.
男生都喜欢
Guys will love it.
你好
Hello.
好的 我先看看我的日程安排
Okay, let's see my to-do list.
我们已经把行李装到车上了
Yo, we're finished packing the car.
你想出来告别一下吗 还是
You want to come out and say goodbye or...?
哦 当然 马上就看完了
Oh, well, yeah, this is almost over.
我们马上就走了
No, like, we're leaving.
- 哦 她要走吗  - 要去大学啊 记得吗
- Oh. She's leaving?  - Like, to go to college, you know?
- 哦哦 抱歉  - 是啊 四年呢
- Oh, oh, my bad.  - Yeah, four years, so...
- 好吧  - 走吧
- Oh, all right. - Let's go.
别看了 赶紧走
Nope, like... Go. Come on.
别为我担心 好吗
Uh, don't worry about me, okay?
要到伤感的时刻了
This is really hard right now.
你看起来不太好
You don't seem fine.
我真为你骄傲
I'm so proud of you.
我爱你
I love you.
好了
Uh, okay.
你是我生命中的光
You're the light of my life.
克莱尔:哦
CLAIRE:Oh.
好啦
Okay.
帮忙装行李可真是谢谢你
Thanks for helping us pack the car.
斯科特:对不起
SCOTT:I'm sorry.
我不知道你们已经装好了
I didn't realize you guys were done already.
对妈妈好点儿
Be nice to Mom.
还有一定要回我短信
And please respond to my texts.
我会的 不用担心
I will. Don't worry about it.
我 呃 回头我会去找你的
And, um... I-I'll come visit you at some point.
好啊
Okay. All right.
嗯
Yeah.
- 我爱你  - 我也爱你
- I love you.  - I love you, too.
- 玛姬:展翅高飞吧孩子
- MARGIE: Fly.
斯科特:嘿
SCOTT:Hey.
嘿
Hey.
呃
Uh...
我想着我还是要看看那个权力的游戏
I was thinking of finally seeing that Game of Thrones.
我是不是应该沉溺进去
Should I binge it?
哦 那个剧 挺 挺暴力的
Oh, it's a, it's a pretty violent show.
你确定要看吗
You sure you could watch that?
我在急诊工作
I work in an emergency room.
哦对
Right, yeah.
那你看烧杀抢掠啥的应该没问题
So, you could probably handle a good pillage.
是啊
Yeah.
好 那我就准备看了
Okay, well, maybe I'll start watching it.
- 好的  - 你跟我一起吗
- Yeah.  - You watch it with me?
呃 其实我 差不多看完了 所以
Um, well, I actually just kind of finished it, so I-I don't...
剧情还在我脑中盘旋 所以我可能
It's really fresh in my mind, so I-I would probably...
- 好吧  - 我可以看一部分
- Okay.  - I can watch some of them.
我觉得我可能不能全看一遍了 但
Uh, I don't think I can watch all of them again, but...
- 嗯  - 那就待会儿见了
- Well...  - I'll see you later, then.
好吧
All right.
你还好吗
Uh, are you okay?
还是
Or...
怎么了
Oh. Yeah?
过来
Come on.
没 没
Uh, it's, it-it's...
没事的
It's okay. It's...
我在这儿 我在
I-I'm here. Uh, I'm here.
别 别难过了
Don't-don't worry about it.
你知道 她
She's, you know...
她离咱们只有45分钟车程的
Well, she's only, like, 45 minutes away,
她肯定 过个五分钟就会打来电话的
and she'll-she'll probably call in, like, five minutes.
但是
But, hey.
你不是还有我呢吗 对吧
You still got me, right?
对
Yeah.
哦 草
Oh, shit.
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey!
奥斯卡:看 你应该这样拿
OSCAR: See, you got to hold it like this.
塔拉:我看看 噢
TARA:Let's see. Oh.
- 哦耶  - 哦
- Oh, yeah!  - Oh!
嘿 嘿 等下 兄弟们
Hey, hey, wait. Hey, hey, guys.
是这样
Look, look.
你们不能在这儿呆着
You can't be here, man.
- 你们得离开  - 凯尔西:为什么
- Y-You got to go.  - KELSEY: Why?
保安:这是私人土地 这就是为什么
GUARD: It's private property, that's why.
这是个废弃的孤儿院 我们怎么不能呆了
It's an abandoned orphanage. Why can't we be here?
里奇:谁鸟你啊 兄弟
RICHIE:Who gives a shit, man?
你在这儿干嘛
What are you doing here?
你在守着孤儿们的鬼魂儿吗
You fucking protecting the ghosts of dead orphans?
听着 胖坎耶 闭上你的臭嘴
Look, fat Kanye, shut your damn mouth.
我五分钟候再他妈过来
I'll be back in five minutes for you assholes.
如果你们还在这儿 我就报警 没商量
If you're still here, I'm calling the cops, period.
你最好报警 哥们儿 因为你是个假警察
You better get the cops, man, 'cause you're a fake cop.
- 你需要真警察  - 保安:小王八羔子
- You need the real ones.  - GUARD: Motherfuckers.
- 操你们娘的  - 伊果:我有点后悔
- Fuck all of y'all.  - IGOR: I feel bad.
我们 是 是不是太过分了
We-we were a little too mean.
- 斯科特:是啊  - 他挺好的
- SCOTT: Yeah.  - He's nice.
是啊 他是个好人
Yeah, he's a really good guy.
那种人 他才是史泰登岛真正的问题
See, that guy... that is what is wrong with Staten Island.
别的镇上的人都不来我们这儿
We don't get any cool people from any of the other boroughs.
没人来
No one comes here.
我们只能跟这儿的土著混蛋们过一辈子了
We're stuck with the fucking pricks that live here.
你在骂我们
You're talking about us.
还当着我们的面
Right in front of us.
凯尔西:是啊 算是吧
KELSEY:Yeah, kinda.
我是想说 没人愿意来
I mean, no one comes here.
没有任何人员流动 那家伙 都有两百岁了吧
There's no flow of people. That guy's, like, 200.
咱们小时候就认识他
We've known him since we were six.
为什么咱们这儿不能像布鲁克林一样酷
Why can't we be cool like Brooklyn?
没有道理我们不能像布鲁克林一样酷啊
There's no reason we shouldn't be cool like Brooklyn.
我们这儿景色美 离城市又近
We got amazing views. It's close to the city.
物价便宜 居民和蔼 真是没道理
It's cheap. Nice people. It makes no sense.
我们算是新泽西瞧不起的唯一的地方了
We're, like, the only place that New Jersey looks down on.
垃圾场得你从太空都能看见
You could see the garbage dump from space.
这地方也就这样了
This place is never gonna change.
不会的 肉类加工厂区不就改变了
No, it happened to the Meatpacking District,
还有那个村儿
the Village.
布鲁克林原来也是个操蛋的地方
Brooklyn used to be a fucking shithole.
咱们就是下一个了
We are next.
我要参加公务员考试
I'm gonna take my civil service test.
我要在城里工作 在城市规划部门
I'm gonna work in the city, in city planning.
你们看着吧 这地方即将成为下一个威廉斯堡
You watch, this place is gonna be like fucking Williamsburg
- 十年内建成  - 里奇:别 别介 我们可不想要
- in ten years.  - RICHIE: No, all right? No. Nobody wants that.
为什么你想在市里干城市规划的工作
Why do you want to work in the city and do city planning?
听着就无聊
That sounds so boring.
我觉得布鲁克林更好
I feel like Brooklyn is better.
我曾经跟一个住布鲁克林的人约过会
I dated a guy that lived in Brooklyn.
他是个调酒师
He was a mixologist.
他用牛奶做冰块
He made ice cubes out of milk.
- 他真是太有品味了  - 奥斯卡:闭嘴
- He was so classy.  - OSCAR: Shut up!
我爱史泰登岛
I love Staten Island.
这里好的没话说
It's amazing.
很快人们就将看到这一点 相信我
And people are gonna see it soon, trust me.
斯科特:你要是这么爱这里
SCOTT:Well, if you love it so much,
干嘛不让我把它文在你身上
why don't you let me tattoo it on you?
不 我可不会再让你给我文身了
No, I'm not gonna let you tattoo me again.
好吧
Fine.
那我也需要一个可以文的人
Well, I need somebody to tattoo.
我 我都没人可文了
I'm, I-I'm running out of...
里奇 你呢 兄弟
Come on, Rich. What about you, man?
- 别看我 哥们  - 为啥
- Don't even look at me, dude.  - Why?
你文的东西太丑了
Your work is mad inconsistent.
奥巴马文的不对
Obama ain't right.
斯科特:我只是把眼睛文错了 好吧
SCOTT:I got the eyes wrong, okay?
里奇:哪儿哪儿都不对
RICHIE:He's not right.
好嘛 这个文身伤到我了
All right, man, this has hurt me, all right?
我再也没有黑人朋友了
I don't have any black friends anymore.
我再也不能去理发店了
I can't go to a barber shop no more.
你把奥巴马文错了 没有比这严重的问题了
You got Obama wrong. Ain't nothing worse than that.
你呢 伊果 你要文条龙还是啥吗
What about you, Igor? You want a dragon or something?
哦 我可真喜欢你的文身
Oh, I love your tattoos.
我弟弟
My brother?
太像了
It's a spitting image.
- 斯科特:是啊 是我的代表作之一  - 是我的最爱
- SCOTT: Yeah. It's one of the best. - It's my favorite.
不不不 这是我的最爱
No, no, no, no. This is my favorite.
哦 这个真的精彩
Oh, you killed that.
- 可不 眼睛上很下功夫了  - 只是
- Yeah, I really worked hard on the eyes.  - Just...
真是可爱 我喜欢那个菊花
He's so cute. I love his butthole.
它时刻提醒我我有个肚脐眼
It reminds me that I have a belly button.
- 我还是算了  - 那什么 我得走了
- So, I'm good.  - Yeah, I got to go.
看你上赶着送文身真是悲哀
Watching you beg to give tattoos is too sad.
吓死我了
And that's freaking me out.
斯科特:快完事儿了
SCOTT: We're almost done.
马上
Almost.
好了
All right.
- 大功告成  - 看起来很不错啊
- You're all done.  - That looks really good.
是啊 我是说
Yeah, I mean, I wish
我希望你能让我文点儿更酷的 但也可以了
you'd let me do something cooler, but yeah.
卧槽 好疼 太疼了吧
Oh, fuck no. That hurts so bad.
- 又一个傻帽文身  - 斯科特:是啊 但 但我喜欢那种疼痛感
- Another dumb tattoo.  - SCOTT: Yeah, but I-I like the pain.
疼痛才是文身的真谛
The-the pain is the whole point of getting tattoos.
难道你不喜欢那种 文身的时候
Don't you just love when you're getting tattooed,
深入骨髓的痛 让你的神经颤动
and it hits the bone and pinches a nerve,
那就像
and you're like...
我对疼痛不感兴趣
I'm not a fan of the pain.
你不应该让他文你的 好吧
You shouldn't let him do it to you, all right?
他发挥不稳定
He's inconsistent.
奥斯卡:我觉得那个文身很傻
OSCAR:I think that tattoo's dumb.
那你们看见图案的时候就该告诉我
Y'all should've told me when you saw the design.
上面说:取关我
It says, "Unfollow me."
本来你粉丝也不多啊
You don't even have that many followers.
卡拉关注我了
Carla follows me.
- 兄弟 她不是真人  - 奥斯卡:卡拉不是真人
- Bro, she's imaginary.  - OSCAR: Carla not real.
卡了不是真人 哥们儿
Carla's not real, dude.
里奇:要我们说多少遍啊
RICHIE: How many times do we have to say this?
斯科特:她不是真人
SCOTT: She's not real.
我讨厌这虫子
I hate bugs, dawg.
我是土匪
I'm a gangster!
斯科特:别 那是只蜜蜂 老兄
SCOTT:No, that's a bee, bro!
奥斯卡:那边有个孩子
OSCAR:There's a kid down there.
- 哟 小孩儿  - 哟
- Yo, kid! - Oh, yo.
- 哟 小孩儿 你好啊  - 哦草 那儿有个孩子
- Yo, kid, what's up?  - Oh, shit, there is a kid.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
你在海滩溜达吗 过来 上这儿来
You hanging out on the beach? Come here, come here.
别害羞 我们不会害你
Don't-don't be shy. No stranger danger here.
我不碰你
I'm not gonna touch you.
- 你好吗 小老弟  - 你在干什么
- What's up, pal?  - What are you doing?
我在找我朋友
I'm looking for my friend.
"Looking for my friend."
你想跟我们当朋友吗
You want to be friends with us?
我们是好人
We're the good guys, right?
- 你可以跟我们一起玩儿 小老弟  - 来吧
- You can hang out with us, pal.  - Come on.
来跟我碰拳 把你的拳头放在这儿
Let me get some of that. Put it right there.
- (fists bump)
- (imitates explosion)
你入伙了
You gang.
是我们的人
Part of the gang.
我们的人
Gang.
那是什么
What's that?
这是纹身枪
Uh, it's a tattoo gun.
我在给哥们纹身
I was giving the homeys tattoos.
我也想纹身
I want a tattoo.
- 小老弟挺狠的啊   - 真的吗
- You're a tough guy? - Really?
- 行啊小伙子 你确定要纹身吗   - 我确定
- Sure, young guy. You want a tattoo? - Yeah.
哥们 这孩子想要纹身 小老弟行啊
Dude, kid wants a tattoo. That's my guy right there.
老哥 你不能给他纹身
Bro, you-you can't give him a tattoo.
- 他还是个孩子   - 来吧来吧
- He's a little kid. - Yeah, there we go.
- 想纹身吗   - 我总得找个人练练手
- You want a tattoo? - Bro, I got to practice on something.
- 没错   - 他看上去不小了
- Yeah. - He seems old enough.
- 是真汉子吗   - 当然
- You a tough guy? - Yeah.
你是纯爷们
You a badass.
来 老弟 给咱们秀一下肌肉
Come on, show those muscles, kid.
- 两只手 两只手   - 好样的
- Come on. Both arms, both arms. - Yeah, there you go.
- 举起来   - 肌肉猛男秀仅对内部开放
- Put 'em up. - You got tickets to the gun show?
- 秀出来秀出来   - 就是这样   - 好样的
- There it is. There it is - All right. - There we go.
- 你叫什么名字   - 哈罗德
- What's your name? - Harold.
那我叫你哈利
I'm-a call you Harry.
不行 叫我哈罗德
Don't. It's Harold.
好吧
Okay.
- 好小子   - 我喜欢他
- Hell yeah. - I like this kid.
我的生命里就缺一个他
I need him in my life.
是个人才
He has structure.
兄弟们 我不觉得这是个好主意
Guys, I don't think that's a good idea.
拜托 我们不听你的
I mean... we don't listen to anything you say.
- 没错   - 是啊 你说你到底为什么老提意见呢
- Yeah. - Yeah, I mean, why do you even try to give us advice?
那么 你想要什么样的纹身
So, what do you want a tattoo of?
惩罚者
The Punisher.
- 惩罚者   - 行吧
- The Punisher? - Okay.
- 狠角色啊 哥们   - 好吧
- That's tough, man. - All right.
他可以选任何图案 但他选了惩罚者
He could've said anything. He said The Punisher.
没问题 我可以的 是这个吗
Oh, yeah, I could do that. Is that it?
没错 是他
Yeah, that's him.
- 你确定吗   - 确定
- Are you sure? - Yes.
能否请你给我你的法定许可
Do I have your legal permission to do this?
- 允许   - 对我来说就够了
- Yes. - That's good enough for me.
- 你们觉得呢   - 可以成为呈堂证供
- How about you guys? - Holds up in court.
你们都听到了 好嘞
You guys heard it. All right.
唷 他不能给你许可 他才十岁
Yo, he can't get consent. He's ten.
那么 别乱动好吗 这纹上了可就洗不掉了
Now, hold still, okay? 'Cause it is permanent.
伙计们 停下 快停下
Yo, guys. Stop. Stop, stop, stop.
- 表情严肃一点   - 别担心 哥们
- Put your game face on. - Don't worry, dude.
这玩意也不过就是会跟你一辈子
This will just be on you for the rest of your life.
开始了
There you go.
- 看看这个坚强的小伙   - 好样的
- Look at you, tough guy. - There you go.
我不想纹了
I don't want to do it!
- 我不纹了   - 可是我得把这纹完了
- I don't wanna! - Well, I got to finish it.
- 现在只有一条线   - 冷静点 哥们
- Now there's just a line. - Calm down, man.
- 这会让你看上去很傻 坐回来 放轻松   - 冷静点
- You're gonna look stupid. Sit back down. Relax. - Calm down.
- 坐下 继续   - 放松
- Sit down. Do it. - Relax.
快跑 快跑孩子
Run! Run, kid!
跑快点 小屁孩 快跑
Run, little man! Run!
跑
Run!
该死
Goddamn it.
我他妈的还信了他了
I fucking believed in that kid, man.
刚开始看着挺坚强 下一秒就怂了
He seemed so tough at first, uh, but then immediately wasn't.
所以我才不跟千禧一代玩啊 哥们
That's why I don't fuck with millennials, dude.
我再说一遍 我们也是千禧一代
Again, we are the millennials.
他老这么说 但我都不知道他在说什么
He keeps saying that, but I don't know what that means.
我后悔跟你们交朋友了
I regret my friendship with you guys.
你好 我叫雷蒙德·毕夏普
Yeah, hello. My name's Raymond Bishop.
这个是我儿子 哈罗德 跟人家问好 哈罗德
This is my son, Harold. Say hello, Harold.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这是怎么了
What's going on?
是这样 你儿子好像在树林那边
Well, it seems your son was down in the woods
给别人免费纹身 而我儿子上了他的当
giving out free tattoos, and my son was one of his victims.
什么 我 我不太明白
What? Well, I-I don't understand.
你怎么知道是我儿子 你怎么找到这里的
How do you know it was my son? How'd you get this address?
我有我的办法 相信我 我有门路
I have my ways. Believe me, I have my ways.
你是警察吗
Are you a cop?
不 我是个消防员 行了吗 我玩命工作
No, I'm a fireman, okay? I work for a living.
看看这个 你能相信吗
Look at this. Do you believe this?
看这里 你看到这条线了吗
You see that there? See that line?
我不知道这是得烧掉还是怎么样
I don't know if you burn these off or what,
但这个必须得给我弄掉
but we're taking care of this
而且你得承担所有费用 你明白吗
and you're paying for it, you understand me?
- 我都不知道这是什么   - 斯考特
- I don't know what this is. - Scott! Oh.
我 我真的很抱歉
I am... I'm so sorry.
我 我
I-I-I...
我工作的医院有一台激光美容仪
There's an aesthetic laser at the hospital where I work,
可以把这个去干净了
and it can completely remove it.
呃 我能给你打折
Uh, I get a discount.
我 这钱我来付
I'm-I'm gonna pay for the whole thing.
我有点语无伦次了 我感到抱歉
I don't know what I'm saying. I'm... I feel terrible.
你应该抱歉
You should feel terrible!
看看这个
Look at that!
- 怎么了 哦妈的   - 啊 终于来了
- What's up? Oh, fuck. - Ah, there he is.
- 你给我滚过来   - 嘿 他跟我说他18岁了
- You get your ass out here! - Hey, he said he was 18.
他看上去像4岁 你个傻逼 不好意思
He looks like he's four, you fucking moron! Sorry.
- 他同意了   - 他骗人
- He consented! - He's lying.
- 哈罗德 拜托   -他当然是在骗人
- Harold, come on! - Course he's lying!
你同意没有法律效力 他才9岁
You can't have consent! He's nine years old!
爸爸 咱们走吧 你这样我很尴尬
Dad, let's go. You're embarrassing me.
我们不走 好吗
We're not going anywhere, okay?
他还是个小孩
He's just a little kid!
你他妈的是哪根筋搭错了
What the fuck is wrong with you?!
呃 他在林子里乱窜
Uh, he was roaming around in the woods.
说想要个纹身 当时你在哪呢
He wanted a tattoo. W-Where were you?
我他妈的在工作
I was at fucking work!
- 去你的吧   - 你给我出来
- Fuck you! - Come out here!
我要是你 我现在就乖乖闭嘴
If I was you, I'd shut your fucking mouth,
要不然我现在就报警
because I can call the cops right now
你马上就得进局子
and have your ass thrown in jail.
- 我犯了什么法   - 你给孩子捅针眼了
- For what? - For sticking needles in a kid's arm,
你个瘾君子
you fucking dope!
他是你带大的吗 你教他什么了到底
Did you even raise him? Did you even raise him?
是这样 没必要报警
You know, there's no reason to call the cops.
这事我能处理 他我也能处理
I can handle this and I can also handle disciplining him.
切 明显你处理不了 要不然你儿子也不会年过中年
Well, clearly you can't or you wouldn't have a middle-aged son
还住在你家 到处给未成年人瞎纹身
still living at home, tattooing minors against their will!
是我让他纹的
I asked him to do it.
- 不是他的错   - 听见了吗 这才是个汉子
- It's not his fault. - That's right. That's my man.
去 车里待着 哈罗德 去
Go wait in the car. Harold, go on.
以后不许对我这么大声
And don't raise your voice at me, either.
回见了 哈罗德
Later, Harold.
谁要跟你再见 别忘了看路
Don't say goodbye to my kid. Look both ways.
- 两边都要看   - 回你房间
- Look both ways! - Go to your room.
- 我看了   - 怎么说话呢
- I am! - Watch your mouth.
顺便告诉你 我没有人到中年
For your information, I am not a middle-aged man.
我才24岁 现在我要回房间了
I'm a 24-year-old man, and I'm going to my room
因为我他妈的想回去了
'cause I fucking want to.
你在这房子带大的这玩意是人吗 哈
What kind of fucking animal are you raising in this house, huh?
发票我肯定会拿来
I'm bringing you the bill.
我才不管花了多少钱
I don't care what it costs, all right?
- 这他妈的算什么事啊   - 好的
- I mean, what the fuck is going on around here? - All right.
给我一天的时间 我给你预约激光
Just give me a day to arrange the laser.
行 另外
All right. You know, you know something?
他爸爸在吗 爸爸在哪里
I-Is his father home? Where's his dad?
我 我也不想对着你大喊大叫
I-I don't, I don't want to fucking yell at you.
他爸爸不在了
He's deceased.
哦
Oh.
呃 呃
Well, uh...
我 呃 很抱歉
I'm, uh, sorry for your loss.
我肯定如果他爸爸还在
I'm sure if he was still around,
他肯定也会同意的
he would agree with the fact that,
就是 这钱还是应该你们来付
you know, you should still pay for it.
像漫画里面一样大的山羊胡
Comically huge mustache.
他是不是长这样
Is this what he looked like?
他就长这样
That's exactly what he looked like.
- 你看上去很害怕   - 是的
- You're scared of me. - Yeah.
唷 他 他 这没什么好笑的
Yo, he-he… And that's not funny.
他就这么冲进来 开始大喊大叫
He burst into the door, started screaming,
气得胡子乱飞乱跳
and his mustache was flapping all over the place.
- 乱飞乱跳   - 他看上去像强手棋的那个人
- Flapping. - He looked the Monopoly Man.
非常吓人
It was terrifying.
“注意看路
"Look both ways!
两边都得看”
Look both ways!"
- 简直神经   - 但我还是得说
- Fucking maniac. - But I will say,
在树林子里给小孩纹身可不算什么好主意
probably not a good idea to tattoo children in the woods.
- 那可不   - 你有可能会惹上麻烦的
- Yeah, probably. - You know, you could get in trouble.
- 是啊 有可能   - 你为什么要这样
- Yeah, you could. - Why did you do that?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我还以为不会有事的
I thought I would get away with it.
而且 我以为他 至少得15了吧
Plus, I thought he was, like, at least 15, you know?
- 哦真的吗   - 我 我第一个纹身是我
- Oh, really? - I got... Yeah, I got my first tattoo...
- 他到底多大了   - 9岁
- How old was he? - Nine.
你以为他15了
You thought he was 15?
- 是的 我简直   - 你是不是抽太多了
- Yeah, I'm fucking… - Maybe you've been smoking too much.
我可能就是蠢
I think I'm just stupid.
你得看看我妈最近
No, you should see my mom, though.
- 自从我妹妹走了以后就很奇怪   - 是吗
- It's so weird since my sister left. - Yeah.
她总是在哭 而且
She's just crying all the time and, like,
她总是想跟我聊天 跟我待着
she's trying to talk to me and hang out with me.
有一天 她让我陪她去逛商场
The other day, she asked me to go to Nordstrom Rack.
我差点就自刎了
I almost slit my throat.
那你去了吗
Did you go?
没有 我假装睡着了
No. I pretended to be asleep.
拜托 她 她可能就是想有个人陪陪她
Oh, come on, she… Maybe she needs company.
你妹妹走了以后她很孤单
She's lonely without your sister.
没错 她 她肯定会寂寞的
Yeah, she's-she's, she's gonna be lonely.
你是没看见她在我妹妹欢送派对上的样子
I mean, you should've seen her at my sister's send-off party.
就 就很奇怪
It was, it was really weird.
你们给你妹妹办欢送会了
There was a party?
是啊
Yeah.
为什么没邀请我
Why wasn't I invited?
邀请你去高中毕业派对
To a high school graduation party?
那 都有谁去了
Well, who was there?
就 就是
It was, you know, it was just
家人 之类的
family and... shit.
怎么 你不想让我和你家人在一块吗
What, you don't want me to be around your family?
从我十岁开始就认识他们了
I've known them since I was ten.
嗯 就是
Well, yeah, I just...
我以为你不会感兴趣的
I didn't think it was something you would want to go to.
我错了
I'm-I'm sorry.
拜托 这也太扯淡了
Come on, that's fucked up.
怎么了 这怎么扯淡了
Why? Why is that fucked up?
因为我们 你懂的 我们不一般
Because we're, you know, doing something here.
我们 我们什么不一般了
We're... Are-are we doing something here?
我也不知道 我以为我们不一般
I don't know, we're starting a thing.
就是 咱俩睡也睡了 玩也玩了
I mean, we're having sex and we're hanging out a lot.
- 就我以为   - 我以为咱俩就是
- I mean, it's… - I thought it was just, like,
就是 没这么认真的关系
more, you know, casual than that.
你懂吗
You know?
那你是说 你生命中的重要时刻不希望我陪着你吗
Well, you don't want me to go to any, like, life events?
生命 生命中的重要时刻是什么
Life... What's a life event?
什么 我都不知道那什么意思
What does that what does that even mean?
算了 随便吧
You know what? It's fine.
- 怎么了   - 没事
- What? - No, it's fine.
你回来
Come back.
我错 等等
I'm sor... Wait.
等
Wai...
- 你知道吗 你说的没错   - 什么
- You know what? You're right. - What?
你这话什么意思 我从来都是错的
What are you talking about? I'm never right.
不 这次你没错 我们就这样吧
No, you're right. We shouldn't do this anymore.
我不想咱俩再这么继续下去了
I don't want to fucking do this anymore.
你说什么呢 我不明白
What are you talking about? I don't understand.
这事就不对 是个小失误
It was all a mistake. It was a mistake.
但没事 咱俩现在达成共识了
But it's fine. We're on the same page.
咱们的关系跟以前一样
We'll go back to what it was before.
我会像对奥斯卡和里奇那样对你
I'll treat you like I do Oscar and Richie.
我不是这个意思
I-It's not even that.
就是 我还不知道我到底想要什么
It's just, like, I-I don't know what I want yet.
我还在试着理清头绪
Like, I'm trying to figure my shit out.
你说得对 你应该这样 好好整理整理
And you should. Please do. Figure your shit out.
但以后我不会跟你上床了 好吗
But we're not gonna have sex anymore, okay?
我得走了
I got to go.
我应该请你跟我一起去的
I should've invited you to the party!
我也不知道那是我人生的重要时刻
I didn't know it was a life event!
我已经跟医院说好了 到时候直接付钱
I-I already arranged to, uh, pay directly at the hospital.
但如果你想让我付你支票 你等我两分钟 好吗
But if you want a check, just give me two minutes, okay?
不不不 我 我想付这个钱
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. I'm-I'm... I-I want to pay.
我来付 这钱我来付
I'm gonna pay for it. I'm gonna pay for it.
不不不 我会付的
No, no, no. I'm gonna pay for it.
而且我也 我会跟斯考特好好谈谈
And I'm, and I'm also gonna talk to Scott
这事太过分了 简直疯了
because that was totally out of line, totally nuts.
对 我明白
Yeah, I-I understand that.
但 听着 我就是想跟你道个歉
But, uh, look, I just wanted to apologize, okay?
我 上次我有点失控了
I-I got a little out of control before, uh...
我 我让愤怒冲昏了头脑
You know, I just, I let my anger get the best of me.
破了当初下的决心
Broke my stupid resolution.
天啊 还不是因为这样我的婚姻才破裂了
God knows it's what messed up my marriage,
我 我真的很想跟你道歉 可以吗
and I-I just really wanted to apologize, okay?
我 我当时很烦躁
I mean, I was upset,
但我不应该那样表达自己
but I-I shouldn't have conveyed it that way.
你不用道歉
There's no need to apologize.
是我的孩子先胡来的 这样不好
My kid's being a fucking lunatic. It's not cool.
我 我也反应过激了 他没什么错
Oh, I... I overreacted. He's fine.
不 这还只是冰山一角
No, it's the tip of the iceberg.
害 孩子嘛 好多都这样
Ah, you know, lot of kids do stuff like this.
嗯 孩子才不这样呢
Mm, kids don't do stuff like this.
他就差没在树林子里
He did the second-worst thing
那啥了你儿子了
you could do to a kid in the woods.
不管怎么样吧 我之前不应该那样对你
Well, either way, I shouldn't have behaved the way I behaved.
我真心向你道歉
So, I'm truly sorry.
我接受你的道歉 这很好
Apology accepted. It's nice.
这附近的人可不都这样
Don't get many of those around here.
- 谢谢   - 哦 这样可能
- Thanks. - Oh, hey, this might seem
有点突然 但是
a little crazy, but, uh...
我能请你喝杯咖啡吗
can I take you out for a cup of coffee?
斯考特给我纹了这个
So, Scott did this.
哦 这是个可卡犬吗
Oh. Is that a cocker spaniel?
不不 这是我女儿
No. No, that's my daughter.
我女儿克莱尔
That's Claire.
哦 没错 我看
Oh, yeah, yeah. I can...
- 我以为   - 没事
- Yeah, I just thought… - No, it's okay.
- 我以为那是耳朵   - 没事
- I thought those were ears. - Um, it's okay.
- 那是她的头发   - 是的 我明白了
- That's her hair. Okay, yep. - I know. I hear that.
斯考特16岁的时候有了他第一个纹身
Scott got his first tattoo when he was 16.
- 哦 这样   - 他纹了个科米蛙
- Oh, okay. - It was of Kermit the Frog.
- 还挺可爱的   - 是啊 是啊
- That's kind of cute. - Yeah, yeah.
抽大麻的科米蛙 嗯
Kermit smoking a joint, so...
抽大麻的科米蛙
Kermit smoking a joint?
天 我怎么不记得芝麻街里
Geez, I don't remember that episode
有这么一集 哈
on Sesame Street, huh?
还挺好笑的 他是个幽默的孩子吧
That's kind of funny. He's a funny kid, then, huh?
- 他特别好笑   - 是吗
- Oh, he's so funny. - Yeah?
- 他真的很好笑   - 你觉得他会事业有成吗
- He's so funny. - You think he's gonna stick it out?
嗯 我也不知道
Uh, well, that I don't know.
我 我曾把他送去艺术学校 但他退学了
I mean, I sent him to art school, but he quit.
他 他没法集中 因为
He-he couldn't really focus 'cause...
他有注意力缺失症 所以他
He also has ADD, so he...
反正 他是个有注意力缺失症的纹身艺术家
Anyway, he's a tattoo artist with ADD.
嘿 你知道吗
Well, you know what?
我们消防局里的所有人
All the guys down at the firehouse,
他们都有纹身之类的
they all have tattoos and stuff, you know.
我自己是没有纹过 但是
Personally, I never got one, though, you know.
你知道 我也不是反对这个事
You know, not that I have anything against them.
我就是 我总觉得我太怂了
I just, I just always felt I was too pasty.
- 消防局 哈   - 是的
- So, the firehouse, huh? - Yeah.
那个消防局
The old firehouse.
- 嗯 就是那个消防局   - 是啊
- Mm-hmm, the old firehouse. - Yeah.
你负责爬梯子还是负责消防车
So, you're a ladder or engine?
爬梯子
Ladder.
我猜也是
Knew it.
你们家有谁是消防员吗
You got firefighters in your family?
是的 我先生
Yeah, my husband.
- 哦 天 很抱歉   - 没事
- Oh, geez. Sorry. - Yeah.
我忘了
Forgot.
嘿 不知道这样是不是唐突了 但是你不介意的话
Hey, uh, I hope this isn't too forward, but do you mind
我能问问你先生发生了什么事吗
if-if I ask what happened to your husband?
哦 有个酒店着火了
Oh, it was a hotel fire.
屋顶塌陷
The roof collapsed.
他进去想救人
He went in to save somebody.
他们告诉他这样太危险了 但是你知道 他就是那种人
They told him it wasn't safe, but, you know, he was like that.
- 等等 斯坦·卡尔林是你丈夫吗   - 没错
- Wait, Stan Carlin was your husband? -  Mm-hmm.
- 派拉蒙酒店大火   - 是的
- Paramount Hotel fire? - Yeah, yeah.
你认识他吗
Did you know him?
- 你 你听说过   - 没没没有
- You, you... Or you heard… - No, no, no, I...
你见过他还是
Hung out with him or...?
不 我只是听说过他
No, I j… I just heard about him.
他真的很勇敢
He was a real brave guy.
- 是啊   - 他其实
- Yeah. - He was kind of a,
其实是个传奇人物 老实跟你说
kind of a legend, to be honest with you.
是 是吧
Yeah. Yeah.
事情发生的时候 斯考特那时候才7岁 所以
And Scott was only seven when it happened, so...
- 哦 那还挺难的   - 导致了很多后果
- Oh, that's tough. - A lot of consequences.
- 是啊 这情况挺艰难的   - 是啊
- Yeah, that's a tough situation, but… - Yeah.
但我还是得说 你做得很棒 你知道吗
But I-I got to tell you, you did a great job, you know?
你看 我是说
See, I mean, I...
我知道我们之前有点小小的冲突
I know we had a little bit of a difference there,
但是 我觉得 他是个好孩子
but, I mean, he's a good kid.
而且我得说 如果他所能想到的最坏的事
And I got to tell you, if-if the worst he's doing is-is,
是给人画几个不正规的纹身
you know, a couple unlawful tattoos,
- 你做得真的很棒了   - 是啊
- you-you did a hell of a job. - Yeah.
但 我却不觉得这是他会做的最坏的情况
Yeah, I don't think that's the worst he's doing, though.
- 是啊   - 害 我也不知道了
- Yeah. - Well, I don't know.
但是 小孩嘛 就这样的 不是吗
You know, uh, that's how kids are, you know?
每个人在不同时期总会经历这样一段
Everybody gets it at a different time.
不管怎样 你 呃
Anyways, what are you, uh...
咱们坐在这里 全听我说话了
I-I'm just sitting here, doing all the talking here.
你呢 你是做什么的
What do you, what do you do?
我是个护士
I'm a nurse.
在学校里的护士
I'm a school nurse.
也在急诊室当护士
I'm also an ER nurse.
你在急诊室工作吗
You work in the ER?
天啊 玛姬 我们之前可能见过
Jesus Christ, Margie, we probably met each other.
有可能
Could be.
那 你工作如何
So, how you doing?
我
I'm...
非常累
very tired.
真的吗 你看上去精神不错
Really? Well, you don't look tired.
真的我说真的 你看上去很漂亮
No, seriously, you look great.
- 真的吗   -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
我就是 你 你是在跟我调情吗
I just don't, like... I mean, are you flirting with me or...?
- 对啊   - 真的吗
- Yeah. - Yeah?
真的 我很努力了 看上去不像吗
Yeah, a lot. This is, this is what it looks like.
还挺微妙的 我都不
It is really subtle. I couldn't...
我都看不出来是不是
I can't tell what's going on.
这就是了 我的确做得很微妙
This is how it looks. I'm very subtle.
行吧
All right.
- 我比较笨 你比较巧妙   - 对啊
- I'm rusty. You're subtle. - Okay.
- 是 是啊   - 很高兴认识你
- Yeah, yeah. - Nice to meet you.
我看到你在外面的表现了 哥们 干得不错
I see you out there, man. You're doing great.
继续 继续保持
Keep... Just keep doing what you're doing.
享受工作 明白吗
Have a good time, you know?
你开心 顾客也会开心
The more fun you have, the more fun the customers have.
好的 谢啦
All right, thanks.
嘿打杂的 为什么12号桌还是脏的
Hey, busboy, why is table 12 still dirty?
哦 他们之前还在聊天
Oh, 'cause they were talking.
我觉得我不应该打扰到他们 但是
I didn't think I should interrupt them, but...
打断他们 让他们走
Interrupt them. Get them out of here.
- 好吧   - 这是你的工作
- All right. - Do your job.
- 抱歉   - 小心点 伙计
- Sorry. Whoa. - Take it easy there, brother.
- 我错了   - 天啊   - 谢谢
- My bad. - Jesus. - Thank you.
呃 你好 你这边吃完了吗
Uh, hi. Uh, are you done enjoying your meal?
我嘴巴里还有东西 而且我还在嚼呢
There is food in my mouth, and I am chewing.
你觉得我吃完了吗
Do you think that I'm finished?
我是举着这个纯当锻炼是吗
I'm just holding this for my health?
- 给我倒点水   - 抱歉
- Get me some water. - Sorry.
- 嘿 你过来 过来 我们能点单了吗   - 可以啊
- Hey, come here. Come here. Can we order? - Uh, yeah.
- 我去叫你这桌的服务员   - 不行 不行
- I'll go get your waiter. - No, no, no.
我们没时间等了 待会还有事呢
We don't have time for that. We're in a hurry.
我饿死了
I'm starving.
好 那我先点了
Okay. Can I go?
通常是女士优先 但算了你点吧
Usually, the woman goes first, but go ahead.
- 没事没事   - 是吗
- No, no, no, no. - Oh, yeah?
- 要不然这顿我付了   - 行吧
- How about I'm paying? - All right.
我要一个巴马芝士鸡胸排 加肉酱
Can I have a chicken parm with meat sauce?
不要放玛瑞纳拉酱
No marinara.
薄一点 鸡排要薄一点
Thin. Thin chicken parm.
你为什么不写下来
Why aren't you writing it down?
哦 因为我其实 我其实不负责点餐
Yeah, I-I can't actually because, uh, I'm not a waiter.
我只是个打杂的 所以他们没有给我笔
I'm just a busboy, so they don't even give me a pen.
那就记住了
Memorize it. Yeah.
我要一个海鲜意面
Seafood pasta. That's what I want.
不要蛤蜊 好吗 但是给我双份的虾
No clams, okay? Double up on the shrimp.
我总是这么点 我们是老顾客了
That's how I always get it. We come here all the time.
你们刚才说的话 我一句都没记住
I'm not gonna remember a word you guys just said.
这又不是什么高科技 赶紧去
It's not rocket science. Just go.
- 给我们下单   - 但我 好吧
- Get our shit. - Oh, I'm... All right.
我饿死了
I'm starving.
♪ Send me the addy, I'm hunting 'em down ♪
♪ Grrt, grrt... ♪
这是要开舞会吗还是什么？
There a dance party or something?
- 是格斗之夜 - 好的 格斗职业
- It's fight night. - All right, fight night!
冠军锦标赛！
Tournament of champions!
为了小费而战
Fighting for tips.
谁要上？谁第一个上？
Who's going? Who's going first?
-我，Zoots - Zoots
- I, Zoots. - Zoots.
- 每个人为了他们的小费而战 - 是我们赚的小费？
- Everyone fights for their tips. - The tips that we earn?
- 对，但是你现在必须要为它们而战了
Y-Yeah, but you have to fight for them now.
谁想来点 哼？
Who wants some?! Huh?!
- 嗯？ -谁要来？ - 到你了哥们
- Huh? - Who got it?! - It's you, bro.
- 不可能 不 不可能 - 把手套带上
- No way. No, no way. - Put the gloves on.
上吧 上吧 揍他
Get in there. Get in there. Hit him.
-嘿 哟 - 嘿
- Hey, yo. - Hey.
我不想 别这样 我不想干这个
I don't want... Please, I don... I-I don't want to do this.
- 我们还是别打了 - 你不想打了？
- Let's just not do this. - You don't want to do this?
- 你什么意思 - 嗯 我的意思是我们是朋友对吧
- What do you mean? - No, well, 'cause we're friends, right?
但是在接下来的15秒
Yeah, no, for the next 15 seconds,
我们的友谊结束了 朋友
this friendship is over, son.
-明白吗 - 啥？
- Understand that? - What?
- 嗯？ - 啥？
- Hmm? - What?
你必须得明白，格斗是件严肃的事情
Got to understand, fighting is serious.
-我不喜欢 - 太吓人了
- I don't like it. - It's sacred.
这是我向我的主和救世主致敬的方式
It's how I tribute my Lord and Savior.
-啥？ - 这是我向
- What? - It's the way I tribute
我的主和救世主致敬的方式，耶稣
my Lord and Savior, Jesus.
我不认为耶稣会让你
I don't think Jesus would want you
我把揍出屎
to kick my ass right now.
他想让我拿走小费
He would want me to have these tips.
- 这是他的意思 - 你可以把小费都拿走
- That's what he means. - You can have the tips.
我原来也没想要
I don't even want 'em.
- 这是啥啊 - 我不知道
- What is this? - I don't know.
这什么鬼
What's this shit?
我看过好几遍奎迪
I've seen Creed a f... a couple times.
- 你看了啥 - 我看了好几遍奎迪
- What'd you do? - I seen Creed a couple times.
- 噢 - 我们在跳棉花眼睛乔吗
- Oh. - Are we about to do the Cotton Eye Joe?
- 没错 - 没错
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- 来吧 朋友 - 好的
- Come on, son. - Okay.
- 好的 - 来吧 朋友 噢 这才对
- Yeah. Okay. - Come on, son. Oh, that's right.
你要打这里吗 这么打吗 朋友
You gonna come this way? Come this way, boy.
-好的 - 来吧 出拳吧伙计
- Okay. - Come on. Go ahead, take your shot, boy.
- 来吧 出拳吧 伙计 - 真的？
- Go ahead, take your shot, boy. - For real?
- 嗯哼 耶 来吧 - 噢
- Uh-huh, yeah. Come on! - Ooh!
现在我们是朋友了
Now we are friends,
- 该死的 - 噢 天啊
- goddamn it! - Oh, geez.
- 吃屎吧 耶
- Take that shit. Yeah!
我们现在是朋友啦 这就是朋友的意义
We friends now, nigga, 'cause that's what friends are for.
淘汰了这个家伙
Out this bitch.
(grunting rhythmically)
♪ Zoots又成功了一次 ♪
♪ Zoots done did it again, uh ♪
♪ 跟我说 Zoots又成功了一次 ♪
♪ Said Zoots done did it again, ah... ♪
我想我们有了赢家
I think we have a winner.
- 来吧 - 嗯嗯
- Come here. - Mm-hmm.
嗯
Mm.
嗯 让我...
Mm. Let me just...
- 我想把毛衣脱掉 - 好啊
- Just want to get this sweater off. - Okay.
再把这个灯关上
And I want to turn off this light.
让我把这个灯关上
Let me turn it off.
- 好 - 好
- Okay. - Okay.
(both grunt)
等我一下
Just one-one second.
让我 让我 把这个灯关上
Let me, let me, let me turn off this light.
台灯可真多
Got a lot of lamps, huh?
和商店似的
It's like a store or something.
来吧
Come here.
嗯
Mm.
("You Be Killin' 'Em" by Fabolous playing)
- ♪ 漂亮 ♪ - ♪ 噢 ♪
- ♪ Nice ♪ - ♪ Oh ♪
♪ 姑娘 最近怎样 我想我是多此一问♪
♪ You what's up, girl, ain't got to ask it ♪
♪ 现在要让他们都去死，我已经买好了棺材 ♪
♪ I dead 'em all now, I buy the caskets ♪
♪ 他们本来该逮捕你，或者直接逮捕那个给你买衣服的家伙 ♪
♪ They should arrest you or whoever dressed you ♪
♪ 我不想给你增添压力 ♪
♪ Ain't gon' stress you ♪
♪ 但是我想让你知道 姑娘 你的魅力秒杀了他们 ♪
♪ But I'm-a let you know, girl, you be killin' 'em ♪
♪ 你秒杀了他们 ♪
♪ You be killin' 'em ♪
♪ 姑娘 你秒杀了他们 ♪
♪ Girl, you be killin' 'em ♪
噢 噢 噢
♪ Uh-uh, oh ♪
♪ 一直被模仿 从未被超越 ♪
♪ Often imitated, never duplicated ♪
♪ 人们说她是个超级美女 要我说这都算低估 ♪
♪ They say she a dime, I say she underrated ♪
- ♪ 漂亮 ♪ - ♪我刚与她邂逅 ♪
- ♪ Nice ♪ - ♪ I just met her ♪
♪ 下一步已经出炉 ♪
♪ So the next solution ♪
♪ 让我的老情人 立马处决 ♪
♪ Dead my old chick, execution ♪
♪ 姑娘最近怎样 我想是多此一问 ♪
♪ You what's up, girl, ain't got to ask it ♪
♪ 现在要让他们都去死，我已经买好了棺材 ♪
♪ I dead 'em all now, I buy the caskets ♪
♪ 姑娘 你秒杀了他们 ♪
♪ Girl, you be killin' 'em ♪
♪ 你秒杀了他们 ♪
♪ You be killin' 'em ♪
♪ 姑娘 你秒杀了他们 ♪
♪ Girl, you be killin' 'em ♪
♪ 你秒杀了他们 ♪
♪ You be killin' 'em ♪
♪ 姑娘 你秒杀了他们 ♪
♪ Girl, you be killin' 'em... ♪
- Scott？ - 在
- Scott? - Yo.
过来一下
Come sit down.
我有点事情想给你说
I need to talk to you about something.
怎么啦
What's up?
有人死了？
Someone die?
不 谁都没死
No, no, nobody's dead.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
我开始约会了
I'm seeing somebody.
什么意思？
What does that mean?
呃 我在和男人约会
Uh, uh, I'm seeing a man.
我 我已经和个男人约会了一阵了
Well, I-I've been dating someone for a little while now.
你在约会？
You're dating someone?
那 那太棒了啊
That-That's awesome.
为啥你要偷偷的约会，小荡妇
Like, w-why are you dating him secretly, you little slut?
你怎么不告诉我呢
W-Why didn't you tell me?
是... 是因为他特别特别老...
Is he, like, really, really old or...
还是特别特别年轻
or is he really, really young?
难道是我的朋友？ 是Igor吗
Is it one of my friends? Is it Igor?
不 不 不 我只是
No, no, no. I just, I...
我只是不想让你困扰 除非这事能成
I just didn't want to bother you unless it was really serious.
困扰？你是我妈啊
Bother? You're my mom.
我当然希望你能好好的啊
I hope you're getting banged out real good.
这个幸运儿是谁啊
Who's the lucky guy?
额 是...
Uh, it's, um...
是Ray
It's Ray.
谁是Ray
Who's Ray?
你还记得那个被你纹身的孩子吗？
Remember the kid you tattooed?
是他爸爸
His father.
- 是那个混蛋？ - 嗯 我知道
- That fucking prick? - Yeah, I know.
他真的是个很好的人 对我也很好
He's a really nice man, and he's really good to me.
- 他还是消防员 - 他是个消防员?!
- And he's a fireman. - He's a fireman?!
这就操蛋了
That's fucked up.
- 为什么 - 你是什么意思 为什么
- Why? - W-What do you mean, why?
自从17年前我爸死了以后 你就没有约会过任何人了
I mean, uh, you haven't dated anyone in 17 years since Dad,
然后你约会的第一个人还是消防员？
and the first guy you date is a fireman?
你不感觉有点奇怪吗？
You don't think that's a little fucking weird?
我对消防员没什么意见啊
I got nothing against firemen.
我也没有 但是这家伙也不喜欢我
Neither do I, but the-the guy doesn't like me,
这人和我爸干着一样的工作
and he has the same job as Dad, like...
我已经搞砸了 妈 我还有克罗恩病
I'm fucked up as it is, Mom. Like, I have Crohn's, okay?
我这里也不怎么正常
There's something wrong up here. Huh.
我找不到手表
I can't find my watch!
你想对我做什么？！
What are you trying to do to me here?!
我受的苦还不够多吗
Haven't I been through enough?!
等等 我干了什么 我做错什么事了吗？
Wait, what did I, what did I do wrong?
- 我做错事了吗？ 我干了什么？
W-What did I do wrong? What did I do?
我 对不起 我做了什么
What... I'm sorry. Like, what did I do?
我没有 我没有对你怎么样
I'm not, I'm not doing it to you.
我只是不想下半辈子一直孤零零的
I just... I-I don't want to be alone the rest of my life.
我也不想让你孤独
I don't want you to be alone, either.
那这样就很烂了 就像是 就像是
That would suck, but, like, come on. This is, like...
这很明显不是一个好的选择 对吧？
This is pretty obvious this is not a good choice, right?
(sighs)
我想一起吃个饭
I would like us to have dinner.
这.... 这对我很重要
I... This is very, very important to me.
我对这份感情十分认真
I am in a serious relationship...
- 你十分认真？ - 和一个好人
- You're in a serious rela... - ...with a very nice man.
那个人？得了吧
With that guy?! Come on!
你不爱他的 对吧
Y-You don't love him, do you?
你不会那么说吧... 你不会那么说的 对吧
You're not say... You're not, like, saying that, right?
呃 我们还没说那个字
I-I... Well, we don't use that word yet.
但是如果他对我说了 我想我应该也会说
But if he said it to me, I-I would say it back.
噢天啊！上帝！
Oh, my God! Jesus!
你还没长记性吗？！
Do you not learn?!
你看看上次发生的事
Look what happened last time!
- 你想再来一遍吗？- 好的 好吧？
- You want to do that again? - Okay. All right?
这怎么样
How about this?
我们一起去你工作的餐厅
How about we come by the restaurant
吃一顿晚饭
and we have dinner when you're working
然后你就过来打个招呼
and you just come by and you just say hi?
就过来打几次招呼 怎么样？
Just say hi a couple times. How about that?
怎么样？
How about that?
怎么样... 你怎么不问问他？
How about... Why don't you ask him?
昂？
Huh?
你怎么在这里
Why don't you just build
也给Ray弄一个祠堂
another shrine to Ray while you're at it?
就放爸爸对面，搞不好他们还能成他妈的兄弟了！
Right across from Dad's so they can be fucking pals!
嗯 我更喜欢那个
Yeah, I like that better.
我才发现你还挺搞笑
But I'm actually finding you funny
因为你真的很搞笑
'cause you're really funny.
- (Margie laughs) - (jazz music playing)
看看这人
Look at this guy.
- 这辈子能有这样的时光 - 嗯
- Having the time of his life. - Mm-hmm.
好像这是他家一样
Acting like he owns the place.
我知道这家伙 帕马森烤茄子
I know that guy. Eggplant parmesan.
噢 我会的
Oh. I'll be.
你妈像个坏女孩哦
Your moms is a bit of a baddie.
她看起像是“事后”
She look postcoital.
- 什么“事后”？ - 就是睡完以后
- What's "postcoital"? - It's like post-fucking,
但因为是你妈，我想礼貌一点
but it's your mom, so I want to be nice.
但是 哦 绝对已经发生了
But, uh, oh, it's definitely happening.
(exhales slowly)
事后
Postcoital.
如果你来看我
If you ever come to see me,
如果你来看我 那...
if you ever come see me, that's...
- 那晚上会发生的 我保证 - 我知道
- It'll happen that night, I guarantee it. - Yeah, I know.
噢 他来了
Oh, here he is.
-嘿 -嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
- 你好吗 - 挺好 你呢
- How you doing? - Good. How are you?
很高兴再见到你
Good to see you again. Yeah.
呃 我很抱歉给你儿子打了标
Uh, I'm-I'm really sorry for branding your kid.
噢 没有没有 没关系的 没关系的
Oh, no, no, no. It's-it's fine. It's fine.
花了三百五十块 但是我没让你妈掏钱
Cost 350, but I didn't make your mom pay for it.
(Ray laughs)
但是 嘿 没伤害 没犯法
But, uh, hey, no harm, no foul.
你知道 要是没有这档子事 我...
You know? 'Cause, uh, if that didn't happen, I, uh...
我也不会遇见这位美丽的女士
wouldn't have met this lovely lady.
噢 很高兴帮忙
Oh, well, happy to help.
事情解决了
Things work out.
对
Yeah.
感谢上天我干了这事
Thank God I did what I did, then.
你们要不要先来点啥
Uh, would you guys like to start with still
呃 比如苏打水？
or, uh, sparkling water?
- 哦 那就苏打水 - 噢 苏打水 好
- Oh, let's go sparkling. - Uh, spar... Yeah.
你喜欢苏打水吗？
Yeah? You like sparkling?
- 喜欢 - 好的
- Yeah. - Okay.
我们能再来点面包吗？
Yeah. Oh, can we get some more bread, too?
一般就这样
Usually go still.
知道吗 上次我来的时候 面包是热着上来的
You know? Last time I came here, it came out hot.
- 对 - 真的 真的是太完美了
- Yeah. - It was... oh, it was perfect.
就像是我妈做的一样
It's like my mom made it.
当然
Sure.
苏打水和热面包
Sparkling and hot bread.
好的 谢谢伙计
All right. Thanks, buddy.
噢 你不能就那么吐口水 兄弟
Oh, you just can't spit on that like that, man.
你得狡猾一点 你可别就那么吐上
You got to be crafty. You can't just go out at, like...
你得 你得略施小计
You got to, you got to maneuver.
拿舌头舔舔或者放点料进去
Lick on it or put a boogie in it or something.
你觉着我能把这一整个塞进屁股里吗？
You think I can fit this whole thing in my ass?
如果 呃 你真的下决心要那么干 兄弟
If, uh, you really put your mind to it, bro.
嘿 我看见他往面包里吐口水了
Hey, I saw him spit in the bread.
来了 热腾腾的面包
All right, scorching hot bread.
- 哦  谢谢 - 好
- Oh, thank you. - Yeah.
你妈妈去上厕所了 请坐一下吧
Your mom's in the john. Have a seat.
噢 别担心 你没惹什么事
Oh, don't worry, you're not gonna get in trouble.
就一小会
Just for a minute.
好吧
All right.
那么... 你喜欢在这里工作吗
So... how, uh, how you liking the job here?
呃 挺操蛋的
Uh, it eats ass.
我记得 原来的时候
You know, I remember I... Back in the day,
我在那个地方 那个披萨店上过班
I used to work at that, uh, you know that pizza parlor
- 主路头上的那家？ - 嗯
- down there on Main Street? - Mm.
- 你还记得那家吗 - 我过去在那里上班
You remember the one? Yeah. I-I used to work down there.
我爱死它了 做披萨
I loved it. You know, making the pizzas.
姑娘们老来
Girls would come in, you know.
她们就不得不和我说话
It's like they just had to talk to me.
嗯
Yeah.
嗯 那真不错
Well, that's awesome.
我很开心你在披萨店约到不少
I'm glad you got laid a lot at your pizza place.
好吧 听着 Scott
All right. Listen, Scott.
- 我知道这有点奇怪
I-I know this is weird, okay?
你和你妈妈已经单独生活了很久
You and your mom were alone together for a long time.
你有自己的熟悉的环境 你明白吗？
You got set in your ways, you know?
你都已经习惯了
You got used to things.
但我不知道 我就感觉
But I don't know, I just feel like
你妈妈现在值得得到更多
your mother deserves more right now.
我是认真的 我真的觉得我可以让她高兴
And I'm serious, I really think that I can make her happy,
她也能让我高兴
and she makes me happy.
我的意思 这是件好事 对吧？
So, I mean, that-that's a good thing, right?
对 对 我觉得是个特棒的事
Yeah. Yeah, I think it's a great thing.
我... 我希望我妈高兴比一切都重要 那...
I... I want my mom to be happy more than anything, so...
那太好了 我也是
Good. I do, too.
你喜欢什么运动？
So, uh, what's your sport?
- 呃 我喜欢篮球 - 哦 是吗？
- Uh, I like basketball. - Oh, yeah?
- 嗯 - 打什么位置？
- Mm-hmm. - What position?
呃 我打小前锋
Uh, I played small forward.
-小前锋 - 对
- Small forward. - Yeah.
好吧 我自己算是棒球迷
All right. I'm kind of a baseball guy myself.
- 哦 是吗？ - 你喜欢 呃...
- Oh, yeah? - You like, uh...
我是个老头 我喜欢那玩意
I'm an old man. I like that stuff.
我有洋基队的季票
I got season tickets to the Yankees.
- 不可能吧 真的吗？ 那太帅了 - 对
- No way. Really? That's cool. - Yeah.
今年是史泰登岛的一年
I think it's Staten Island's year.
噢 史泰登岛洋基队啊
Oh, Staten Island Yankees.
- 小联盟 - 噢 当然
- Minor League. - Oh, absolutely.
我才不会掏钱去看那些贵的要死的小屁孩
I'm not gonna go pay to see those overpaid crybabies.
他们很努力的维持小联盟的位置
They try harder at the Minor League level.
还有 我还是红袜队的粉丝 从来没变过
Plus, I'm a Red Sox fan. I'm never setting foot
- 在那个体育场里 - 好吧 我得回去了
- in that stadium. - Well, I-I should get back
回去工作 呃 在被吼之前
to work, uh, before I get yelled at.
- 好吧 去吧 - 那么 就这样
- Okay. Go ahead. - So, yeah.
-当然 好的 - 好的
- Absolutely. All right. - All right, man.
享受热面包吧
Uh, enjoy the hot bread.
- 嘿 - 好的 酷
- Hey. - Okay, cool.
嘿
Hey.
你们两个在讨论什么呢
What are you fellas talking about?
- 嘿 妈妈 - 我就在问Scott
- Hey, Mom. - Oh, I was just asking Scott
他有没有空来看洋基队的比赛
if he wanted to go to a Yankee game sometime.
噢 Scott怎么说
Oh, what did Scott say?
-Scott... Scott说好啊
S-Scott... Scott said yeah.
好的 今天晚上谁要打拳
All right, who's fighting tonight?!
我想打打拳
I want to fight somebody!
哦 对不起 Pepe
Oh, I'm sorry, Pepe.
我不是针对你
Don't take this personally.
噢
Oh!
怎么了这是？
What happened?
就是一击刺拳
That was just a jab.
噢 没事的 Pepe
Oh, it's okay, Pepe.
- 没关系的 - 你... 你确定吗？
- It's all right. - You s... You sure?
当然
Yeah.
- 我之前从来也没有这样过
I-I mean, I never done that before, so...
我感觉很对不起你
I feel bad for you.
("Down on the Corner" by Creedence Clearwater Revival)
♪ 在街道上 ♪
♪ Down on the corner ♪
♪ 的角落里 ♪
♪ Out in the street ♪
♪ Willy在和穷孩子们一起玩耍 ♪
♪ Willy and the Poor Boys... ♪
你好啊 谢谢
How you doing? Thank you.
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
♪ 装腔作势的人在路上栽了跟头 ♪
♪ Rooster hits the washboard ♪
♪  引来了人们的朗朗笑声 ♪
♪ And people just got to smile ♪
♪ 弹贝斯的人的勇气可嘉还独奏了一段
♪ Blinky thumps the gut bass and solos for a while ♪
♪ 穷孩子们听的他的... ♪
♪ Poor Boy twangs the rhythm out... ♪
观众们请注意
May I please remind you
场地内禁止使用闪光灯拍照
that there is no flash photography.
你好吗 你好吗 你们还在戒酒吗
How are you? How are you? You guys still sober?
(crowd cheering)
- 投球真垃圾 投的真烂 - 你就那么干！
- Shitty throw. Shitty throw, though. - That's how you do it!
好的 就这样 就这样
All right, there we go. There we go.
跑啊 北鼻 跑啊
Let's go, baby, let's go.
活灵活现
Look alive!
(women whooping, shouting)
你觉着他们能拿下三色堇施平纳吗
Think we're gonna take these pansy Spinners tonight?
哦 兄弟 我觉着拿不下施平纳
Oh, man, we can't take the Spinners,
- 你也许就只需要关上它 - 嗯
- you might as well just shut it down. - Mm.
我们需要结束它
We should just pack it in,
把这些人送回小联盟
send these guys back to Single-A.
我孩子小联盟的队伍可以给这些人
My kid's Little League team could give these guys
争取些钱
a run for their money.
这些人也都有工作
These guys are all on the job, too.
这是老混蛋
The old ballbuster here...
他是这里的老大哥
he's the senior man of the house.
你叫我老大哥？
Did you call me a senior?
你是这里唯一的秃子
You're the one who's bald.
得了吧 Papa 我就是开个玩笑
Come on, Papa. I'm just fucking around.
嘿 想吃热狗吗
Hey, you want a hot dog?
噢 不 我有克罗恩病
Oh, no, I can't. I, uh, I have Crohn's.
那是个啥
What's that?
就是你的胃里全部都乱套了
It's, like, when the lining of your stomach is all messed up,
让你一直都很难受
so it makes you shit all the time.
哦 谢谢分享
Oh, thanks for sharing.
下次你就只说“我不想要热狗”就行
Next time, just say, "I don't want a hot dog."
好的 我只是想让大家了解一下
All right, I'm just trying to spread awareness.
(crowd cheering)
就这样 就这样
There we go. There we go.
-打得漂亮 打得漂亮 - 看着真棒 伙计们
- Nice hit. Nice hit. - Looking good, guys.
干的不错
Way to hustle.
26号
Number 26...
嘿 呃
Hey, uh...
你有没有想过要穿上这身制服
you ever think about putting on the jacket?
- 不 - 你笑的什么
- No. - What are you laughing about?
这是个很傻的问题 Ray
'Cause it's a stupid question, Ray.
- 你说傻什么意思 - 这他妈就是很傻
- What do you mean, stupid? - It's fucking stupid.
如果你问那个在太空炸死的老师的孩子
Would you ask the kids of that teacher who blew up in space
你想不想当个宇航员
if they want to be an astronaut?
哇 我不觉着那个女士有孩子
Whoa, I don't think that lady had any kids, though.
是啊 我也觉着她没有 她都死在天上了
Yeah, I'm sure she didn't 'cause she died in space.
你要是死在天上就不太容易生个孩子
It's hard to have kids when you're dead in space.
听着 我可以告诉你我对消防员的感觉
Look, I-I could tell you how I feel about firemen,
但是 我觉着这些伙计不会想听我的意见
but I-I don't think you guys want to hear my opinion.
- 不是的 请告诉我们 - 别 别 别这样
- No, no, no, please tell us. - No, no. No, no, no.
- 别 我不想听 - 你不用非得那么干
- No. I want to hear it. - You don't got to do this, man.
- 得了吧 - 行吧
- Come on. - All right, no.
- 行 那这样怎么样 - 算了 你别
- Yeah. Okay, how about this? - Come on, you don't...
嗯 如果你是个消防员 就别要孩子了
Uh, if you're a fireman, just don't have kids
或者家庭也干脆别要 行吧？
or a family at all, okay?
那样的话 当你他妈有一次回不了家的时候
So that way, you don't fucking crush them
也不会让他们彻底崩溃 明白吗？
when you don't come home that one time, you know?
你们就是太自私了
And-and you're just so selfish.
你们成天就和你们的兄弟闲逛
You just hang out with your boys all day
像他妈的兄弟会一样
like it's a fucking frat house.
甚至一半的时间都没在灭火
Half the time, you're not even putting out fires.
就只会打飞机 看疤面煞星 对吧？
You're just jerking off, watching Scarface, okay?
- 行了 放松点 伙计 - 不 我就是那么说
- All right, take it easy, man. - No, I'm just saying.
你告诉孩子你会一辈子
And it's wrong to tell a kid that you're gonna be there
陪在他身边是不对的
for him for his whole entire life.
嗯 然后你就会错过毕业典礼 错过生日 是吧
Yeah, but you miss graduation, your birthdays, okay?
嗯 还有我的毕业舞会
Uh, my d... my prom dances.
这对一个孩子来说太残忍了
That's a very mean thing to do to children.
如果你有一个家庭
And, uh, if you have a family,
- 那你就是个混蛋 - 不 听我说 不
- y-you're an asshole. - No, listen, no.
放松 放松点
Take it easy, take it easy.
- 这是一种方式看待他 - 对
- Well, that's one way to look at it. - Yeah.
给我爸说去吧
Tell that to my dad.
但是你不能 因为他死了
Oh, but you can't, 'cause he's dead.
有人能帮我转达他吗
- Anybody got a good response to that?
耶
Yeah!
再来
Again!
哇哦
Whoo!
比赛太棒了 比赛太棒了
What a game. What a game.
所以 我不该生孩子了？
So, what, I shouldn't have kids?
不 你可以有孩子
No, you... you should have kids.
我要生孩子
I'm gonna have kids.
你知道 也许你该从你的T恤上
You know, maybe you should take a cue
学一下 明白吗 微笑
from your shirt, you know? Smile.
放轻松
Lighten up.
实际上还挺搞笑
That's actually kind of funny.
好的伙计们 为什么不能更像他一点
Guy's all right. Why can't you be more like him?
他没事的
He's all right.
为什么你要让我那么尴尬
Why can't you not embarrass me like this?
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起我让你在你朋友面前丢人了
I'm sorry I embarrassed you in front of your friends.
(laughs)
继续坚持你的立场吧
And just-just stick to your guns.
好吗？ 会好的
All right? It'll be fine.
嘿 嘿
Hey. Hey!
进来吧
Come on in.
和我们一块吃早饭
Come have breakfast with us.
我做了薄烤饼 还做了你喜欢吃的香肠
I made pancakes, and I made the sausage that you like,
还有煎蛋卷
an omelet.
来吧 来吧 来坐下
Come, come, come, come sit.
伙计 这鸡蛋配着
Man, these eggs are spectacular.
洋葱和胡椒真的太赞了
With the onions and the peppers.
太好吃了 太好吃了
I love it. I love it.
他这是 在这里呆了一晚上吗
Did, uh, did he sp-spend the night?
对 是的
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
他昨晚睡在这里
He slept here.
在这屋里
In this house.
我已经成年了哦 这没什么问题
I'm an adult. I can do that.
有些事情我想和你谈一谈
I-I need to talk to you about something.
好的
Okay.
我觉得 你现在是时候
I was thinking that it's time
去找一间属于你自己的公寓了
to think about getting your own apartment.
什么
What?
你为什么这么说
W-Why would you say that?
是这样的
Well...
你呢 是个很棒的孩子
You are so awesome.
而我呢 有时候可能有点过分关照你了
And I think I've been there for you too much.
人嘛 往往只有在失去安全感的时候
'Cause sometimes in life, the thing that's motivating
才能激发他的潜能
is when people don't have that safety net.
话是没错 但我现在正需要这份安全感
Right, right, but I need that safety net
我还没准备好呢
'cause I don't have my shit together.
为什么 你早不提完不提 偏偏现在提
So, like, uh, w-why are you doing this?
是因为他吗
Is this 'cause of him?
不
No.
你看你也二十四岁了
It's just you're 24 years old now.
二十四啊 菲尔普斯二十四的时候都好几块金牌了
24. I mean, Phelps had a fistful of gold medals by 24.
你插什么嘴
Why are you talking?
我也就是给些参考 没别的意思
I'm just giving you some perspective, that's all.
你看啊 格雷茨基二十四岁的时候 已经打进了九十六球
You know, Wayne Gretzky had, like, 96 goals when he was 24.
啥
W-What?
罗杰 斯陶巴 现实毕业于西点军校
Roger Staubach graduated West Point,
然后赢得了海斯曼奖 再参加了越南战争
won a Heisman Trophy, fought in the Vietnam War,
回来后加盟了达拉斯牛仔 那时他也就二十四岁
and then joined the Cowboys by the time he was 24.
这都是些什么人 关我屁事啊
I don't know who that is, so, s-so who-who gives a fuck?
我觉得 你应该可以的
I think that maybe you're-you're ready
只是你自己不自觉
and you just don't even know it.
所以你是要把我赶出去咯
So, you're kicking me out?
不 不是的
No, no.
我只是希望 你可以在明年夏天前 找好自己的公寓
I just want you to get your own apartment by summer.
好的 所以说就是把我赶出去咯
Right, so you're kicking me out of the house.
有整整九个月的时间呢
That's nine months from now.
你看啊 九个月你如果动作快一点孩子都有了
I mean, you-you could have a baby in nine months.
时间还多着呢
It's a long time.
你是要搬进来吗 所以先要把我挤出去吗
Are you moving in? Are you trying to push me out?
我到底是做了什么 我以为我们俩关系还行
What, like, what did I do? I-I thought we were cool.
Scott 大家都是成年人了 要互相体谅
Scott, Scott, let's all be adults here. Come on.
你妈妈已经以努力了很久了
Your mother has worked very hard for a very long time.
我呢过几年也要退休了
And I'm gonna retire in a couple years,
所以生活呢会发生一些变化 当然了这都是往好的方向在转变
so things are gonna change around here, but in a good way.
我们相信 你可以自己干出一番成就的
I mean, w-we think you... that you can do great things.
对对对 我知道我会赶出一番成就
Yeah, I know I'm gonna do great things.
但这不需要你来提醒我 而且啊
But, like, I don't need you to tell me that, like...
这到底是怎么回事
This is... What's going on?
我怎么了我
This is... I-I...
我不喜欢这样
I don't like this.
别太在意 就目前来说
So, be that as it may,
直到你搬出去前 当然了搬出去对你是一件好事
until you leave... which is gonna be good for you
可以帮助你更积极地面对生活
and it's gonna be motivating...
搬出去前 你需要帮忙干点活儿
you're gonna have to pull your weight
不多不多 就一点儿
a little more around here.
比方说 有件事情 我们就觉得你一定能胜任
And one thing that we thought would help you contribute...
对你来说举手之劳 一点都不难
would be easy, wouldn't be hard to do...
我们觉得 当Ray需要工作 没有时间的时候
is to help Ray bring his kids back and forth to school
你可以去帮Ray接孩子上下学
when he can't do it because of work.
比如现在
Like now.
今天开始
Like today.
你们在逗我吧
You're joking, right?
你要我帮你接孩子?
You want me to take your kid to school?
就是我给纹身的那个?
The kid that I tattooed?
我有两个孩子 另一个现在七岁
I got two kids. The other one's seven.
你要让我帮你带孩子啊
You're gonna make me babysit your kids?
这... 我嗑药的哦
Do... I'm on... I do drugs.
没事 我看你现在很清醒啊
Well, looks like you're walking.
谢谢
And thank you.
我现在可是一肚子意见啊听到没有
I'm not cool with any of this, okay?
况且 你们要我搬哪里去
And-and where do you expect me to live?
我拿什么钱去找地方
And w-with what money?
你知道我还在啃老的不是吗
You know I'm a fucking bum, right?
都什么乱七八糟的 卧槽
Yo, this is fucked up! Seriously.
尤其是昨天晚上 还搞什么交流感情
Especially after last night, all that bonding boy bullshit.
你真的是满嘴跑火车
You're full of shit, man.
就是一个骗子
You're a fucking liar.
那么 我现在就去帮你接孩子
I'm gonna go walk your kids.
接个屁 你想也不要想
No, I'm not fucking letting you take 'em.
你谁啊你 就来接孩子
Fuck you. Who the fuck are you?
你可说得太对了
Yeah, I-I agree with you completely.
我来接孩子 这都是Ray出的主意
Why... 'cause that... It was Ray's idea.
我也觉得我来接很不妥当 真的
I don't think I should be taking them, either.
你说得对
I agree with you.
你是傻逼吗
Are you a weirdo?
哈 可傻逼了
Oh, the weirdest.
谁能傻得过我呀
Nobody's weirder than me.
得了吧 傻逼哪会承认自己是傻逼
See, a weirdo wouldn't say that.
傻逼都说自己不傻逼
A weirdo would deny it.
那么 我是接还是不接呢
So, do I have to take 'em or...?
接
Yes.
妈呀
God, no.
那怎么办 本来应该是Ray干的活
I mean, Ray was supposed to do it.
我也没办法
I can't fucking do it.
还有半个小时就上课了
Their schools start half an hour apart
去学校还要横跨整个小镇呢
on the other side of town.
我说 你妈勾搭了我前夫是吧
So, your mom is banging my ex?
对 而且我也不是很开心
Yeah, I'm not thrilled about it, either.
那是 你开心的起来就邪乎了
Yeah, well, you shouldn't be.
Harold. Kelly.
你们过来 快
Come here. Come here.
有好玩的事情哦 快过来
There's something, something kind of fun.
来这边
Come here. Come here.
你好啊
Oh, hey, man.
这个是Harold 这个是Kelly
So, this is Harold, and this is Kelly.
这位是...
And, uh, this is...
Scott
Scott.
好的Scott 接下来他送你们去学校
Scott. He's gonna be taking care of you.
- 听到了吗   - 你好啊 Scott
- Okay?   - It... - Nice to meet you, Scott.
你好啊 Harold 第一次见面吧
Hi, Harold. It's nice to meet you.
真高兴认识你
For the very first time.
如果他做了什么奇怪的事情
If he does anything weird,
你们就告诉我
you tell me.
就算他让你们不要说 你们也告诉我
Even if he tells you not to tell me, you tell me.
我觉得这人应该挺正常的 但也不是没可能看走眼
I'm pretty sure he's not weird, but I could be wrong.
明白了吗
'Kay?
- 爱你们哦   - 好的
- Love you. - Okay.
- 爱你 妈妈   - 我可没开玩笑
- Love you, Mom. - Seriously.
爱你 妈妈 拜拜
Love you, Mom. Bye.
小心了
Pay attention.
明白
Got it.
拉好手 两个人的都拉好
Hold both their hands!
谢谢你了
Thank you.
看汽车 先看左边 再看右边啊
Look both ways. Look both ways!
让他别吵
Tell her to stop.
妈呀
God!
Harold 你平时喜欢什么呀
So, w-what do you like to do, Harold?
我喜欢超级英雄
I like superheroes.
哈 谁不喜欢呢
Well, so does everybody.
我喜欢自己想出来的
No, I make up my own.
这样啊 什么样的英雄呀
Oh, yeah? What kind?
闪冰侠
Ice Flash.
他能干什么呢
What does he do?
他能把东西冻住 还能向别人射出冰块
He freezes stuff and shoots ice at people.
哦 听着不是很厉害呀
Oh, well, that's not gonna work.
为什么
Why not?
我那个电吹风就能锤爆他了
I could just use a hair dryer and ruin him.
不过想法不错 再接再厉
Keep thinking, though.
你呢 你平时都喜欢干什么呀
What do you got? What do you like to do?
- 我喜欢唱歌   - 唱歌呀
- I like to sing. - You do?
能给我来一曲儿吗
Could-could you sing for me?
好的
Sure.
啊 多么美丽的早晨
♪ Oh, what a beautiful morning ♪
嗯
Yes.
呕 多么美丽的一天
♪ Oh, what a beautiful day ♪
很好
All right.
喜悦由心而生
♪ I've got a wonderful feeling ♪
万事顺心发展
♪ Everything's going my way. ♪
唱的真好听 击个掌来
That shit was dope. High five.
她唱歌可好了
She's a good singer.
这首歌的歌词我持保留意见
I don't agree with the sentiment of the song,
但唱得真不错
but it was really great.
就这样 在学校一天开心哦
Anyway, have a great day at school.
至少 但愿不会太糟糕
Uh... I hope it's not shitty,
还有 给你妹妹 一个吻别吧
and, um, yeah, give your, uh, sister a kiss goodbye.
- 我们从不搞这个   - 你吻就是了
- We don't do that. - Just do it.
怎么样 感觉不错吧
See? Wasn't that nice?
如果她明天就挂了 那你至少你会记得
Now, if she dies tomorrow, you'll remember that,
你吻别过你妹妹了
that you kissed her goodbye.
上学愉快哦
Have a good day at school.
- 拜拜   - 小心点
- Later, man. - Pay attention.
- 我明天怎么就挂了呢  - 不知道
- Why would I die? - I don't know.
这种事情你永远都说不准
You never know what's gonna happen.
你觉得自己是不死之身吗
Think you're immortal?
这里 就是这间
This. It's this one.
好的
Okay. All right.
那么 在学校玩得开心哦
Well, have a good day, okay?
- 好的   - 放学再见 大概吧
- Okay. - I'll see you soon, I guess.
- 请问需要什么帮助吗   - 呕 你好啊
- Can-can I help you? - Oh, hi.
我是Ray的朋友
I'm-I'm Ray's friend.
我就是来送她上学的
I was just here to bring her here.
- 你认识Ray吗   - 大概算认识吧
- You-you know Ray? - I know Ray a little bit.
他最近在勾搭我妈妈
He's kind of, like, banging my mom.
所以 你懂的 嗯
So, yeah, I'm just, you know,
我就把她送过来了
just dropping her off.
你再办公室那边登记过吗
Did you sign in at the office?
没有 我都不知道还有办公室
No. I didn't even know you had an office.
好吧
Okay, um...
Kelly 你有什么问题吗
Kelly? You okay?
没有
Yeah.
- 你确定吗   - 确定
- You sure? - Yeah.
如果有的话你可以告诉我哦
You know you can tell me.
我没事
I'm okay.
你认识他吗
Do you know him?
算认识吧
Yeah, kind of.
是个新朋友
He's a new friend.
好的
Okay.
哈 我在车里教她教得可好了 才不会招供呢
Oh, I trained her in the car. She's not gonna break.
开玩笑的
I'm just kidding.
我是不会伤害她的
It's, uh... I'm not gonna hurt her.
那么 祝一天愉快 我这就...
Um, but have a great day. I just...
那个 等等 能不能帮忙把画都摆好
No, uh, actually, could you, uh, set up the paints?
- 不   - 来 来 来
- No. - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- 还有这些刷子   - 不
- Uh, and just wash these brushes. - No.
- 谢谢你啦   - 不 不
- Thank you so much. - No. No.
- 谢谢   - 不
- Thank you! - No.
不好意思 请问您有没有看过
Did-did you happen to get a chance
- 我给你的那个   - 哦 看过你的本子了
- to take a look at the, uh... - Yeah, I looked at your book.
我以前也这么干过 大概十四岁的时候吧
I mean, I drew like that, too, when I was 14.
从你的本子来看 你还缺少一些基本的东西
From what I saw, you don't really have the basics,
你得再练练
so you got to figure that out.
嗯 所以我才来这里的
Well, yeah, that's why I'm here.
我希望可以从你这里学纹身
I mean, I was hoping I can learn from you.
那么 你就是要做我的学徒咯
Right, well, um, you'd be my apprentice.
你在店里会和一个奴隶一样
Uh, you'll be a slave to the shop.
- 没事的 只要我最后可以给被人纹身   - 不行
- Hey, man. As long as I get to tattoo people, right? - No.
在我允许你纹身之前 不行
Never. Until I say.
你要做的是给针消毒 给我洗车
Uh, you'll be sterilizing needles, washing my car,
帮店里扔垃圾
taking the trash out.
基本上 就是个店里的佣人
I mean, you're basically our bitch.
那么 在这里打工能挣 大概多少钱呢
So, how much will I be, like, making here?
- 挣个鸡巴   - 鸡巴
- Dick. - Dick.
好吧
Okay, well...
有很多人想要这份工作呢 老兄
It's a long line of people who want this job, man.
那我怎么付房租啊
How do I, like, pay my rent?
这就不是我要关心的问题了
That one right there is not my problem.
你第一天来这里 已经开始抱怨了是吧
It's your first day, you're already complaining.
很奇怪 不是吗
It's kind of weird, huh?
不然还是算了吧
Yeah, let's not do this.
你还是出去走走吧
You should take a walk.
- 每种   - 好吧
- Pussy. - All right.
那我能问个问题吗
Well, could I ask you a question?
假设我在这里工作
If I did work here?
他怎么还在这里
Why is he still here?
比如说吧 有个傻帽来到店里
Let's say some idiot walks in, right?
他想要纹一个死神在身上 而这个死神呢
And he wants to get a tattoo of a Confederate flag
还披着美国国旗
wrapped around the Grim Reaper.
你可以让那个傻帽滚蛋的是吧
You could tell that guy to go fuck himself, right?
毕竟这么一个纹身实在是太二了
'Cause that's a ridiculous tattoo to ask for.
我不会去评价别人想纹的图案
It's not my place to judge people, man.
这不是我该干的事情
I don't do that.
那如果来了另一个人呢 他走了进来
Well, what if another guy walked in and he wanted to get
想要把他死去的朋友James纹在胸口
a tattoo of his dead friend James on his chest, right?
但是你知道那个James
But you know James, and you don't want
你不想纹这个图案 因为你知道
to give him the tattoo, 'cause you know James
James是个混账 世界上少了他
and he's an asshole and that the world's
才算清净呢
better off without him.
- 那你该怎么办   - 你找死吗
- What do you do then? - You have a death wish?
不 我不想找死
No, I don't have a death wish.
但那位摩托车上的女士有点那意思
But that lady on the motorcycle does.
她连内裤都没穿一条
She's not even wearing any underwear.
- 下面可是会烧焦的啊   - 你欠揍是吧
- She's gonna burn her pussy. - Do you want to do this?
欠揍就来啊 我来揍你
You really want to fucking do this?
不不不 我不想挨揍
I don't want to do anything with you.
我只想知道James是怎么死的
I just want to know who killed James.
是那个披着国旗的家伙干的吗
Was it the Confederate flag man?
还是骑摩托的小姐姐干的
Was it the motorcycle lady?
说实话 Kelsey 你和照片上真的是一模一样
I got to be honest, Kelsey, you look exactly like your picture.
不过更加丰满一些 更劲爆
You're kind of thicker, more robust.
哈哈哈 谢谢
Oh, thank you.
- 真的   - 瞧你夸的
- Yeah. - It's a compliment.
你看着有点像 安东尼奥 班德拉斯
You look a little bit like Antonio Banderas,
不过我先得把眼睛眯起来看
if I squint really hard.
哈哈 那你就眯着吧
Oh, please squint all night long.
别睁开了
That's great.
真的Chelsea... 不好意思 我是说Kelsey
Chelsea, you are... I mean, Kelsey, I'm sorry.
- 没事没事 正常   - 你不介意就好
- Th-That's all right. It's only... - Yeah, you know.
你叫什么来着
What's your name again?
- 我已经忘了   - 我叫Jake
- I forgot already. - Um, it's Jake.
实在是不好意思
Sorry about that.
你是做什么的呀
So, uh, w-what do you do?
我在学习如何在城市中工作
Oh, I'm studying to work in the city.
- 哦   - 我想可以
- JAKE: Oh. - Um, I want to make
让史坦顿岛重新成为一个好地方
Staten Island, like, a great place again.
这个岛已经很不错啦 为什么要这么做呢
Staten Island's already cool. What are you talking about?
是呀
Yeah, it is.
- 真的挺不错了   - 你是我见过第一个这么说的人
- Yeah. Yeah, it is. - You're the first person here to say that.
不不不不不
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
这可是这个星球上最好的地方了
It's the best place on Earth.
至少在东海岸 是一个不错的地方吧
Well, at least on the East Coast, I think.
不好意思
Excuse me.
嗨
Oh, hey.
- 嘿   - 你好
- Hey. - Hi.
- 你好   - 嘿
- Hello. - Hey.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
你们想要 汽水 还是说没汽的
Uh, would you guys like, uh, still or sparkling water?
你来选吧
Um, you pick.
我比较喜欢带汽的
Uh, I'm more of a sparkling guy,
- 那就汽水   - 就汽水吧
- so sparkling. - Sparkling it is.
不过我更喜欢龙舌兰 所以我能否
But I do like tequila, so if I could
来一小瓶 再加块冰块
get just a Patrón, you know, with a rock.
- 可以吗   - 没问题 可以 没问题
- That cool with you? - That's fine. Yeah, that's fine.
- 可得吗 那就好 我比较喜欢龙舌兰   - 没问题
- Yeah? Cool. Yeah, I prefer a tequila. - Cool.
龙舌兰加冰 你们还需要什么吗 热面包啊
Tequila and rock. You guys want, like, warm bread or...
橄榄油啊
uh, olive oil?
面包吧
Warm bread.
呕
Oh.
老兄啊 你不会又把一个顾客给吓跑了吧
Bro, did you scare off another customer?
你怎么回事啊
What's wrong with you?
真的很不好意思
I'm so sorry about that.
他是有人介绍开后门进来的
He has, like, nepotism, you know?
疣荏㿍烧是什么病
Is that a disease?
是一种很坏的病
Yeah, it's a bad one.
我带个人过来就是想让你吃醋
I brought that guy here to make you jealous.
好气气你
You could give a fuck.
让我吃醋啊
T-To make me jea...
- 你一点都不吃错 也不生气   - 我在乎啊
- You don't seem jealous or upset at all. - I do care.
我当然在乎啊
Of course I care.
我在Tinder上找了一个最帅的男人
I chose the hottest guy on Tinder.
你看看我 看看我
Look at me. Look at me.
看看我的胸
Look at my tits.
都和埃菲尔铁塔差不多了
There is literally the Eiffel Tower...
就拖在这里
it's holding them up in here.
你看着很漂亮
You look great. I'm...
谢谢你啊
Thank you.
请别在这里哭了 求你了
Please don't cry here. Please.
你看着太糟糕了
You look awful.
啥 啥意思 什么糟糕不糟糕的
What? What do you mean? What are you...
你的皮都快透光了 还有你那黑眼圈
Your skin looks see-through and the circles around your eyes
看着就和一只厌食的熊猫似的
are so dark you look like an anorexic panda.
唉 我知道
I... Well, I-I know.
我知道
I know I do.
你总是看着病怏怏的 皮肤苍白得和得了病一样
You always look sick and pale like you have a disease
你自己是不知道 但你现在看上去
but you don't know it yet, but you literally look like
好像我轻轻碰你一下你就要灰飞烟灭了一样
if I touched you, you'd just turn to dust.
对不起 我最近过得不是很好
I'm sorry. I-I'm not doing very well.
我真的 你懂的 我
I-I'm not, you know... I...
那我怎么和你约会的对象解释啊
Well, what do I tell your date?
你问我啊 让他滚蛋啊
I don't know. Tell him to fuck off.
我就刚认识他十分钟 是个做DJ的
I met him ten minutes ago. He's a DJ.
你为啥觉得控冰就不能是一种牛逼的超能力呢
Why do you not think ice is a good superpower?
牛逼坏了好嘛
It's amazing. I mean...
闪冰侠的冰是无所不能的
Ice Flash can do anything with his ice.
而且坚不可摧
And it's indestructible
那可是超级英雄的冰啊
'cause it's superhero ice.
他可以用冰做一个反射一切的大盾牌
He can make giant shields that reflect anything.
可以制造一个巨大的冰坦克
He can make giant ice tanks,
还有大号的冰飞机
giant ice planes and giant jets,
还有发射大导弹的直升机
helicopters that shoot giant missiles.
想想就激动啊 什么都能变
I mean, think of all the possibilities.
这么一说的确挺厉害
That's actually kind of cool.
- 谢谢   - 都是你自己想出来的吗
- Thanks.   - You came up with that?
是的
Yeah.
你越来越厉害了呢
You're getting, like, really good at this.
谢谢
Thanks.
他的盾牌是什么颜色的
What color is his shield?
额 是冰的颜色
It's, well, the color of ice.
那么 冰的颜色是什么样的颜色呢 透光的那种吗
Well, what's the color of ice? Is it, like, see-through?
比如淡蓝的 还是说
Like, light blue ice or is it like...?
是淡蓝的 因为
It's blue ice 'cause it's...
- 就像是超级英雄的冰 超厉害   - 好的
- it's, like, superhero ice, and it's cool. - Right.
Ronnie 还记得那个孩子吗
You remember that kid Ronnie?
舅舅开药店的那个
His uncle owns the pharmacy.
他给了我钥匙 我们马上就要满载而归了
He gave me the key. We're gonna load up on oxys.
所以从今往后我们就做起抢匪了吗
So, we're robbers now. That's our future.
不不不不 就这么一次嘛
Nah. Nah, nah, nah, nah. We're gonna do this one time.
干他一票 才能梦想成真
Get the money to seed our dreams.
才能有启动资金
Get that venture capital.
才能开一家你想要的纹身餐厅
Open that tattoo restaurant you wanted.
这也没什么 Jay-Z 也这么做的
It's not that big a deal. Jay-Z did it.
他就是通过卖白面才有钱搞Rap的
He sold crack to fund his rap career.
但是Jay-Z的朋友基本上 不是死了就是在蹲大牢吧
Aren't most of Jay-Z's friends, like, dead or in jail?
没错 但在这次行动中 我们是Jay-Z
Yeah, but we're Jay-Z in this situation.
而不是Jay-Z的朋友
We're not Jay-Z's friends.
但Jay-Z只有一个啊
We can't all be Jay-Z.
不可能有四个Jay-Z吧 这不合理啊
There can't be four Jay-Zs. That doesn't make any sense.
你们知道的吧 我可以为你们赴汤蹈火
You guys know I'd do anything for you, right?
谢谢
Thank you.
- 谢谢   - 但这事儿不行 我不干
- Appreciate you. - Just not this. I'm out.
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
- 你说什么   - 这太疯狂了
- What? - This is crazy.
嘿 我们不能没有你 你可是在外面放哨的啊
Hey, we need you, all right? You're the lookout.
放哨谁不能放啊
Literally anybody can be the lookout.
- 我不想参与到这种事情里来   - 不 不 不 不
- I don't need to be a part of this. - No, no, no, no, no, no.
我们需要你 你是我们最好的朋友
We need you. You're our best friend.
- 我们信任你   - 啥
- We trust you. - Wha...
但是 好朋友是不会让他的好朋友
Well, best friends don't make other best friends
去做违法乱纪的蠢事的
do stupid illegal shit.
你让我干的蠢事还不够多吗
You make me do stupid shit for you all the time.
- 比如说?   - 我想想啊
- Like what? - Uh, I don't know.
记得有一次你以为你
What about the time when you thought
- 得睾丸癌了吗   - 又来了
- you had testicular cancer? - Here we go.
- 我就知道又是这事情   - 是的吧
- Knew this was gonna come up. - All right?
我大老远开车过来 然后你让我摸你蛋蛋
And then I drive over and you make me touch your nuts.
换了我我也会为你这么做啊
I would've done it for you, bro.
如果你说 艾玛我的屁股好像有什么问题
You're like, "Hey, yo, there's something wrong with my ass."
- 那我也会说 来 裤子脱了   - 得了吧
- I'd be like, "Yo, bend over." - Come on.
我们为你做了这么多事
After everything we've done for you?
你能为我做些什么呢
What do you do for me?
我让你把我全身都纹了一遍
I let you tattoo my whole body.
所以呢 你不是很喜欢吗
So what? You love my tattoos.
你把我当做了人肉笔记本
You use me as a human sketchbook.
我是真 真的
I-I-I-I don't, really.
没有我嘴上说的那么喜欢这纹身
I don't. Not as much as I say I do.
我不干 对不起
I'm out of here. My bad.
你啊 你
You know what?
就是个怂包
You're a real bitch!
- 大怂包   - 嘘
- You're a bitch! - Shh.
嘘你个头啊 嘘
Yo, don't shush me.
-噢 -天啊 看她这是有多兴奋
- Oh. - My God, look how excited she is.
-我认为肯定是她 -我已经兴奋得飞起来
- I'm assuming that's her. - I started running too early!
嗨
Hey! Oh.
噢 你这也太纤瘦了
Oh, oh, oh, you're so skinny.
-一直都有进食吗？ -是呀
- Have you been eating? - Yeah.
-嗨 -嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
你好吗？
How are you?
这是Ray
This is Ray.
-嗨 -你好吗？-噢
- Hey. How you doing? - Oh.
-很高兴我们最终还是见面了 -很高兴见到你
- Nice to finally meet you. - Nice to meet you.
我觉得我已经很了解你了
Yeah, I feel like I already know you.
你母亲时常提起你
Your mom talks about you all the time.
-噢 是嘛 -哦
- Oh, God. - Oh.
不 仅提及你的优点 真的只是你的优点
No, only good stuff, only good stuff.
我们可以去吃点什么吗？ 我真的已经厌倦了吃盒饭
Should we go eat? I am so sick of eating off a tray.
-你饿吗？ -好 我也想吃
- You hungry? - Yeah, I could eat.
-可以随时吃 -蛤
- Could always eat. - Uh-huh.
学校不错
Beautiful school.
“好呀 我也想吃 我可以随时吃”
"Yeah, I could eat. I could always eat."
该死的混蛋
Fucking asshole.
看这两位小天使
Look at those two angels, huh?
-是呀 我认识他们 -对呀
-Yeah, I know them. - Yeah.
-嗯 -你陪伴他们走上学的路不是吗？
- Mm-hmm. - You walk them to school, don't you?
-是 我知道他们是谁 -噢 天哪
- Yeah, I know who they are. - Oh, my God.
-她也太可爱了吧 -看这卷发
- She's so cute. - Look. Look at those curls.
我曾带他们去看《破铜烂铁》外百老汇音乐剧
We took them to see Stomp Off-Broadway.
-他们炒鸡欢快 -噢 天啊
- They went crazy! - Oh, my God.
我超爱《破铜烂铁》
I love Stomp.
《破铜烂铁》是什么？那是什么？
What's Stomp? What is that?
它一直都是最棒的音乐剧
It's the greatest musical of all time.
是的 在这个剧中演员们表演敲打 比如敲打垃圾桶
Yeah, it's, like, that show where people play the drums on, like, garbage cans
再比如敲扫帚
and, like, tap with broomsticks.
-敲打家里用的东西 -是的
- Stuff around the house. - Yeah.
我们只觉得烤炉可做英式玛芬
Like, you just see a toaster, we make an English muffin.
他们可以用烤炉敲打出音乐 真不可思议
They-they see a whole song. It's incredible.
据我所知流浪汉靠在地铁里敲打垃圾桶的盖子来索要
I know a homeless guy that plays trash can lids on the subway, for a dollar.
然后在站台被大家冷眼看待
And then he took a shit on the platform.
噢 好吧
Oh. Well, you know.
也不知道他能不能获个托尼奖（音乐剧最高殊荣）什么的
I don't know if he's gonna get a Tony for that, but...
也许他们不断的练习说不定哪天可以带着成人尿布
Maybe if they keep practicing and get an adult diaper,
去百脑汇表演
they can, uh, get to Broadway someday.
好吧
Yeah.
你们的感情是认真的吗？
So, are you guys really serious?
噢
Uh-oh.
是这样的
Well, actually,
我打算在今年的感恩节去波士顿见见他的父母
I'm going up to Boston to meet his parents at Thanksgiving.
-哦 -什么？你要在感恩节的时候去波士顿...
- Oh. - What? You're going to Boston to...for Thanksgiving? To wha...
好吧 那我去哪呀？
Well, where-where am I gonna go?
-你也可以和我一起 一起去 -是呀 我怎么办
-Ah, you'll come. You can come. -Yeah, me, too.
-我们也可以去的 -是呀 我们很乐意你们也去 -噢
-We can all go. - Yeah, we'd love to have you up there. - Oh.
你觉得你会再婚吗？
You think you're gonna get married again?
噢 天啊 我这搞得让我们有点尴尬
Oh, boy, look what I got us into.
Claire
Claire.
好吧 这个 我来
Well, you know what? I'll...
我来回答这个
I'll, uh, I'll answer that, you know?
几个月前 我可能会不想结婚 但
A couple of months ago, I would've said no, but...
嗯 我们能走了吗？
Uh, can we go?
Scott
Scott.
别这么没礼貌
Don't be rude.
我嘛？我不觉得我没礼貌
Me? I'm not being rude.
他一直都在叨逼叨
He's talking the entire time.
他才是没有礼貌的那个
Wha... He's the one being rude.
仅是聊天而已
Was just making conversation.
好吧 那你觉得我还可以说些什么？
Okay, so what did you want to say?
-别扯了 -现在你想怎样
-Cut this shit. - Tell us now.
我想说我觉得我们是时候该离开了 怎么样？
All I wanted to say was I think it's time to go, okay?
我很开心 简直太赞了
I had a great time. This is wonderful.
我认识我们已经情感交流过了
I think we all bonded.
是时候该离开了 好吗？
It's time to leave now, all right?
好吧 我们稍后会去个派对
Well, we're going to a party later,
你可以和我们一起
if you want to come with us.
你不能再让我难堪了
You just can't embarrass me.
好吧 无所谓了 让我们特么赶紧离开这
Sure, whatever. Let's just get the fuck out of here.
他在闹情绪
He's in a good mood.
试着你这辈子都哄着他
Try doing it your entire life.
-今晚我们会玩得很开心的 -好的
-We're gonna have a good night. - Oh, yeah.
不 我们不会的 我很讨厌大学派对
No, we're not. I hate college parties.
你可是从来都没有来过大学派对的
You've never been to a college party.
好了 放飞自我
Come on, just enjoy it.
-放轻松 投入进去 -对的 放轻松
-Relax. Go with it, okay? - Yes, relax.
你修什么专业？
What's your major?
是 嗯 嗯 社会进化学
It's, uh, uh, evolutionary sociology
与生物学有点关系
with-with a splash of bio.
哦 我觉得这个不太可能
Oh. I-I didn't know you could do that.
你可以想特么干什么就干啥什么 这可是大学
Yeah, you can do whatever the fuck you want. It's college.
我喜欢你的纹身
I like your tattoos.
我是个演员 所以我不觉得
I'm an actress, so, like, I don't think
我能纹许多处纹身 因为 比如
I can get that many tattoos, because, like,
如果我有个视镜 白莲花角色
what if I get cast as, like, an angelic role?
那种年轻版的薇诺娜·瑞德
Like, I'm kind of, like, a young Winona Ryder.
我也可以演莎士比亚当年写的巨作
So, like, I could play those parts, and, like, also, like,
中的角色
back when Shakespeare was writing plays, like...
-你觉得如何？ -这是什么呀？
- What do you think? - What is that?
菊花
It's a butthole.
-懂吗？ -我的天啊
- Get it? - Oh, my God.
-嗯 -我们在谈论为什么百分之一的人口
- Uh-huh. - So, we're talking about how the one percent
越来越富有
keeps, like, getting bigger and bigger and bigger,
贫富悬殊越来越严重
and the wealth inequality is just out of control,
而我们不能再继续以这种方式走资本主义道路
and we can't continue with capitalism this way.
是的 我已经厌烦了这种无意义的竞争
Yeah, I'm s... I'm sick of the rat race.
是这样的
Yeah, no, exactly.
那“美国梦”会是神马样子？
Like, what happened to the American dream?
据我所知 现在已经是“美国噩梦”
I know. It's like an American nightmare now.
-对 -是吧
- Oh, my... Yeah, exa... - Right?
-拿过来 太爽了 -哇 爽
- Bring it... Oh, shit! - Oh! Oh, shit!
哇 爽
Oh, shit!
太特么爽了
That was fucking fun.
我当然知道 很爽
I know. It was so fun.
是呀 我觉得
Yeah, like, I feel like,
我觉得我头一次可以这般融入进去
I feel like I kind of fit in for once, you know?
第一次感受到不是所有人都讨厌我
And not everybody hated me for the first time.
你可以常来呀
You should come here.
是吗？ 你觉得我有机会可以进入到这样的一个地方吗？
Yeah? You think I can get into a place like this?
我的意思是 你仅需要高分的成绩
I mean, you'd need a good GPA.
好吧 我可没有考过高分
Yeah, well, I don't have a good one of those.
我甚至高中都没毕业
I-I didn't even graduate high school.
不是得高中毕业才可以读大学吗？
Don't you have to graduate high school to go to college?
是的 不过现在着手去做为时不晚
Yeah, but it's not, like, too late to do that.
好吧 尽管这样 我还是觉得自己年纪有些大
All right, even so, you know, I-I'm a little too old.
你懂吗 我看起来就像个缉毒警察
I'd look like a narc, you know?
在角落里一呆很异类
I would look creepy in the corner.
每个人都觉得 “这家伙在这干嘛”
Everybody'd be like, "What's that guy doing here?"
这里的每个人年纪都不小
Everybody here is so old.
好吧 我就是个煞笔 好吗 Claire？
All right, well, I'm fucking stupid, Claire, okay?
你想让我这样说吗？
Is that what you want me to say?
我无法集中精力 我无法安静的坐着 是吗？
I can't pay attention. I can't sit still, okay?
我是个煞笔 我是个蠢货
I'm stupid. I'm a dumb idiot.
我还得比其他人努力十倍
I would have to work ten times harder than those people.
然后还特么被嘲笑
And everybody would fucking make fun of me,
我可不想再尝试一次 所以 不想
and I'm not ready to deal with that again, all right? So, no.
所以 就这样嘛？
So, that's it?
啊？
Huh?
这就是你长久以来觉得
That's how long you're gonna think about
上大学的样子吗？
going to college for?
40秒步行
I mean, that was, like, a 40-second walk.
可以有很多想法 你不觉得吗？
Uh, that's a lot of consideration, don't you think?
好吧
Okay.
-你的路程呵 -那是
-It's your journey. - Indeed.
我们进入正题
Now, let's get down to brass tacks, all right?
关于Ray的出现我们该怎么办？
W-What are we gonna do about Ray?
-什么意思？ -别装傻
- What do you mean? - Don't act stupid.
我的意思是 我们该怎么做
I mean, h-how are we gonna, you know,
使他与老妈分手？
get Mom to break up with him?
我觉得他不错
I think he seems fine.
-你觉得他不错？ -你有什么想法？
-You think he's fine? - What do you want?
那是老妈的选择 我们无权过问
It's Mom's choice to make. We don't need to get involved.
好 我知道 但我们仍需要保护她
Yeah, I know, but we should still protect her.
她不能就这样继老爸后
She can't just be with
下一个男人就随便好上了
the first guy she's been with since Dad.
她该好好挑选下
She got to, like, peruse some dick.
老妈不需要好好挑选下
Mom doesn't need to peruse dick.
-你知道她需要的 -我觉得老妈很开心
-You know she needs to. - I think she seems happy.
你想让她与N多人开车吗？
You want her to have sex with a ton of people?
不 但 也许吧
No, but, yeah, kind of.
-我的意思是...-真恶心
- I mean... - That's gross.
可是 如果你知道在最开始的时候 情形会往坏处发展
Well, if you knew something was bad before it even started,
假设你有机会去阻止 难道你不会去阻止吗？
wouldn't you stop it if you had the chance?
就像把希特勒扼杀在摇篮中一样 你懂的
It's like that whole baby Hitler thing, you know?
如果你有机会在希特勒长大前 杀掉摇篮中的希特勒
If you had the chance to kill baby Hitler before it grew up,
你会去做吗？
you do it?
你难道不会扼制它 让它完全完全死掉
Wouldn't you strangle it until its eyes popped out?
所以 Ray的“摇篮中的希特勒”
So, Ray's baby Hitler?
是呀 目前 他就是
Yeah. In this situation, he is, yeah.
他就是“摇篮中的希特勒”
He's baby Hitler.
你想帮我杀了这个“摇篮中的希特勒”吗？
So, do you want to help me kill baby Hitler?
好吧 你全对 Scott 你全对
Okay, you're right, Scott. You're right.
-明天见 -Claire
-I'll see you tomorrow. - Claire!
Claire
Claire!
告诉你 Claire是真的
Tell you, Claire really seems like
很喜欢大学生活
she's enjoying school, you know?
是呀
Yeah.
她正当年呀
She's just blossoming.
是呀
Yeah.
她似乎觉得她可以拥有这个世界
Girl just seems like she could take on the world.
我和你讲
I'll tell you,
无论你之前怎样培养过她 你做的太赞了
whatever you did with her, you did it right.
也可以培养下Scott
Dump some of that on Scott, you know?
你觉得他的纹身餐厅的想法如何？
What do you think about his tattoo restaurant idea?
我觉得不怎么样
I think it's terrible.
纹身就像一个医疗疗程
Getting a tattoo is like, uh... it's a medical procedure.
你肯定不想看着病
You don't want to go to the hospital
吃着晚饭
and order supper, you know?
我就是欣赏他有远大的理想 不过他也太跳脱了
I just love that he has big dreams, but he's just so lost.
无论我怎么努力给他输入正能量 他就是
I mean, no matter how much I try to fill him with good energy, he just...
他毫无自信
he's got no self-esteem.
他的前途可堪呀
He's really going nowhere.
别这样责备自己
Don't be so hard on yourself.
科学家们从事这类研究很久
Scientists have been doing studies.
他们觉得很多东西都是来自遗传
They say a lot of this stuff is genetic.
你从你的祖父母们继承了这个
You know, you inherit it from your grandparents.
所以责任归于他们
So blame them.
我们走
Let's go.
如果有人看见我们
Right. If anybody sees us
或者你听见警笛再或者情况不妙 你给我传信息“你醒着呢吗？”
or you hear sirens or anything bad, you text me, "You up?"
我可以发些其他的东西给你吗？
Could I just text you something else?
这个感觉有点像我找你约炮...
That sounds like I'm trying to bang you, kind of.
-按照我说的做 -好吧
-Just do it. -Fine.
-好吧 -我们走
-Fine. -Let's go.
-我们出发 -等一下
-Let's roll. -Hold on.
好 我们出发
All right, let's go.
一切顺利 兄弟
Good luck, homey.
爱你 Scott
Love you, Scott.
我去
Oh, shit.
玩真的
This is real.
太赞了
Yes! All right.
你死定了
You're dead.
你在干嘛？
What's going on?!
卧槽
What the fuck?
-你谁呀？ -你不该在这的
-Who are you?! -You're not supposed to be here.
你在说什么？这是我的店！
What are you talking about?! It's my store!
你在和谁讲话？
Who are you talking to?
-他是谁呀？ -快进屋
-Who is that?! -Go back inside.
-快进屋 -什么？不需要你告诉我进屋
-Go back inside! -What? Don't tell me to go back inside!
我在解决这事！
I'm handling this!
不错 不行 不错
Yes. No. Yes.
不行 不错 不错 不行
No. Yes. Yes. No.
赶快从我的店里滚出去！
Get the fuck out of my store!
-我不想伤害你 -滚出去
-I just don't want to hurt you, okay? -Get out!
-我只是...-不能再容忍你们这样了
-I just... -You're not doing this again, okay?!
-这已经是第三次了 -你们够了！
-This is the third time! -Enough of you guys!
-一年里三次 -妈蛋的
-Third time this year! -Shit! Shit!
-滚出去 -靠
-Get out! -What the hell?
-放开我 -今天绝对不行
-Get off me! -Not today!
今天绝对不行 今天是“反抗日”（Alan Moskowitz所制作的电影多为人类反抗电影）
Not today! Today is Alan Moskowitz's day!
这个漂亮的妹妹是谁？
Well, who's the pretty lady?
嗨 安吉丽娜朱莉
Hello, Angelina Jolie.
-这怎么锁了！ -钥匙在哪？
- Yo, it's locked! - Where are the keys?
我们都把钥匙放在柜台
We left the keys on the counter.
为什么你把门锁了？
Why'd you lock the door?
那是我不想让其他人进来
Because I didn't want anybody to come in, man.
不能再容忍你们这样对我了！
You're not gonna do this to me again!
决不可以在我的店里再有这种事
Not in my store!
-我们可从来没来过这呀！-妈蛋的
-We've never been here before! -Shit!
我绝不轻饶
I'm standing my ground!
卧槽
Fuck.
靠
Shit!
“你醒着呢吗”“你醒着呢吗”“你醒着呢吗”
"You up? You up? You up?"
-现在怎么办？ -别出声 别出声
-What's happening? -Be quiet. Be quiet.
别出声 别出声
Be quiet. Be quiet.
“想约炮吗”“想约炮吗”“想约炮吗”“想约炮吗”
"Want to fuck? Want to fuck? Want to fuck? Want to fuck?"
“想约炮吗”
"Do you want to fuck?
想约炮吗？ 想约炮吗？
Do you want to fuck? Do you want to fuck?
好吧 Igor
Okay, right, Igor.
接电话 Igor
Answer the phone, Igor.
快接呀 快接呀 快接呀
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
不 不 不
No. No. No. No. No.
Scott
Scott.
快点关掉
Shut off your ringers!
该死的
Goddamn it.
嗨 Oscar 我是Scott
Hey, Oscar, it's, uh, Scott.
我很想知道
I was just, uh, wondering if, uh, you know,
你那事干完了嘛
you're almost done with that thing.
我们需要钥匙
We need those keys.
卧槽
Fuck that!
靠
Holy shit!
快点 Igor 快点！
Come on, Igor! Come on! Come on!
盗贼在里面
Um, the robbers are inside!
举起手来！
Hands in the air!
店里那个女人有枪
The lady inside's got a gun.
趴在地上
Get down on the ground!
别动
Do not move!
为什么你们要抢劫药店？
Why would you rob a pharmacy?
我没有在抢劫药店
I wasn't robbing a pharmacy, okay?
我只是个望风的
I was the lookout, for your information.
望风也是犯罪
The lookout is also committing a crime.
你脑子进水了吗？
Are you fucking crazy?
听着 这都是Ray的错
Look, it's all Ray's fault, okay?
他想踢我出局
He's trying to kick me out.
我恐慌了然后做了个错误的决定
So I panicked and made a bad decision, okay?
我也会犯错的！
I'm only human!
错误的决定？这可是重罪
A bad decision? That's a felony.
那又怎样？
Yeah, so?
我根本就没进去
I didn't even, I didn't even go inside, all right?
我与此事无关
Uh, it's not...I'm untouchable.
我什么都没做
I didn't do anything, all right?
都是Ray的错
Uh, i-it's Ray, okay?
我知道他心存不轨
He... I-I know he's up to something.
-他就是想抹去老爸的存在 -你就不想让老妈幸福生活吗？
-He's trying to erase Dad. -Can you just let Mom be happy?
老妈很幸福
She is happy.
只要她离开那个人 老妈会幸福的
Well, she will be, you know, once I get rid of that guy.
他心存不轨 他心存不轨
He's hiding shit, okay? He's hiding shit.
他就是个黄鼠狼 我已经发现他了
He's a weasel. I-I'm onto him.
这就是你为什么不想离家的原因
This is why I didn't want to leave,
你把你的神经质都放在了老妈身上
cause now all your crazy's focused on Mom.
我没做什么神经质的事
I'm not doing anything crazy, okay?
什么都不做才是神经质 我现在要做些什么
Doing nothing would be crazy. I'm doing something, okay?
我要采取行动
I'm taking action!
别去骚扰老妈 你别再这样了
Leave Mom alone. Stop acting like you.
什么意思？
What's that mean?!
你毁掉了我的万圣节派对
You ruined my Halloween party.
我明知故问
You know, you know what? You know what?
去好好享受你的派对 我了解了
Go enjoy your party. I-I got this.
你不了解 别做蠢事
You don't got this. Don't do anything.
我了解了
I got this.
别做蠢事！
Don't do anything!
嗨 Scott 有事吗？
Hey, Scott. What's up?
-嗨 -嗨
-Oh, hi. -Hi.
我就是过来看看孩子们
I, uh... I just came by to say hi to the kids.
他们在吗？
Are-are they around?
噢
Oh.
他们不在家
Well, they're not here.
他们去了他们的奶奶家
They went to their grandma's.
哦
Oh.
你在干嘛呢？
Well, what do you got going on over there?
我在开这瓶红酒
I'm trying to open this bottle of wine,
不过我把这木塞搞坏了
but I think I mangled the cork.
我可以帮忙 想让我帮把手吗？
Oh, well, I could help. You want me to help?
好呀
Yes. Yes.
来吧
Please.
-耶 -好棒
- Yeah! - Yes.
你有好朋友来拜访吗？
So, uh, do you have a friend coming over or something?
不
Oh, no.
不 我自己小酌下
No, I just need some mommy time.
当她们的孩子被送走 妈妈们需要小酌下的
Sometimes, mommies need to drink when the kids are away.
我可以一起吗？
Oh, well, could I hang?
我也想小酌下
I-I could use some mommy time.
当然可以 不过你到了可以饮酒的年龄了吗？
Sure, but are you old enough to drink?
当然 我已经到了可饮酒的年龄 我还想吸点
Yeah, I'm old enough. I just... I'd rather smoke.
不介意我在这吸大麻吧？
Do you mind if I smoke in here?
不介意
Oh, no. No.
让我们嗨起来
Let's crack some windows.
-今天可是周二 -确定吗？
-It's Tuesday. -Really?
Ray不喜欢我吸大麻
Cause Ray hates when I smoke weed.
我不喜欢Ray
Mm. Well, I hate Ray.
太赞了
Awesome.
-嗯 -你知道嘛...
-Mm. -You know...
你的孩子是我见过
You have the sweetest,
最讨喜最可爱的
most adorable kids I've ever met in my life.
我简直不敢相信是Ray的孩子
Like, I can't believe they came out of Ray.
我懂
I know.
你知道吗？
And you know what?
关于Ray
You know what the thing is about Ray?
我从来没在孩子们的面前说过他的一句坏话
I never say a bad word about him in front of the kids,
做这事炒鸡难的 因为他就是个混蛋
which is very difficult because he's a cunt.
是的 我可以想象
Yeah, I-I can imagine.
我不是他的孩子 所以来说他的坏话吧
Well, I'm not one of your kids, so have at it.
都说出来吧 都告诉我
Let it all out. Tell me everything.
你知道嘛 他一直都不想
Do you know he is fighting to
抚养他的孩子
actively not have custody of his kids?
-你居然接受？ -是呀
-You can do that? -Yeah.
-简直不可想象 -我懂
-That's insane. -I know.
居然有人不想和你的孩子在一起？
Who wouldn't want to hang with your kids?
谁不想跟那些孩子们一起玩啊
Who wouldn't want to hang out with those kids?
什么样的怪物会不想跟那些孩子们一起玩啊
What monster wouldn't want to hang out with those kids?
每一秒都那么美好
Every second!
你姑娘那天唱了首歌
Your daughter sang the other day.
她唱了啥
What did she sing?
俄克拉荷马里的什么吧
Something from, like, Oklahoma! or something,
虽然我讨厌那破玩意 但是我他妈的爱死她的歌声了
and-and I hate that shit, and I fucking loved it.
她真是个小天使
She's such a little angel.
- 嗯  - 我还以为她是个机器人什么的
- Mm.  - I-I thought she was a robot for, like,
最初跟她玩的那几天的时候
the first couple days I was hanging out with her.
我说吧  她真的好完美啊
I know. She's so perfect.
什么品种的傻逼啊
What a fucking putz.
嗯 所以他只想在
Yeah, so he only wants to see them
周三晚饭和周日的时候探望他们
on Wednesday night for dinner and Sunday.
- 你不能这样随便挑的  - 还有
-  You can't just pick and choose.  - And, uh...
对啊 你不能挑的
No, you can't.
把孩子当什么了 橄榄球季票么
What are your kids, the NFL package?
- 等等 对啊  - 对吧
- Wait, you're only... Yeah.  - Yeah.
不过你也不会想要孩子的监护权的
But why would you want your kids, really·,
尤其现在你连自己的住所都没有还睡在消防队里
if you don't have an apartment and you sleep at the firehouse?
就是
I mean, you...
无法理喻
Unbelievable.
什么样的成年男人
What kind of a grown man
在史泰登岛住不起自己的屋子
can't afford his own apartment in Staten Island?
真他妈废物
Fucking loser.
他把我们所有的钱都赌输了
He lost all our money gambling.
他无家可归 身无分文 还是个不负责的孩子爹
He is homeless, he's penniless, and he's a deadbeat dad.
你妈为啥跟他在一起啊
What is your mom doing with him?
你懂得 我妈17年都没对象
You know, my mom hasn't gotten laid in 17 years,
所以我觉得她的标准相当低了
so I think her bar is pretty low.
真的  好吧
Really? Yeah.
虽然不想承认 但是他床上倒是真不错
He's good in bed, I hate to say it.
好吧
All right.
好吧 我倒不是真的需要知道这事
Well, I didn't really need to know that.
嗯啊
Yeah.
他有个漂亮的鸡巴
He's got a beautiful cock.
这是 他唯一的优点了
I mean, it's the... it's his only attribute.
那个大粗鸡巴让我
That big thick cock kept me in it
多跟了他8年
for eight years longer than I should have stayed.
这是事实
It's a fact.
我就知道我能闻出来
I knew I smelled you.
- Scott你搞什么鬼  - 啥
- The fuck, Scott?  - What?
啥  你现在开始监视我了吗
Huh? What, are you spying on me now?
- 你是夏威夷神探吗  - 啥
- You Magnum, P.I.?  - What?
跟你妈说我无家可归
Telling your mom that I'm homeless?
说我是个废物 你觉得很搞笑么
You think it's funny to tell her that I'm a loser?
你在说啥 不搞笑啊 啥啊
What are you talking... No. What?
什么叫我在说啥
What do you mean, what am I talking about?
你跟那谁  你去找我前妻唠嗑去了
You've been speak... You talking to my ex-wife?
额 是啊  她其实是个很好的人啊
Uh, yeah. She's actually a really nice person.
- 哦 是吗  那你咋不娶她啊  - 啊
- Oh, is she? Why don't you marry her?  - Yeah.
你咋不娶了她再看看会发生啥
Why don't you marry her and see what the fuck happens?
嘿 我只是想保护我妈不被你伤害 好吧
Hey, I'm just trying to protect my mom from you, okay?
你他妈是个神经病
You're a fucking psychopath.
- 哦 我是神经病  - 是
- Oh, I'm a psychopath?  - Yeah.
我对你简直是不能再好了
I've been nothing but nice to you!
我努力指引你
I tried giving you direction.
然而你却一直他妈的忙着飞你的叶子
You're too busy smoking your fucking weed.
你除了一直在迫害我
And all you've been doing is trying to destroy
和Margie的感情以外没有干别的
everything that I have with Margie.
因为你他妈的是个废物啊 弟弟
Because you're a fucking loser, dude!
你是 你是个无可救药的赌徒
You're a, you're a degenerate gambler
你都 你都50多了 还压在喷气机队上
in your-your mid-50s, who bets on the Jets.
额 你难道这么多年赌出来不长记性么
Uh, who... Have you not learned anything about betting?
- 喷气机队会赢回来的  - 不 不可能的
- The Jets are gonna come back!  - No, they're not!
他们挑了三个种子选手
They got three number one fucking picks!
他们永远赢不回来的  他们永远赢不回来的
They're never gonna come back! They're never gonna come back!
我在努力给你妈一个好的生活
I'm trying to give your mother a good life!
我  没 你没有好吧  你就是坨屎 弟弟
I... No, you're not, okay? You're a piece of shit, dude.
你他妈吸毒上瘾 然而我是屎？
You're a fucking drug addict! I'm a piece of shit?
是啊 你就是坨屎  我是他妈废物
Yeah, you're a piece of shit! I'm a fucking loser?
你是我这辈子他妈的碰到的最大的废物
You're the biggest loser I ever met in my fucking life!
- 哦 这样  果然你最懂啊  - 是的就这样
- Oh, really? You should know.  - Yeah! Yeah!
因为你身边都是这种人
You surround yourself with them.
- 哦 真的  你来啊  - 哦真的
- Oh, yeah? Why don't you try me?  - Oh, really?
你来啊 来啊 来啊 来啊
Why don't you try me? Yeah, yeah, yeah...
那接下来可不会按你想象的一样的
This ain't gonna go how you think it's gonna go.
所以你最好从我眼前  靠玩真的
So why don't you get the fuck out of my... Really?
- 操你大爷  - 你他妈敢打我
- Fucking asshole.  - Throw a fucking punch at me?
- 就敢打  - 啥  你能不能冷静一下
- Oh, yeah.  - Huh? You gonna cool off?
- 过来啊你个混蛋  - 你能不能冷静一下
- Come here, cocksucker.  - You gonna cool off?
我他妈的帮你冷静冷静
I'll fucking cool you off.
Yeah, I'll fucking cool you off!
嘿 你现在冷静下来了
Hey, you cool off now?
这可是你自找的
You're in there 'cause of your own actions!
你在逗我吗
Are you kidding me?!
我要告诉我妈你要淹死我
I'm gonna tell my mom you tried to drown me.
在这种小破水池子里
In an aboveground pool?
你他妈至少2米4好吧
You're, like, fucking eight feet tall.
我爸不在这你算是捡着了 他非打死你不可
You're lucky my dad isn't here. He would kick your ass.
噢 真的么 你猜怎么着 我认识你爹  好吧
Oh, yeah? Well, guess what, I knew your dad. Okay?
- 所以呢  - 所以我见过他几次
- Yeah?  - Yeah, I crossed paths with him a number of times.
你猜怎么着  他比你还混球
And you know what? He was even a bigger asshole than you are!
好了 就这样吧 停下
All right, that's it, that's it.
你赢不了 别打了
It's over. It's over.
You like that? You like that?
你想这样  你想这样
- 天啊  - 你大爷的
- Jesus.  - Fucking asshole.
好啦 认输吧 认输吧
Come on, tap out! Tap out!
- 操你大爷的  就不  - 放开我  放开我
- Fuck you! No!  - Get me out! Let me out!
- 不 就不  - 放开我
- No! No!  - Let me out!
- 我的天啊  - 放开我
- Oh, my God!  - Get me out!
你俩什么毛病啊
What's the matter with you?!
他是神经病
He's a psycho.
不是
No.
- 我们就是在聊天  - 聊啥啊
- We're just talking.  - About what?
- 他跟你说的那些关于我的假话  - 他就是个畜生
- About him telling you lies about me.  - He's an animal.
他抱起我然后扔到了泳池里
He picked me up and he threw me in the pool.
- 他必须得走人  - 不 我要你走人  现在就走
- All right? He has to go.  - No, I need you to go. Now.
啥  为啥是我 他先起的头
What? Why-why me? He-he's the one who started it.
那就对了 赶紧滚吧
Yeah, that's right. Get the hell out of here.
顺便赶紧找个工作好好过日子得了
And get a job and a life while you're at it.
你吃白食的日子到头了
Your freeloading days are over.
你 也是  滚蛋
You, too. Get going.
等会 我干了啥啊
Wait, what did I do?
你对我儿子动手了
You put your hands on my son!
你不尊重我的家庭
You're not respecting my family!
你是个畜生
You're an animal!
稍等  听我说
Look, okay, just listen.
- 先冷静一下  - 我不需要冷静一下
- Just calm down.  - I don't have to calm down!
你打了我的儿子
What are... You're attacking my son!
你还满嘴胡说八道
And you're, and you're making up lies!
你骗我让我觉得你是个好人
You made... You tricked me into thinking you're a good guy.
你不是好人
You're not a good guy.
- 好吧  - 你他吗就是个小人
- Right. Mm-hmm.  - You're a fucking small guy.
Margie Margie 你听我解释
Margie, Margie, just let me explain this to you.
- 你听我解释好吧  - 你管不了我
- Just let me talk to you, okay?  - You are not in control of me.
好的 好的 听我说好吧
Okay, okay, listen, all right?
你看到的只是事情的一部分
Okay, you don't have all the information you need.
Scott在作妖
All right? Scott is acting out
因为他不敢前进
'cause he's afraid to move on with his life.
跟波士顿红袜队
It's no different than when the Boston Red Sox
终于赢了世界大赛是一个原理的
finally won a World Series, okay?
- 哦 我的天  - 他们需要达到那种状态
- Oh, my God.  - They had, they had to get to a point
- 那种相信自己 好吧  - 你可闭嘴吧
- where-where they believed, okay?  - Just shut up.
- 所有  - 你他妈闭嘴
- All-all...  - Shut the fuck up.
我就问了他一个问题 然后他就翻脸了
All I did was just ask him a question, and he flipped out.
所有我就把他放在温和的水里
So I put him in the water, which is soft.
我缓解这个危机
I diffused the situation.
我的培训里都有这些的
It was what-what m-my training's all about.
我 我真的是缓解了这个危机
I-I wa... I was totally diffusing the situation.
你有闭嘴的时候吗
Do you ever shut up?
你他妈有闭嘴的时候吗
Do you ever just shut the fuck up?
你就在那叭叭叭叭
You just talk and you talk and you talk,
自己都不知道自己在讲啥
and you don't know what you're saying.
狗屁不通
It makes no sense.
感觉就像你收集了各种
It's like you picked up all these little pieces
各样的信息
of information from all over.
全是断片的  毫无意义的
They don't make any sense. They're fragments.
无意的 废话
No sense. Nonsense.
我现在不讲了
I-I'm not talking.
我忍了这么多了 我不管了
I've had it up to here. I'm done.
你俩 滚犊子
Both of you, get your shit out of here.
Margie.
操
Oh, fuck.
Well...
那么
那么 现在我们去哪儿
Well, where do we go now?
你问我干啥
What are you asking me for?
你捅的娄子 你个蠢货
You created this whole mess, you fucking schmuck.
嘿 哥们
Hey, man.
你生我气么
Are you mad at me?
我  当然没有啊
Me? No, of course not.
那你生我气么
Are-are you mad at me?
我啊
I mean,
- 没生但是  - 他们
- no, but...  - Are they...
他们有在问我么
Are they asking questions about me?
我不会告密的 哥们
I'm not gonna snitch on you, man.
但是吧 就是 我跟他们说什么啊
But at the same time, like, what am I gonna say to them?
你是那个望风人 但是没望风
You were the lookout that didn't look out.
额 好吧 我其实想问你
Um, well, I've been meaning to ask you.
介于你现在住这儿了 额 我在想
Um... you know, since you're in here, uh, well, I was wondering
你介不介意我在你家住一段时间
if you wouldn't mind me staying at your house for a little bit.
你来就是为了问我这个
You came up here to ask me that?
- 我也是来看你的啊  - 你来
- I also came to see you.  - You came...
不你不是来看我的  你是来问这个的
No, you didn't come to see me. You came to ask me that.
然后 不你不能住我家
And, no, you can't stay at my house.
抱歉 但是我没地方去了哥们
I'm sor... I have nowhere to go, bro.
- 我家挺吓人的  - 我妈把 我妈
- My house is frightening, dude.  - My mom kicked, my mom
- 把我赶出来了  - 你他妈生活怎么搞得
- kicked me out.  - The fuck are you doing with your life?
大老远开车过来就是为了问我
Drive all the way down here just to ask me
能不能住我家
if you can stay at my house.
- 不是  - 对 你根本不爱我
- No, I-I...  - No, you don't love me.
我爱你啊
I do love you.
抱歉 我 我 你说得对
I'm sorry. I-I... You're right.
我不应该提的 抱歉
I shouldn't have asked. I'm sorry.
你知道嘛 我正好想让你帮个忙
And you know what? I need you to do me a favor.
说吧哥们 啥都行
Anything, bro. Just ask.
你得帮我喂猫 行吧
You got to feed my cat, all right?
喂大概三到五个月把
For the next three to five months.
有其他别的我能做的么
Is there anything else I could do?
因为我有点对猫过敏
'Cause I'm-I'm kind of allergic to cats.
你可得照顾好我家小糖糖
You better look out for Sprinkles,
因为我可是一直在照顾你
because I'm looking out for you, all right?
听你的
You got it.
听好了 哥们
And, listen, man.
我要你花时间陪着小糖糖
I need you to spend time with Sprinkles.
我不要你只是
I don't want you just
到那儿喂完食就跑了
going in there, feeding him and running out.
你得到那儿 挠他的肚子
You got to go in there, scratch his belly.
你得告诉他我想他 过不久就回去见他
You tell him I miss him and I'll see him soon.
好的
Right.
额 弟兄们都怎么样
Um, how, uh, how are the boys?
Igor和Richie在里面过得好么
How's Igor and Richie doing in there?
我跟你讲 我还没见到Richie
I'll tell you right now. I haven't seen Richie.
Igor呢
Igor?
哥么 朝右看
Bro, look to your right.
那是Carla
That's Carla.
Carla
Carla.
卧槽 别开玩笑
Holy shit! Get the...
哥们 她她么是活的
Bro, she's fucking real.
她她么是一个大活人
She's fucking real.
她她么是活的 卧槽
She's fucking real. Holy shit.
哟 大美女啊
Yo. She's hot, man.
他说的都是真的
He was telling the truth the entire time.
- 真好啊  - 是啊
- Good for him, man.  - I know.
- 酷毙了  - 是啊
- That's awesome.  - Yeah.
嘿 说你呢
Hey, you.
你他妈的在这干啥呢
What the hell are you doing there?
哦 抱歉 我以为这是我家
Oh, I'm sorry. I thought this was my house.
从我家后院滚出去
Get out of my backyard!
滚出去
Get the hell out of here!
刚刚做的还是蛮开心啊
I'm really glad we did that.
真的很舒服
It was really nice.
我也是
Me, too.
碉堡了
That was awesome.
嗯我好想你的
Yeah. I missed you.
是吧  我也好想你来着
Oh, yeah? I missed you, too.
就像从前一样的
Just like, uh, old times.
我想我的朋友们了
I miss all my friends, you know.
鲨鱼先生  怪骷髅先生
Mr. Shark, Mr. Weird Skeleton.
嗯 他们也想你了
Well, they missed you, too.
他们也想你了
They missed you, too.
嘿 我现在出了点状况
Hey, I, uh... I'm in a bit of a situation.
我能在你这儿待几天么
You think I could stay here for a few days?
你在说啥
What are you talking about?
说起来挺丢人的
Well, it's silly.
我跟Ray大吵了一架
Me and Ray got into this big fight,
然后碰巧我妈看见了 然后她就吼了我俩
and then my mom caught us, and she just started yelling at us.
然后就把我俩赶出来了  她有点不太对劲
And she threw us out, so... She kind of lost her mind.
所以你就来我这儿了
Is that why you're here right now?
不是
No.
你干我就是为了有地方住
Did you just fuck me for shelter?
不 我不是为了有地方住干的你
No, I didn't fuck you for shelter.
我啥都没干
Uh, I-I-I didn't do anything.
啥  我啥都 我就 我就想要个待的地方
What? I didn't... I just... I just need a place to stay.
我的天
Oh, God.
老哥 我们还要吵多少次
Dude, dude, how many times we got to do this?
你在说啥 我就是想
What do you mean? I-I just want to...
我就是需要  需要几周而已
I just need... It's just for a couple weeks.
没啥大不了的
It's not that big of a deal.
几周  你刚才还说几天
A few weeks? You just said a few days.
- 额 也可能是几个月  - 几个月
- Uh, or a couple months. It's...  - Months?
我在思考人生
I'm figuring my stuff out.
未来不确定的
I don't know the future.
哦 我的天 你
Oh, my God, you...
走你
There you go.
- 嘿 干嘛  - 我不会再让我自己
- What the... Hey.  - I'm not going to let myself
生你的气了 不过我告诉你
be upset by you, but I'm gonna tell you something.
你让我觉得自己像个疯子
You make me feel so crazy.
不过我不会让我自己变成疯子的
I'm not gonna let myself be crazy now,
但是你让我觉得自己像个疯子
but you make me feel crazy!
你自己就是疯子然后
You are so crazy that you make
你还会把你周围所有人都逼疯
everyone around you feel fucking crazy.
遇见你的人 那些普通人
The people meet you, and they're normal people,
他们跟你呆久了 就他妈的变成了
and then they hang out with you, and then they're fucking
闪灵里的Jack Nicholson一样
Jack Nicholson in The Shining or something.
好吧 好吧
Okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
我要保持禅境  我要去冥想
I got to stay Zen. I got to meditate.
我现在就在冥想 而你需要滚蛋
I'm meditating right now, and you got to go.
- 啥 啥  - 没错 带走你的破烂
- What? What?  - Yeah, here's your shit.
好吧Okay.
保持冷静
Staying calm.
你得走了  现在就走
You got to leave. It's time to go.
可是
Well...
滚蛋
Get out.
可是我没地方去啊
Well, I don't have anywhere to go.
那我就不管了
It's not my problem anymore.
谢谢你来的这一炮
Thank you for the sex.
在你张嘴说话之前还是蛮美好的
It was wonderful until you started talking.
You got to go.
你走吧
我能睡你弟弟那屋嘛
Could I sleep in your brother's room?
不行
No.
可是他有上下铺喂
But he has bunk beds.
他才14岁
He's 14 years old.
嘿 哟 Dougie 我能睡你屋嘛
Hey, yo, Dougie, can I crash in your room?
没门老哥
That's not happening, bro.
老天爷
Jesus Christ.
操
Fuck.
嘿 你知道Ray Bishop在哪儿吗
Hey, do you know where Ray Bishop is?
他在后面  跟我来
He's in the back. Come with me.
那你下次能不能先戴面具
How about next time you put your mask on
然后再下车
before we get off the rig?
我得在门口等你一分钟
I mean, I'm standing at that front door for a minute
- 什么鬼啊   - 我让他这么干的
- waiting for you. What the hell?   - I told him to.
Always with the backhanded compliment.
总是阴阳怪气的夸人
你为啥就不能
Why can't you just, you know,
说两句好听的
at least say the nice thing and then...
- 跟你 给句好话就不错了 - 好吧
- Listen, you should be happy with any compliment.  - Okay.
- 这叫建设性意见  - 这叫
- It's constructive criticism.  - It's...
- 就是 总是损人  - 继续
- It just... It's always bad.  - Go ahead.
我更能接受鼓励什么的
I would respond better to encouragement.
我就
I'm just...
那我鼓励你他妈闭嘴吧
I encourage you to shut the fuck up.
他太弱了  他禁不住的
He's soft. He can't take it.
- 你说的的  - 他一肚子情感
- You're right.  - He's an emotional eater.
可不 这一代的毛病就是这个
Well, that's the problem with this generation, man.
禁不起批评
They can't take criticism.
- 他们 可委屈了  - 我知道
- They get, they get all-all upset.  - I know.
嘿 我不能代表我们这一代所有人 好吧
Hey, I'm not a whole generation, all right?
我就 我就是个普通爷们  一个有感情的普通爷们
I'm just, I'm just a man. A man with feelings.
- 哦 我的天  - 呕 呕
- Oh, my God.  - Aw! - Aw!
现在你让我变成坏人了
Now you're making me look bad.
- 你这算爷们  - 停一下  现在你让我变成坏人了
- You're a man?  - Now you're making me look bad. Stop.
Ray
Ray.
嘿 Ray
Hey, Ray.
哦 老天爷
Oh, Jesus Christ.
你在这干啥
What are you doing here?
就 我没地方可以去了 好吧
Look, uh, I-I don't have anywhere else to go, all right?
我没有办法了 所以
I'm out of options, so...
我为啥要管
Why would I care?
我很抱歉 呃
I'm sorry. Like, uh-uh...
找个树底下躺着去  我不管
Go sleep under a tree. I don't care.
你知道你让我失去了什么吗  你知道吗
Do you have any idea what you took from me? Do you?
嗯  你采访我前妻采访了60分钟
Huh? You do a 60-minute interview with my ex-wife
去了解了我是个什么样的人
to find out what kind of guy I am?
你觉得她准备说啥
What do you think she was gonna say?
- 我不知道啊  - 顺便
- I don't know. I...  - By the way,
我不是个赌徒 我是做短线投资的
I'm not a gambler, okay? I day-trade.
我不知道有啥区别啊
I don't know the difference.
那你张嘴之前应该先去弄明白有啥区别啊
You should've found out before you shot your mouth off.
我知道你吸了不少大麻 但是你不蠢
I know you smoke a lot of weed, but you're not dumb.
你知道你他妈的自己在干啥
You knew what the fuck you were doing.
你去找了世界上最恨我的人
You went to the person that hates me the most
得到了我所能得到的最差的评价
to get the worst review you could possibly get.
你咋不来这而问问这些人呢
Why didn't you come down here and ask these guys
问问他们觉得我怎么样
what they thought of me?
你有想过这么做么
Did you ever think of doing that?
抱歉  你说的对 你说的对
I'm sorry. You're right. You're right.
- 额 我不应该  - 你才没有歉意
- Uh, I shouldn't have done...  - You're not sorry
否则你就不会那么干了  所以现在呢
or you wouldn't have done it. So now what?
现在你没地方住了
Now you don't have a place to stay?
你现在跑到这里来瞪着你那水灵灵的大眼睛
So now you come down here with your little puppy dog look
然后我就会于心不忍么
on your face, and I'm supposed to feel bad?
但是 我知道
Look, all I know is,
如果你不对我好 我妈会恨你一辈子
if you're not nice to me, then my mom will hate you forever
而且永远不会原谅你
and she'll never forgive you.
真的  这种情感牌你也敢打
Really? You're gonna play that card?
这 这牌超好用的
It's a, it's a pretty good card.
而且我就这一张牌了
It's all I got.
Ray
Ray.
嘿 Ray
Hey, Ray.
Raymond
Raymond.
Ray
Ray!
干啥
What?
嘿 我睡不着
Hey, I can't sleep.
我 我从来没睡过这么早
I-I never go to sleep this early.
哦 那 你知道你该干啥吗
Oh. Well, you know what you should do?
你该闭他妈的嘴
You should shut the fuck up.
睡觉去
Go to sleep.
谢了
Thanks.
睡不着
Can't go to sleep.
你咋不把你的大麻蘸到奈奎尔里面
Why don't you dip your weed in NyQuil,
你个吸毒成瘾的货
you fucking drug addict?
嘿  我要做什么
Hey, w-what do I do?
做你平时做的事  原地不动呆着
Do what you always do. Sit there and do nothing.
嘿 上厕所怎么走啊
Hey. Where do you go to the bathroom around here?
小号的话 直走
Well, number one, down there.
大号的花 街对过的唐恩都乐
Number two, Dunkin' Donuts across the street.
今天过得开心点哦
Have a wonderful day, man.
哦 谢了
Oh, thanks.
大个  睡得咋样啊
How'd you sleep, big man?
我听说你是Stan的孩子
I hear you're Stan's kid.
他是个勇敢的人  很荣幸认识你
He was a brave man. It's an honor to meet you.
谢了 大哥
Thanks, man.
很 也很荣幸认识你
It's a, it's an honor to meet you, too.
虽然我什么也没做
I-I didn't do anything, though.
你觉得你什么都没做
You don't think you did?
没做啊
No.
谢谢你的牺牲
I appreciate your sacrifice.
我纹这个身是为了泡妹子
No, I got this one to impress a girl.
噢 结果怎么样
Oh? And how did that work out?
不怎么样
Not good.
- 我们已经结婚18年了  - 喔 你老婆好惨
- We've been married 18 years.  - PAPA: Ooh, poor woman.
- 18年了是吗  - 恭喜
- 18 years, huh?  - Congratulations.
- 谢谢  - 哇哦
- Thank you.  - Wow.
剩下的这些是毛利人的部落图案
The rest I got, you know, Maori, tribal.
很好看啊兄弟
It's beautiful work, man.
谢谢了 兄弟
Thank you, man. I appreciate that.
- 这个是什么  - 是毛利人图案
- What was that one?  - Maori.
代表着力量和勇气
This stands for strength and courage.
- 真的吗  - 对
- Really?  - Yeah.
你还待在这干什么
What the hell are you still doing here?
是这样 信不信由你
Well, you know, believe it or not,
我找不到地方住一晚 所以
I-I couldn't find a place to live in just a night, so...
- 我信  - 我算是完蛋了 Ray
- I believe it.  - I'm kind of fucked, Ray.
没错
Yes, you are.
赶快吃完你的免费早餐
I'd say finish up your free breakfast,
然后滚吧
and, uh, hit the bricks.
没关系 没关系
All right. It's all right.
这小子可以留下
The kid can stay.
但是你得干活 好吗 你愿意工作吗
But you got to work, all right? You ready to do some work?
愿意啊 你这是 让我做消防员了吗
Yeah. Did... did you just, did you just make me a fireman?
不是
No.
你要不就打扫厕所 要不就滚
Go clean the toilets or get the fuck out.
我让你做 什么鬼
Did I make you a... What...
嘿 帮我个忙
Hey, do me a favor.
楼下那间厕所 我用过了
The bathroom downstairs...I-I used it.
你就从那间开始吧
You can start there.
好极了呢
Great.
戴上手套哈 容易溅上
Get gloves. Pretty muddy.
你知道吗 当我看到这种大块污渍
You know, when I see a big stain like that,
我就先上下刷 然后左右刷
I go up and down, and then I go left and right.
- 真是美好时光呢   - 这就对了
- Good times.   - There you go.
你要把溅上去的也洗了
You got to get the splatter.
看到了吗 真是条完美的直线
You see that? That's a nice straight line.
你们要做很多无聊的工作哈
Yeah, you guys, uh, got to do a lot of shit work, huh?
我们不会说这是无聊的工作
We don't refer to it as shit work.
这是我们的家 我们希望它漂漂亮亮的
This is our house. We want it to look nice.
懂吗 集体荣誉
You know, company pride.
要用热水洗
You got to wash it hot.
热水 不是温水 不是冷水 要很热
Hot. Not warm, not cold. Extra hot.
- 好的  - 因为有臭虫
- Okay.  - Because of the bedbugs.
啥 什么是臭虫
What-What's bedbugs?
就是 呃 一种小昆虫
They're, uh, a-a tiny insect
它们进了你的家门就要把你逼走
that get into your home and they run you out.
- 你知道它们怎么繁殖吗  - 不知道
- You know how they procreate?  - No.
雄性臭虫把他的丁丁
The male bedbug takes his penis
塞进雌性的肚子里
and jams it into the female's stomach.
雌性臭虫有阴道吗 是有的
Does the female have a vagina? Yeah, she does.
这不重要
It doesn't matter.
他塞进她的肚子里
He jams it into her stomach.
你是怎么知道这些的 兄弟
Well, how do you know all this, man?
我怎么知道 我研究过啊
How do I know? I researched it.
- 就翻过来  - 哦 翻过来
- Just flip it over. Flip.  - Oh, just a flip.
- 对了 没错  - 好的
- There you go, yeah.  - Okay.
你学会了 就顺着翻下来
You got it. Just flip it right down.
- 叠得很好啊  - 嗯
- Very nice.  - Mm.
干得好
Well done.
当你长了臭虫 所有人都会离开你
When you have bedbugs, everybody leaves.
我父母不和我联系了
My parents stopped calling.
我兄弟姐妹不来看我了
My brothers and sisters stopped coming over.
我女朋友把我甩了 所有人都走了
My girl left. Everybody's gone.
你知道最后谁会留在你身边吗
And you know who's there for you at the end?
真是讽刺
Ironically?
只有臭虫
The bedbugs.
我从没想过我会这么说
I never thought I'd say it,
如果我当上了主厨 我就让你做我的助手
but if I make chief, I'm making you my aide.
- 是吗  - 你好啊小子
- Yeah?  - What's up, kid?
你觉得你测试做得怎么样
Well, how do you think you did on the test?
测试太难了
Tough test.
当然了 我希望我做的还不错
I mean, you know, I hope I did good.
我操
Fuck!
- 他干得不错
- He's doing a good job.  - (scoffs)
他洗车洗得不错
He knows how to wash a truck.
那就收拾收拾去洗车行干吧
Getting ready for his career working at a car wash.
你怎么就不肯放过这孩子
You ever gonna give this kid a break or what?
我不知道该做什么
I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
那就什么都别做
Then do nothing.
Stan死的时候是你负责这个工作吗
Were you on the job when Stan was killed?
是啊 你知道是我
Yeah. You know I was.
你听说的时候第一个念头是什么
What's the first thing you thought of when you heard?
我在想他有没有孩子
I-I wondered if he had kids.
我们到底为什么要洗车
Why do we have to clean this thing anyway?
反正它都会着火
It's just gonna get fire on it.
那些被活活烧死的人
You think the people that are burning alive
会在乎车洗得亮不亮吗
give a fuck if the truck is shiny?
我就随口一说
Just saying.
我都不知道你为什么要洗车
I don't even know why you got to clean the truck.
怎么地 你还想在大火面前性感一点吗
What, you're trying to show up all sexy to a fire?
我喜欢他
I like him.
不要 住手
No! No! Stop!
够了
All right!
我给你扶一下书包 滑下来了
Let me fix that backpack. It's slipping.
你送我去学校感觉好奇怪
It's weird having you walk me to school.
为什么呢
Why is that?
因为平时都是Scott送我
'Cause Scott always walks me.
有时候我也送你
I walk you sometimes.
可能是吧
I guess so.
他和你们在一起时奇怪吗
Is he, uh, is he weird around you guys?
没有啊
No.
他挺好的
He's nice.
他经常问我还好吗
He asks me how I'm doing.
你怎么回答他
What do you tell him?
我说我还好
I say I'm doing fine.
你不用说谎来照顾我的感受 好吗
Look, you don't have to lie to make me feel better, all right?
我知道我和你妈妈做得不够好
I know me and your mom could do a better job
我们应该一起克服这事
getting along through all of this, and, uh...
对不起 我处理得并不好
Hey, I'm sorry if I haven't handled it so well.
这是什么
What's that?
这是【闪电冰侠】
Oh, that's Ice Flash.
Scott给我画的 但是画得不太好
Scott drew it for me, but it didn't come out so good.
是啊 我觉得他画的很乱
Yeah, I think his drawings are a little shaky.
这张是我画的
That's the one that I drew.
这是他画的
This is how he drew it.
挺不错吧
It's good, right?
是啊 岂止是不错
Yeah, it's better than good.
这很厉害
Did a great job.
是啊
Yeah.
他说他会教我
He said he was gonna teach me.
他说他要教你画这个吗
He said he'd teach you how to do that?
对
Yeah.
他说话算数
And he stays to his word.
现在来这里好惬意啊
It's so nice in here now.
我好喜欢这种颜色
I love it. I love the colors.
我全都喜欢
I love everything.
- 来啦  - 嗨
- Mm!  -  Hey.
- 你好呀 Scott  - 怎么
- Oh, hey, Scott.  - What's...
这是怎么了
What's going on in here?
这是 为什么全都不一样了
Where... Why is everything so different?
好看吗 你喜欢吗
Isn't it nice? Do you like it?
那是张粉色的椅子吗
Is that a pink chair?
- 是啊 我们在重新装修  - 这窗帘怎么也变了
- Yeah, we've been redecorating.  - W-What's up with the drapes?
是啊
- Yeah.
植物也换了
Plants, too.
可不嘛 为啥
Yeah. Why's...
你妈妈的品位很好
Your mother has great taste.
好吧
Yeah.
你最近都去哪里了
Where have you been staying?
我一直在消防站 和Ray在一起
Oh, I've been, uh, at the firehouse with Ray.
好的 我很高兴你没有流落街头
Oh, okay. Well, I'm just glad that you're not on the street.
我跟你说他不会无家可归的
I told you he wasn't homeless.
你一点没错 我好喜欢这个绿色
When you're right, you're ri... I love this green.
- 是啊  - 其实我一直在
- Yeah, well... - We... I actually have been
学着 就是 和那些弟兄们相处
learning, uh, a lot and, like, bonding with the guys.
- 是吗  - 所以 是啊
- Oh.  - So, uh, yeah.
对 他们让我做清洁
Yeah, they got me cleaning.
他们让我洗洗东西
Uh, they got me, like, washing stuff and, like,
- 在消防站里干活  - 是吧
- working around the firehouse and...  - Mm-hmm. Oh.
我确实明白你之前的想法了
I really understand where you were coming from before.
就是你把我赶出去的时候
You know, when you threw me out.
我觉得我现在已经改过自新了
Like, I think I really got my shit together now,
我已经准备好 搬回来
and I'm ready to, like, come back and...
好吧
Okay.
所以 你觉得你已经懂得什么叫辛苦工作了
So, like, you think you know what hard work is?
倒也不是 但就是
Well, I wouldn't say that, but, you-you know,
我 我有个初步认识了
I-I-I definitely have an idea.
- 你拖了下地
- You mopped a floor
做了做饭
and-and you cooked.
你打扫了一下厕所
You cleaned a bathroom once.
哎呀 Scott
Oh. Oh, Scott.
那你干完这么多重活肩膀酸吗
And how's your shoulder feel after all that very hard work?
哦 你们取笑我
Oh, you're making fun of me.
你们为啥拿我开玩笑
Why are you making fun...
我工作很辛苦 真的
I-I worked really hard. I did.
不信去问Ray
Ask Ray.
他想搬回来
He's trying to get back.
吃JB去吧 Joy
Eat a dick, Joy.
早上已经吃过了
Had one for breakfast.
已经饱了
I'm full.
喂
Hey!
还有  爸爸的神龛在哪里
And-and wh...and where's Dad's shrine?
- 在哪 去哪了  - 哦 你把气氛都破坏了
- Where-where-where...  - Oh, you're ruining the vibe.
神龛呢 爸爸的神龛呢
Where's his shrine? Where's Dad's shrine?
他的东西也不见了 我的东西也没了
All of his stuff is gone. All my shit's gone.
- 到底怎么回事 - 宝贝
- What's going on?  - Honey.
好吧 让我 我很抱歉
Uh, all right, let...I'm-I'm really sorry.
我不该大声说你 对不起
I'm sorry I raised my voice. I'm sorry.
- 我不该笑你 - 我们能私下说话吗
- I'm sorry I laughed.  - Could we talk in private?
- 好的 我们出去吧  - 行
- Let's go outside, yeah.  - Yeah.
我们出去说几句话
So we're gonna speak for a minute.
- 对不起  - 真的抱歉  - 没关系 Joy
- I'm sorry. - So sorry.  -  It's okay, Joy.
- 我们好好谈一下  - 是啊
- Let's just have a real...  - Let's just... Yeah.
- 我们去外面吧  - 好好开始谈谈
- Let's just talk outside.  - Let's just get into it.
行啊 好勒
You know? Right. Okay.
- 那么…
- So...
天 你不是吧
Oh, no, you did not!
警报
Code alarm.
- 引擎和卡车马上就位
- Engine and truck are first due.
房号118
Box 118.
房顶上有很浓的烟
Heavy smoke coming from the roof.
嘿 Scott 你想跟这辆车一起过去吗
Hey, yo, Scott, you want to ride this one in?
可 可以吗
Is-is that okay?
好啊 上车吧
Yeah, jump in.
- 上车
- Jump in.
- 都听好
-  Listen up.
这个房间的警情已经接到很多个电话了
We're getting multiple calls on this box.
我们肯定要进火场 穿好装备
We're going to a fire. Suit up!
5-7号消防梯呼叫斯塔顿岛
Ladder 5-7 to Staten Island.
收到请讲 5-7号
Yes, go ahead, Ladder 5-7.
二次警报传输中
Transmitting second alarm.
房号 1-1-8
Box 1-1-8.
五层建筑的
Fire in the first and second floor
一楼和二楼失火
of a five-story multiple dwelling.
1-4-9 呼叫1-4-9
1-4-9 to 1-4-9,
司机准备开始工作
Chauffer to start work.
1-4-9司机已就位
1-4-9 Chauffeur to Control.
打开消防栓
Turn on the hydrant.
好的 穿好装备
All right. Suit up.
10-4 号
10-4.
5-7号梯呼叫司机
Ladder 5-7 to Chauffeur.
George 带上天线 打通三楼的窗户
George, take the aerial and vent that third-floor window,
然后带上天线上楼顶
and then get the aerial to the roof.
1-4-9呼叫1-4-9
1-4-9 to 1-4-9.
司机 供水
Chauffeur, start water.
准备好了吗 我开门了
Are you guys ready? I'm opening the door.
49号 水开了
49, here comes your water.
灭火灭火 赶快 扑灭它
Hit it, hit it. Go. Hit it, hit it!
我没事
I'm good.
- 你还好吗  - 还好
- You all right?  - Yeah.
他们会没事的 他们能搞定
They're gonna be fine. They got this.
是啊 我知道
Yeah, yeah, I-I know.
我知道看起来很吓人 但他们心里都有数的
I know it looks bad, but they know what they're doing.
好吗
All right?
5-7号梯 5-7号司机
Ladder 5-7, Chauffeur 5-7.
我打开了三楼窗户
I just vented the third-floor window.
我现在带着天线上楼顶
I'm bringing the aerial to the roof.
5-7号
5-7 O.V. to 5-7.
我在二楼发现一名10-45
I got a 10-45 on the second floor.
我从里面的楼梯把他带到楼下
Gonna bring him down the inside stairs.
10-4号 Ray
10-4, Ray.
5-7号楼顶
5-7 roof to 5-7...
1-4-9号司机
1-4-9 Chauffeur to 1-4-9.
- 水压怎么样  - 水压没问题
- How's the water pressure?  - Pressure's fine.
5-7-9呼叫5-7
5-7-9 to 5-7,
一楼所有房间已经撤离
all the apartments on the first floor are clear.
10-4 队长
10-4, Cap.
每个人第一次进火场
You know, everyone gets nervous
都会紧张的
during their first fire.
你知道吗 我还是个新手的时候 我害怕死了
You know, when I was a probie, I was so scared,
走到哪都跟着我的队长
I would follow my captain everywhere,
拽着他的衣服
just hold on to his jacket.
就紧跟着他 希望自己活下来
You know, follow him around, hold on for dear life.
- 是啊  - 但是 呃
- Yeah.  - No, but, uh,
每个人都会有点害怕的
you know, everybody gets a little scared.
我觉得 这说明你是坦率的
I mean, you know, I mean, it's... keeps you honest.
知道吗 如果你不害怕
You know? No, if you don't get scared,
- 那你肯定不正常  - 是啊
- there's something wrong with you.  - Mm-hmm.
但是 你爸爸从不会害怕
And, by the way, your dad never got scared.
是吗 你怎么知道
Yeah? How-how do you know?
以前吧 我和他在同一个消防站
I mean, back in the day, I-I was at the same house
一起待了六个月
with him for about six months, so...
等等 你和我爸爸共事了六个月
Wait, you worked with my dad for six months
- 你现在才告诉我  - 是啊 我觉得
- and you're just telling me?  - Yeah. I mean, I...
我不想让你感到别扭
Yeah, I didn't want to make you feel weird.
我们不想伤害你
We didn't want to insult you
因为你看上去很脆弱
'cause you seem a little delicate.
- 拜托  - 确实是
- No. Please.  - Well, yeah.
那 他是什么样的人
What, w-what was he like?
他和你有点像
He was kind of like you.
就是 如果你不了解他
You know, like, if you didn't know him,
你就会觉得他是个巨婴 但是他
you'd think he was a crack baby, but he was...
但他是个好人 他是个很不错的人
No, but he was a good guy. He was a, he was a great guy.
- 他是个好人  - 是啊 我听说
- He was a great guy.  - Well, I-I, I mean, I heard
- 他超级搞笑的  - 是的
- he was fucking hilarious.  - Oh, yeah.
他逃脱了好多糗事
And-and he got away with so much shit,
因为他非常讨人喜欢
like, because he was so freaking likable.
什么糗事 他逃脱了什么
What kind of stuff? Like, w-what'd he get away with?
有一次 我们正在西边高速上开车
One time, we were driving down the West Side Highway
- 在外面玩了一整晚  - 对
- after being out all night...  -  Mm.
你知道这事
You know this.
这事超经典
This is a good one.
然后他就
And, uh, he's, like,
爬出天窗 爬上去
he's up on the... through the sunroof.
他就坐在车顶上
He's, like, sitting on top of the car.
我们没办法让他下来
We're like... We couldn't get him in.
我们就加速开车 然后急刹
So we start speeding up, stopping short, you know.
后来我们撞上了桥 他就跌到挡风玻璃上
By the time we hit the bridge, he fell onto the windshield.
- 他就  - 怎么了
- So he's...  - What?
他就
he's, like...
- 怎么样
- What?
就趴在那 咒骂我们 他的脸
Hanging on, cursing at us, putting his face
就挤在挡风玻璃上
up against the windshield.
他骂道 你们这些狗日的
He's like, "You motherfuckers!"
- 就很像阿汤哥的电影
- It was like some real Tom Cruise shit.
然后
So...
我们到了布鲁克林
We get into Brooklyn.
当然啦 那就有警察
And sure-sure enough, there's cops.
就像专门在那等我们似的
Like, uh, like they were waiting for us.
糟了
Oh, shit.
我就想 我们肯定完蛋了
So now I'm like, "Oh, fuck. We're screwed."
Stan从车上下来 他对着警察走过去
Stan gets off the car. He goes over to the cop.
我就想 完了 他要去跟警察闹事了
I'm thinking, "Oh, shit, he's gonna fucking clock this cop.
他肯定会那样
He's gonna, you know..."
结果他直接走过去 捧着警察的脸
And he goes right up to him, grabs his face,
亲了他的嘴
and he kisses him on the lips.
他们是高中同学
They went to high school together.
搞半天他们是高中同学
They went to fucking high school together.
我就想 只有Stan才能逃脱这种事
I'm like, "Only Stan could get away with that."
真的 我发誓
I swear to God.
你知道吗 传闻说
Well, you know, the rumor is
他的可卡因就是从警察这拿的
that he got the coke from the cops.
不是那一个警察 他还认识一个在曼哈顿的警察
Not that cop. There was another cop he knew in Manhattan.
- 什么 不是吧不是吧不是吧
- What? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no! No.
- 可卡因 啥 不是吧  - 伙计们
- Coke? What? No.  - Guys, guys, guys.
- 那是他父亲啊  - 所以呢
- Guys, it's his dad.  - So?
- 我不知道这不能说  - 那是他父亲
- I didn't know it was a secret.  -  It's his dad.
你们不能话说一半啊
You can't just tease me with that.
- 拜托了 伙计们  - 可这是
- Please, guys, but...  - It was...
你们不懂 我妈跟我说
You don't understand. My mom, my mom tells me
说了好多他的故事
all these stories about how much
说他就是个圣人啊什么的
he's like a saint and all that shit.
我超想听可卡因的故事
Like, I-I would love to hear a coke story.
- 拜托了  - 说13禁的版本
- Please.  - The PG-13 version.
不要啊 说完整的版本
No, you don't...No, the real version.
你们不懂我承受的压力
You don't understand the amount  of pressure I'm under,
- 以为他是个完美的人  - 好吧 随你了
- thinking this guy's perfect.  - All right, fuck it, fuck it.
好吧 我们那时候都磕得上头了
All right, we were coked out of our minds.
- 秒啊  - 是吗 我们全都磕了
- Nice.  - All right? We all were.
- 我们 是啊 我们都有份
- We all... Well, I mean, uh, we were.
- 但是时代不一样 那时候我们都有份  - 是啊
- But that was a different time. I mean, we all did it.  - Right.
这家伙是个瘾君子
This guy was the cokehead.
- 你就是个瘾君子  - 好吧
- You were the cokehead.  - All right.
我四年前就戒了 你知道的
I stopped four years ago. You know that.
你在说啥 你以为
What are you talk...How do you think
他这些年怎么保持这么瘦的
he stayed this skinny all these years?
那是因为我新陈代谢快
No, I have a high metabolism.
你的脸皮应该刻在玻利维亚的硬币上
They should have his face on a nickel in Bolivia.
但那是玩闹的时候 好吗
But playtime was playtime, all right?
你知道 当他工作的时候
Like, you know, when he was at work,
他就非常的专业
he was, he was all, you know, business.
他就是那种 当你冲进火场的时候
All right? And he was the guy you wanted by your side
你希望站在你身边的人
if-if you were going into a fire.
我是说 如果你要
Yeah, I mean, if they were gonna,
从零开始塑造一个消防员的话
like, build a fireman from scratch,
他就是那个
he would've been, you know...
- 模板  - 是啊
- Prototype.  - Yeah. Yeah.
没错 他从头到脚
Exactly. You know, top to bottom...
都是一个真正的消防员
He's a fireman.
知道吗
You know?
- 他是最勇敢的那种人  - 是啊
- You know, as brave as they come.  - Yeah.
我想到是玩游戏说
You know, I was thinking about what you said at the game
消防员不应该生孩子
about, you know, like, firemen shouldn't have kids.
我告诉你
Let me tell you something.
你爸爸并不仅仅是那天晚上
You know, your dad, he didn't just die
救了两个人然后牺牲了
saving those two people that night.
他做了太多次
I mean, he did that a lot.
你知道吗 有时候
You know, like, sometimes,
他都等不到指令
he wouldn't even wait for the line.
就会直接冲进失火的房间里
He'd just, he'd just go in, like, a fully involved room,
我们都在喊他 你这是做什么
and you're, like...I'm like, "What are you doing?"
如果他听到里面有人的话
And because if-if he heard there was somebody in there,
他就会马上冲进去
he'd just go in.
这就是他的方式
That's the way, you know...
他就是这样的人
He... That's who he was.
他本性就是这样 你知道吗
That's how he was built, you know?
他不可能 不做这样的事
He couldn't, he couldn't not be that way.
你明白吗
You understand?
谢谢你 真的 谢谢你告诉我
Thank you. No, thank you, thank you for sharing.
太棒了
That's awesome.
他要是听到我这么说
He would slap the shit out of me
肯定会扇死我 但他确实是个英雄
if he heard me say this about him, but he was a hero.
人们需要英雄
And heroes are necessary.
而英雄应该拥有家庭 对吗
And they should be allowed to have families, all right?
虽然我知道 那意味着
But I know it means, you know,
家人会因此受苦
that people suffer.
我很遗憾 真的
And I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
对不起 我说的话太混账了
Well, but I'm sorry for being a dick.
- 所有事都有两面性  - 不用道歉
- There's-there's two sides to every story.  - No.
谢谢你告诉我 谢谢你让我明白这些
Thank you for sharing with me. Thanks for taking me here.
- 好了 我们别搞得跟奥普拉秀一样  - 是啊
- All right, we don't have to get all Oprah.  - Yeah.
-没事的     -嘿敬Stan
- It's all right. - Hey, to Stan.
-来 敬Stan  -来 敬Stan
- Yeah, Stan.- Yeah, Stan.
敬Stan
- Stan. - Stan.- Stan.
("One Headlight"
by The Wallflowers playing)
嘿
♪ Hey ♪
来吧尝试一下
♪ Come on, try a little ♪
没有什么是永恒的
♪ Nothing is forever ♪
总有比中立
♪ There's got to be something better than ♪
更好的事
♪ In the middle ♪
但是我和灰姑娘
♪ But me and Cinderella ♪
组装了一辆车
♪ We put it all together ♪
（即使只有）一个车头灯，
♪ We can drive it home ♪
我们也能驾着他奔向家的方向
♪ With one headlight ♪
她说有好冷 感觉
- ♪ She said it's cold, it feels like... ♪
唉 我点儿头疼 我
My head hurts. I...
我就只能吸吸大麻 喝酒挨不住啊
This-this is why I don't drink.I just, I just smoke weed.
所以你未来打算怎么走啊
Hey, so what are you gonna do?
什么怎么走
With-with what?
你的小日子啊
With your life.
你总有啥是感兴趣的吧
You must be passionate about something.
额 有啊 我对纹纹身有兴趣啊
Um, yeah, the...the tattoo thing.
我超爱纹身的
I... I love that.
你只是嘴上说说的那种喜欢而已嘛
Were you, like, into that?
没有， 我其实私下经常练习的
No, you know, it-it takes a lot of practice, you know, and...
但现在我身边的朋友已经没法让我继续再给他们纹身了
None of my friends will let me tattoo them anymore and...
嘿 要不你给我纹个好了
Hey, why don't you give me a tattoo?
啥
What?
啥个头啊
What-what?
来嘛 我反正没有任何纹身
Come on, I don't have any tattoos.
我就像白纸一张 嘿嘿
I'm a, I'm a blank slate, man.
我后背随你怎么练手
Put it on my back. Yeah, use it for practice.
额 你不是喝多了
Well... well, you're just saying this
才这么说的吧 你不是
'cause you're drunk, right? You're not...
-你不是认真的吧-难道每个人第一次纹身
- You're not actually... - Isn't everybody drunk
都是在喝醉的时候
when they get their first tattoo?
好的吧 Ray
Touché, Ray.
成
Yeah.
反正在背上 我又不在意
It's my back. I don't give a fuck.
反正我又看不见
I'm never gonna see it.
还有 我跟你说
Plus, I got to tell you something, you know.
我看见你给Harold画的英雄了
I saw that drawing you did for Harold.
我都震惊了
I was kind of blown away by it, man. You...
画得有点忒好了
You're getting really good at it.
我练过很多次的
I'm practicing a lot.
是嘛
Yeah.
只要坚持铁杵也能磨成针
Like anything, you keep doing it, you get better at it.
然后呢 我
And I, you know...
我也希望你能成功
You know, I do want to see you do well, all right?
我相信你
I-I believe in you.
哥儿们 谢了
Thanks, man.
你一定很爱我吧
You... you must really love me.
我也很爱你呢
I love you, too.
谢谢你这么说但是我没
Uh, I-I appreciate that, but I'm not ready...
你也会这么对我说的吧
Y-You-you gonna say it back?
我才不这么说
I'm not ready to say something like that.
你得回应我呀
You got to say it back.
要不然我明天挂了 你怎么办
What-what if I die tomorrow?
那我就会说
Then I'll be that guy saying,
你知道吗 虽然我没说出口 但是
"You know, even though I never said it..."
嗯 好
Uh, look...
我给你纹身
I would love to tattoo your back.
好嘞
Okay, cool.
但是先说好啊 不要给我纹什么独角兽
All right, but here's the deal. No unicorns.
-什么彩虹啊  - 嗯
- No rainbows, all right? - Uh.
别整那些小姑娘喜欢上彩色的玩意儿
None of that shit little girls like to color in.
好
Okay.
还有别整人体器官 或者裸女哈
No body parts. No nudity.
- 好  - 别整中文字
- Okay.- No Chinese letters.
-好吧 好吧 -我想
- All right. All right, fine. - I want, I...
整些我看得懂的玩意儿
I want to be able to fucking read
纹在我背上
whatever you put back there.
别整什么黄橙橙的鸡 乱七八糟啥玩意儿的
I don't need some o-order for orange chicken or some shit.
好嘞
All right.
要开始了哦 你准备好了么
Here we go. You ready?
准备好了 开始吧
Yep, let's do it. Let's get it over with.
好 谢谢你
Yeah, I-I really appreciate this.
让我当人肉练习板
This is... It's actually very nice.
好
Good.
我们开始了哦
All right.
我擦
Fuck.
哥儿们 为啥你们爱搞这玩意儿
Dude, why do you get these?
我不知道啊 我
Um, I don't know. I, uh...
每次不痛快的时候 我都会
Whenever I'm going through something, I just,
我都会搞一个纹身
you know, I get one.
让我自己放松下冷静下
It relaxes me and calms me down.
这有助于我思考人生
Helps me, like, think things through, you know.
-这可以让你放松  -是啊
- This relaxes you? - Yeah.
你没想过比如做瑜伽啥的去放松自己么
You ever think of taking, like, a yoga class?
或者冥想啥的
Meditating?
或者献个血
Why don't you just give blood?
那个也是用针扎的
There's still needles involved.
嗯这个纹身好看哦
Yeah, that's a nice tattoo.
很复古
It's aces.
-你丫混蛋在偷看我牌  -啥
- You looking at my cards, you piece of shit? - What?
没呢 我说的是纹身
No, no, no, no. I'm talking about the tattoo.
你干嘛呢
What are you doing?
-啥 -你居然一晚上在搞我
- What? - First good hand you dealt me
你作弊
all night, you're cheating?
-他说的是纹身好不啦  -是啊
- He was talking about the tattoo.- Exactly.
-这么烂的借口
- You are the worst liar ever.
6乘以4等于多少
What's six times four?
- 24.
24 对了 是 24
24. Yeah, 24.
那 7x5 呢
What's seven times five?
-35 答对了
- 35. - Good job.
聪明的娃儿
Look how smart you are.
我在猜你画的都是些啥
I'm trying to guess what you're drawing
你手在我后背上上下下的动着
by the, by the way your hand's going.
记住啊 别整那些个奇怪的玩意儿啊 小心我的40米大刀
Remember, nothing weird or I'll kill you.
都是正常玩意儿  好吧
- Nothing weird. - Okay.
这看起来不奇怪吧
It doesn't look weird, does it?
挺正常的
No, not at all.
嗯 很好不然我会杀了他的
Oh, good, 'cause you know I'll murder him.
看着很不错呢
It looks wonderful.
哎呀 这么疼的咩
Oh! Is it supposed to hurt?
咋这么疼呢
Is it supposed to hurt that much?
墨通过针扎进你皮肤 当然疼了
It's-it's a needle going into your back. Yeah.
道理我懂啊 我以为背上脂肪多点 会好点儿
I know, but I thought I had more back fat than that.
我可以也整个纹身不
Can I get a tattoo?
-不不行   -可以啊
- No. No. -  Sure.
-好吧 -不行
- All right. - No.
绝对不行
Never.
别打扰专业人士干活
Don't mess with perfection.
全员出发
Everybody goes.
全员出动 一级警报
Both companies, first due.
电话警报 警报号 3-4-3
Phone alarm. Box 3-4-3.
罗克兰和富兰克林路中间的卡朋特大道18号
18 Carpenter Avenue between Rockland and Franklin.
2楼的一个私宅窗户有烟雾冒出
Smoke coming from the second- floor window of a private home.
出车
- Turnout.
哟呵
Yoo-hoo.
-你好  -咋了
- Excuse me. - Yeah?
嘿 兄弟 你好么
Hey, man. How you doing?
你好 兄弟
What's up, man?
帮忙一下
I need some assistance over here, please.
-好嘞 -给我一个
- Sure, I... - Hey, give me a sh...
-我的天  -啊 么事的
- Oh, my God! - Ah, don't worry about it.
一切都还好的
Listen, everything's all good.
没什么大不了的
It's, uh, really nothing.
我只要你帮我一下下
I just need a little assistance.
这个马上处理一下就好了
This is something that needs to be taken care of now.
你这是咋整的呀 你还好么 你被枪击中了
What happened? Are you okay? Did you get shot?
-还是你被捅刀子了 -这一点儿也不是小事儿啊
- Were you stabbed? - It's not really a big deal.
可能是我的电子烟在我裤兜里爆炸了
My vape exploded in my pocket. Just...
也可能是我做瑜伽动作没做对
I didn't stretch right before yoga.
可能我刚在玩儿乒乓球儿不小心滑倒了
I was playing tennis.I slipped.
-到底咋回事儿啊 你 - 你要我说点儿啥
- Well, which one is it? - What do you want me to say?
没啥事儿了
It was nothing.
我只是需要你帮我处理下伤口
I just need some medical attention, but just by you.
大哥 我大哥110 问下啊 我也不知道该咋整啊
Dude, I got to call 911. I don't know what to do.
别别别 别回头把警察给我招来了
No, no, no, listen, listen. No police, please.
今儿就算了吧
Not today.
-你说啥呢你  -没事
- What does that even mean? - No.
我们不需要政府的人协助了
We don't need to get the government involved  into this situation.
我们一起弄弄就好了
We can handle this together.
大佬 我现在嗨着呢 没法帮你啊
Dude, I'm so high. I can't help you right now.
我也很嗨着呢
I'm high, too.
那你应该很了解我的感受啊
Well, then you know how I feel.
你要我怎么做
- What do you want me to do?
帮我看下伤口
Take a look at this.
我需要清洗下伤口
I need some sort of foam.
-我嘞个去 - 你有针可以缝下么
- Holy shit! - You got some stitching?
-老兄  - 你 你有没有针
- Dude! - Do-do you have, like, a little needle?
-你有没有类似针一样的东西 -没有
- Do you have something with a needlepoint? - No.
这是咋回事啊
What happened?
就是一场误会 发生点儿争执
It was a misunderstanding. It was an argument.
不过我们和好了 我们解决了
But we're all friends again. We worked it out.
你懂的 都是朋友嘛
You know how buddies get.
老大我得把你送医院去
Dude, I... We-we, we got to take you to the hospital
-不然你会死的 -我会死
- or you're gonna die. - I'm not gonna die.
-是的你会死  -我会死
- Yes, you are.- I'm gonna die?
是的我确定
Yeah, I'm positive.
一定以及肯定 如果咱们不去医院
I'm positive that you're gonna die
你会死的
if we don't go to the hospital.
这里有金属检测器吗
Are there metal detectors in here?
我不确定啊 咋了
I-I'm not sure. Why?
没事
Don't even worry about it.
我后面再告诉你
I'll tell you later.
我去
Oh, shit.
-啊 我去 疼啊 - 你会没事的
- Oh, fuck. - You'll be all right.
-啊老天好疼 - 你会没事的
- Oh, my God. - You'll be all right.
有人吗 帮个忙欸
- Guys, I need help!
这个人在流血 他失了很多血
This guy's bleeding! He's losing a lot of blood!
-麻烦给我一架轮床 - 谢谢
- I need a gurney, please! - Oh, thank you.
- 来 用手压住  -谢谢
- All right, just hold... Put... - Thank you.
-用手压住伤口 会
- Put pressure on it, all right?
你好这个人不是被抢击中了就是被人捅刀子了
Hi. This guy's been, uh, either shot or stabbed.
具体我也不知道 他没说得很清楚
I don't know. He's been kind of vague about it.
先生 你被中枪了 还是被捅刀子了
Sir, have you been shot? Stabbed?
没
No.
-我失足掉进小树丛了- 好吧
- I fell in a thorn bush.- Okay.
让他填下这个表
Have him fill out this paperwork,
他填好了医生一会会叫你名字的
and the doctor will call you when he's ready.
帮我个忙 跟我换个身份证行么
Do me a favor, man. Can we just switch identities?
啥 不要
What? No.
那让我借用下你驾照嘞
Just let me use your driver's license.
大哥我们长得一点都不像啊 -没人会知道的
- We look nothing alike, dude. - No one's gonna know.
相信我
Just trust me.
我流血流得我感觉要拉屎了
I'm bleeding. It feels like I have to shit.
我的天啊
Oh, Jesus Christ.
我是Maggie 的儿子 你认识
I'm Margie's son. Do you know...
我是Maggie的儿子
- I'm Margie's son.
我不认识她
I don't know who that is.
我只是个负责登记的人而已
- I'm just filling in.
好吧
Okay.
-我懂  -我越来越疼
- I know. - My pain keeps coming.
告诉我那个混蛋父亲 我恨他
Tell that fucking cocksucker, my father, that I hate him
也爱他 我原谅他了
and I love him at the same time and I forgive him.
我不用替你转达啊 你一定会没事的
I-I-I do not need to do that, because you're gonna live.
告诉我姐姐 我知道她就是我妈妈
Tell my sister I know she's my mother.
哈
Huh.
我一听到消息马上就赶过来了
Got here as soon as I could.
老哥 我们得帮帮他
Hey, man, we got to help this guy.
他血都要流光了
He's bleeding out.
他是警察吗
This a cop?
他看起来好像一个警察哦
He looks like a cop.
护士您好
Excuse me, ma'am.
我是Ray Bishop 消防57队
Ray Bishop, Ladder 57.
帮我们找个医生救治这个人
We got to get this guy some help.
我们要走过去
We got to move it along here.
-跟我来 - 好 兄弟 起来
- Follow me. - Okay, come on, buddy.
来来来
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
就这样 就这样
Here we go, here we go, here we go.
好的
- All right.
有个 腹部受伤 的患者
Abdominal wound!
到了
There we go.
哪儿呢
Where? Where?
放2号床
Put him in Two.
上2号床
In Two.
测量下他的生命体征
Let's get vitals.
-好了 到了亲   -好 就把他放这里
- All right, buddy. - All right, get him right here.
我们需要脱下你的衣服
We got to get your shirt off.
让我看下你还没有其他创伤
Let me know if you need trauma.
- 哦我去  -好  我们开始了哦
-  Oh, shit. - Okay. Here we go.
-慢慢来 慢慢来  - 你俩去6号床
- Nice and easy, nice and easy. - I'll meet you at Six. Six.
你可以吗 你会好起来的
You okay? It's gonna be okay.
他是你朋友
He's one of your friends?
不是啦 只是纯帮忙而已
No, no, no. I-I was just helping him.
是啊 Scott 把他带过来而已
Yeah, Scott brought him in.
那人是在我们出任务的时候
You know, guy just kind of wandered into the firehouse
不知怎么的自己走到消防站去的
while we were out on a call.
把衣服脱了 衣服上都是血迹
You guys are covered in blood. Take these off.
把它们放这里
Throw 'em here.
放那边去
Put 'em over here.
放那边就好 那下面
Just leave 'em there Down there.
那是啥
What's that?
-你背上的是啥呢 - 哦 那个啊
- What's that? - Oh.
我是你儿子的纹身练习对象
I let your son practice on me.
看起来怎么样 他还没创作完 不让我看还
How's it look? He won't let me see it till it's done.
我看下
Let me see it.
他说想纹啥都可以的
He, um, he-he let me do whatever I wanted, so...
天啊
Jesus Christ.
他没在我背上搞什么乱七八糟的吧
He didn't put anything stupid on there, did he?
他搞好久了都还没完成
Took forever.
没
Nah.
额 我眼睛老纹不好
Yeah, I, um... I can never get the eyes right
我好像把它们画得过深了点 但是 我
'cause I-I just make them too dark, but I-I...
很美啊
It's beautiful.
我为你骄傲
I'm proud of you.
你真的纹得很好 -谢谢
- You could really do this. - Thanks.
没有中文字吧
There's not any, like, Chinese characters
有中文字
or anything back there, is there?
没有没有
No, no.
没有
No, no, no.
你跟我说不要搞那些 我就没搞了
You told me not to.
我很听话的
I would never disobey you.
Ray 谢谢你 让他在你背上联系纹身
Thank you for letting him do this, Ray.
我啥也没做啊 只是做在那里
Oh, I didn't do anything. I just sat there.
都是他在帮我纹
He did all the work.
你很享受给我后背纹身吧
You liked going over the spine, didn't ya?
老享受了
Took it like a champ.
我一直坐在那里缩着背 让他作画
I sat there wincing.
我去
Oh, my God.
你俩好歹拉下帘子撒
Can we at least close the curtain?
-哦 我的男人们 - 老弟 又没人死在这里 （拉啥帘子）
- Oh. My guys. - Guys, people die in here, all right?
我的男人们 过来
- My guys. My guys. - Uh... - Aw, come on.
老妈我才不想跟他拥抱呢 他都没穿衣服
Mom, I don't want to hug him. He's not wearing a shirt.
-来吧 你受得了的啦 - 老兄 你皮肤太滑了
- Come on, you can handle it. - Ah, dude, you're so smooth.
跟个海獭似的
You're-you're like a sea otter.
好了啦 差不多了
- Please, we have to stop.
差不多了
We have to stop. Please. Please.
别抱了 别抱了
- Please stop? Please stop.
但是首先 你要先去见 Stark 伯爵 和他家小姐 你就会
But first, you will get to Lord and Lady Stark and you will...
自打那天跟Ray和他同事从消防站
I hung out with, like, Ray and the guys
去酒吧玩儿的时候
from the firehouse the other night at the bar,
他们聊到了老爸的一些趣事
and, um, they were just telling all these stories about Dad.
那些故事我之前都没听你说过
And there were stories I never heard of before,
比如说他也嗑药
like, you know, about him, like, doing coke
他也很搞笑
and being hilarious.
-是啊 - 你知道这些事儿啊
- Yeah. - You know?
是啊 是啊
Yeah. Yeah.
他是很搞笑
Well, he was hilarious.
是嘛
Yeah.
额
Uh...
他也经常干些出格儿的事 他很疯狂
He was also out of control and crazy.
-听懂了吗 - 你不能这么吼我
- Do you understand? - You can't. (grunts)
你怎么都不跟我说
Why-why didn't you just tell me?
不知道啊
I don't know.
可能我是想让你对他只留下好印象从而
I just... I wanted you to have some good memories
去弥补见不到他的遗憾吧
to offset what happened.
我不知道应该怎么跟你说这些事
I didn't know what to-to say.
我曾经是想跟你说 你爹很喜欢跟你一起看卡通
Was I gonna say, "Your dad really loved watching cartoons
因为他也经常绊跤
with you 'cause he was tripping all the time"?
是啊
- Yeah.
听起来是个好父亲呢
Sounds like a good dad to me.
不 你知道吗
No, you know what?
嗯我懂
Uh, I get it.
得知他跟其他人一样也有自己的毛病
Knowing that he had his issues and... problems
我松了一口气
just like everybody else, it makes me feel better.
他是个真正活生生的人了
It really... it really humanizes him.
他是个很好的人
Well, he was a great guy.
他也是个很复杂的人
He was a very complicated guy.
他有着一颗大爱的心
He had a really big heart.
嗯
Mm.
像Ray一样嘛
Like, like Ray?
额
Uh...
是吧 是像Ray一样
Yeah, I guess, like Ray, yeah.
是哦
Yeah.
是的
Yeah. (laughs)
嗯 你就是对这款的人毫无免疫
Um, I guess you could say that you have a type.
哼
Uh-huh.
是啊
Yeah. (smacks lips)
我就喜欢这款的
I have a type.
你知道我虽不常提起他 但
I know we don't really talk about it much, but...
我
...I, uh...
我很想念老爸
I-I miss Dad.
很想很想
A lot.
是啊
Yeah.
我也是
Me, too.
然后
And, uh...
我为我之前的叛逆
I'm sorry that I've been
的行为道歉
so difficult to deal with.
我会
I'll...
我会努力找到
I'll try and...
属于自己的生活
get it together.
我知道 真的很抱歉
Iam so sorry.
你很难忘掉（老爹）
I think it'll always be hard.
我
I, uh...
我真的很喜欢Ray但
I really like Ray, but I...
他真应该去刮下胡子
He's-he's got to lose that mustache.
我的意思是
I mean, come on.
当我和他一起出门的时候
- When we go out in public,
人可能会以为我被他绑架了呢
people think that I'm kidnapped, you know?
就我俩出现在超市的那身打扮
The looks that we get at the supermarket.
人们看着我就像在问
They're like... People-people look at me like,
你还好么  我回答 我很好
"Are you okay?" And I'm like, "Yeah, no, yeah.
他是我妈 男票
It's my mom's boyfriend."
-好了 兄弟 祝你好运 -谢谢你送我一程
- All right, buddy, good luck. - Thanks for the lift.
老弟 不客气
All right, man.
自信点哈
Confidence, right?
-好的 -加油 拿下她
- Yeah. - All right, go get 'em.
嗨
Hey.
Hi.
你还好吗
Hey. How are you?
-你在这里干嘛呢 - 额 我就
- What are you doing here? - Oh, I just, uh...
我就想找你聊聊
I-I just wanted to talk to you.
额我今天有公务员考试
Well, I have my civil service test today.
嗯 我知道啊
Oh, yeah, I-I remembered.
所以我才想
That's why I wanted to, you know...
-我得走了 -我可以一起去吗
- I have to go. - Can I come?
啥 为毛
What? Why?
做你的精神支柱啊
You know, for, like, moral support.
我想在你身边随时支持着你
I just want to be there for you.
-好吧 我阻止不了你 -嗯那挺好的
- Well, I can't stop you. - Oh, all right, great.
你头发真美
Y-Your hair looks nice.
谢谢
Thanks.
我知道你现在可能想聊
Listen, I know you probably want to talk about
关于我俩的关系这些严肃的话题， 但是我没法跟你聊哈
relationship stuff and serious bullshit, but I can't.
我现在必须集中精力学习 才不会搞砸我的考试
I have to study and focus right now so I don't screw this up.
好
Okay.
我
I, um...
如果你愿意我可以帮你啊
I can help you, if you like.
你才不会想帮我呢
You don't want to help me.
不 我很想帮你的
Mm, yeah, I do. I would love to.
好 那你帮我测试这部分
Okay, w-will you just test me on this part?
好 那个吗
Yeah. That one?
-准备好了  -好
- All right. - Okay.
开始了哦
Here we go.
Amy必须要在一天内完成3个任务
"Amy must complete three tasks at work.
她预计前两个任务
"She estimates that the first two tasks
她需要45分钟完成
"will take her 45 minutes to complete
第三个任务需要花她
"and that the third task will take her
2小时45分钟完成
"two hours and ten minutes to complete.
如果Amy 的估计是准确的话
"If Amy's estimate is correct,
她完成所有任务的总耗时是多少
how long will it take her to complete all three tasks?"
3小时又40分钟
Three hours and 40 minutes.
你猜的还是你已经知道答案了
Did-did you just guess that or did know the answer?
回答正确
No, that's correct.
太厉害了
That's incredible.
-哇 - 还好啦
- Wow.- It's not that amazing.
-没有 就是很厉害呢 -别紧张
- It is, no. - Relax.
都是数学题啊
I-I... Is it all math questions?
应该是了 公务员考试不都这样
I thought it was, like, city shit.
没有没有
No, no.
你得证明你很聪明
You have to prove that you're not stupid,
这样他们才会让你在城市里工作
and then you can work for the city.
哦哦
Oh. Oh.
看来我是没法在城市里工作了
So I can never work for the city.
嘿 我
Hey, uh, I...
我
- I, uh...
I, um...
我爱你
I love you.
很爱很爱
A lot.
我一直都很爱你 我
I-I always have, and I, um...
所以我才表现得很奇怪
That's why I always act so weird.
我不知道我要如何表达自己
'Cause I don't know how to express myself.
因为我的错误表达
Failure to do so
所以给你带来了很大的伤害
could result in serious injury.
我要问下一题吗  -好
- Should I ask the next? - Yeah.
好 下一题  有250个人
All right, so, "Of the 250 people
在一家医疗机构工作 16% 是文员
"working at a medical facility, 16% are clerks.
多少个是
How many are..."
感谢您乘坐Staten Island 渡轮
Thank you for riding the Staten Island Ferry.
我都忘了我读到哪里了
I've lost my place.
一家医疗机构有250名员工
"Of the 250 people working at a medical facility,
- 16% are clerks."
- Mm-hmm.
非文员类的职员有几个
"How many are not clerks?"
答案页都被你泄露了
You're showing me the page.
你会等到我考完试么
Hey, will you wait for me while I do it
然后我们一起回Staten 岛
and then we can go back to Staten Island together?
当然啦 你要考多久
Yeah. Of course. How long are you gonna be?
3个半小时
Three and a half hours.
好
All right.
-真的啊 -是啊 我去找点事做
- Really? - Yeah, I'll go figure something out.
好
Okay.
嗯 就这么定了
All right. Cool.
考试加油哦
Good luck.
搞点有文化的
Maybe do something cultural.
拓展下你的视野啥的
Like, broaden your horizons.
好嘞
All right.
加油哦 好好考
Good luck. Have fun.
我的天啊  我紧张死了
Oh, my God, I'm freaking out!
好紧张
I'm scared.
嘿
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Ratatat ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Na-na-na-na, na-na-na-na ♪
跟我说说你对梦想的看法
♪ Tell me what you know about dreaming, dreaming ♪
你啥都懂
♪ You don't really know about nothing, nothing ♪
你也不惧明日的考验
♪ You don't really care about the trials of tomorrow ♪
与其闷闷不乐的睁眼卧床
♪ Rather lay awake in the bed full of sorrow ♪
不如起来去追逐自己的幸福
♪ I'm on the pursuit of happiness and I know ♪
不是所有闪光的东西都是金子
♪ Everything that shine ain't always gonna be gold, hey ♪
一旦想开了就好了
♪ I'll be fine once I get it ♪
我会越来越好
♪ I'll be good ♪
追逐自己的幸福
♪ I'm on the pursuit of happiness and I know ♪
我知道不是所有闪光的东西就是金子
♪ Everything that shine ain't always gonna be gold, hey ♪
我懂了以后我就想开了
♪ I'll be fine once I get it ♪
我会好起来的
♪ I'll be good ♪
跟我说说你对梦想的理解
♪ Tell me what you know about dreaming, dreaming ♪
你并不是一无所知
♪ You don't really know about nothing, nothing ♪
告诉我
♪ Tell me what you know about ♪
是什么让你夜晚惊梦
♪ Them night terrors every night ♪
凌晨5点 惊出一身冷汗 再也睡不着了
♪ 5:00 a.m., cold sweats, waking up to the sky ♪
我再追逐我的幸福 我也知道
♪ I'm on the pursuit of happiness and I know ♪
并不是所有会放光的都是金子
♪ Everything that shine ain't always gonna be gold, hey ♪
我懂了以后就想开了
♪ I'll be fine once I get it ♪
我会好起来的
♪ I'll be good ♪
追逐幸福
♪ Pursuit of happiness ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
我会找到它
♪ I'll get it ♪
我会好起来的
♪ I'll be good. ♪
哦 从未从不
♪ Oh, never, never, never ♪
我停下思考的脚步
♪ Did I ever stop to think ♪
我发现自己和你在一起
♪ That I'd find myself here with you ♪
在你的梦境世界里
♪ In your own world of dreams ♪
但是我来了
♪ Oh, but here I am ♪
和你在一起
♪ Again with you ♪
你是我快乐的源泉
♪ You are my joy ♪
我的快乐来自于你
♪ And my joy is you ♪
绝不也从未
♪ Never, never ♪
我从未停止爱你
♪ Never did I ever
stop loving you ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
有时候我停下脚步 问
♪ Sometimes I stop and ask ♪
想着你再哪里
♪ And wonder where you were ♪
然后让自己不在想你
♪ Then I rip you from my mind ♪
因为我觉得你并不在意
♪ 'Cause I thought you didn't care ♪
但是我来了
♪ Oh, but here I am ♪
又和你在一起
♪ Again with you ♪
这回我懂了
♪ This time I know ♪
我的心能允许我做的事
♪ What my heart can do ♪
从未绝不
♪ Never, never ♪
未曾停止爱你
♪ Never did I ever stop loving you ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
不知道为啥
♪ I don't know why ♪
我玩不起失去你的游戏
♪ I had to play the game of losing you ♪
这让我知道
♪ To make me see ♪
我还爱着你
♪ That I still love you ♪
是的
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
但是我来了
♪ But here I am ♪
再一次和你在一起
♪ Again with you ♪
你是我快乐的源泉
♪ You are my joy ♪
我的快乐来自于你
♪ And my joy is you ♪
从未 绝不
♪ Never, never ♪
未曾停止爱你
♪ Never did I ever stop loving you ♪
♪ Oh, no, oh, no ♪
从未绝不未曾宝贝
♪ Never, never, ooh, never, baby ♪
我有停止爱你吗
♪ Did I ever stop loving you ♪
我就是无法停止
♪ I just can't stop ♪
♪ No, no, no ♪
从未绝不未曾
♪ Never, never, never ♪
我有停止爱你吗
♪ Did I ever stop loving you ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
宝贝 从来没有
♪ Never, baby ♪
我有停止爱你吗
♪ Did I stop loving you ♪
♪ Oh, no, oh ♪
从未绝不未曾
♪ Never, never, never ♪
宝贝 我有停止爱你吗
♪ Did I ever stop loving you, baby ♪
是的
♪ Yeah, oh ♪
从未 未曾
- ♪ Never, never. ♪